本视频仅供英语学习交流，严禁用于商业途径
更多资源敬请关注公众号：晨雨资料库
[ Ukulele Strumming ]
[ Jimmy ]
Bob! Hey!
Whoo-hoo!
[ Whistles ] Bob!
I think you missed a spot!
Oh, never mind.
That's just your mustache!
Ka-boom!
[ Laughing ]
Ha-ha.
Ha-ha, Jimmy!
Good one.
Uh, at least
I could grow one. You can't!
Gene? Louise?
How about a "ka-boom"?
You can do better
than that, Dad.
Yeah, step it up.
Okay, you do better.
Give me something.
How 'bout-- [ Exhales ]
I don't know.
Nice shoes, Jimmy. Do they
make them for men too? Ha!
All right, that's, uh--
that's good. Hey, Ji--
Oh.
They're gone.
God, I hate Jimmy Pesto...
with his crappy food...
and all his customers.
Forget about your silly rivalry
for one minute.
Bob, listen, come here.
Tina's birthday's
coming up,
and I think we should
do something special...
since she's turning 13.
This is the year
she becomes a woman.
I don't want to hear this.
Bob, she deserves
a special party this year.
If what it says
in her diary is true,
then I'd say she needs it.
A lot.
It's true.
Wait.
You read her diary?
- Yeah.
- What I can stomach.
- I just skim it to make sure
she's not on drugs.
- What-- What does it say?
- It says, "I'm not on drugs."
- It's pretty rough.
But she thinks things
will really turn around
this year.
Yeah, she dubbed it
"The Year of Tina."
Why is everyone
reading her diary?
It's well-written.
She's better on the page
than in person.
And what if the Nazis get us,
and it's all we have
of our family?
Okay, fine.
We'll make this birthday
extra-special.
All right.
Tina, sweetie, come here.
- Yeah?
- Listen, baby.
We'd like you
to have an extra-special
13th birthday party.
So take your time
and think about what would
make the perfect party.
- I'd like it to be
a boy-girl party.
- Mm-hmm.
With mingling.
Mmm.
I want to close the restaurant
and invite my whole class over.
No.
And I want there to be a deejay,
dancing and a smoke machine.
Mm-mmm.
About two hours into the party,
I want there to be a moment...
- where I see Jimmy Jr.
across the room.
- Hmm.
- And we're pulled
toward each other.
- Mm-mmm.
- We meet under
the disco ball.
- Mmm?
And we kiss until our bodies
and souls become one.
Oh, God.
And it's my first kiss.
Mmm.
And it's perfect,
and I remember it forever.
Freak.
Scary.
Wow! You really put
some thought into it.
That, uh,
sounds expensive.
And I could do
without the kissing
Pesto's kid part.
Oh. It's okay. I guess I wasn't
meant to have a good life.
Bob, a word?
Now?
Not now.
Now.
All right.
You want to kiss
Jimmy Pesto Jr.?
Yes. A lot.
Many times.
I can help you.
I'll be your
kissing coordinator.
It's my birthday present
to you.
Yeah, I think
I know how to kiss.
Ow!
Do ya? You think you know
how to kiss?
You know how to lock lips,
huh? Do ya?
Ow!
You think you know
what it feels like
to kiss a man, Tina?
If you don't know what you're
doing out there, you could get
yourself killed, or worse!
Ow! Ow!
S.T.D.'s, Tina.
Have you heard of 'em?
Have you heard of herpes?
Have you?
Yes. Yes.
Do you know what herpes
feels like on your mouth?
Yes.
What? What is it?
What?
Like, um, cuts
on your mouth.
That sounds right.
I'm gonna
slap Gene.
Ow!
Closing down the restaurant,
getting a smoke machine
and a deejay?
That's gonna add up.
We have nothing extra
this month, Lin.
Well, we gotta do
what we gotta do.
Look at her.
- [ Bob ]
She's so awkward.
- She's a good girl.
Okay. I'll talk to Fischoeder
about getting an extension
on the rent.
It's foggy.
Yes, it is.
Are you there?
I am.
[ Exhales ]
Why are we here
in the fog?
I-- I wanted to meet you,
and then you told me
to meet you here.
Oh, that's right.
It was a good idea.
I love the fog.
Listen, Mr. Fischoeder,
I know we talked about
never doing this again,
but if you can just give us
two extra weeks this month
on the rent--
I'm gonna
have to stop you
right there, Bob.
Were you going to follow
that up with anything?
No.
Oh.
Oh, I love the way the fog
feels under my cape.
Well, uh, right.
I'll get going.
Bob, listen,
what if I don't give you
an extension on your rent,
but I do give you
the opportunity to earn
some extra money...
in one of
my side businesses?
That sounds... sketchy.
Oh, it is, Bob.
Oh.
But you get
to wear this hat.
Oh!
So for the next week
I'll be driving a taxicab
to pay for Tina's party.
- And I'll be wearing this hat.
- Cool!
Cool hat or job?
- Job.
- Hat.
- Thank you, Dad.
This party is gonna sizzle.
[ Imitates Sizzling ]
Stop it.
Wait.
Wait, B-Bobby.
Yes?
When are you gonna have time
to drive a cab?
I'll work the full day
at the restaurant.
Then I'll go drive the cab
from 10:00 p.m. to 6:00 a.m.
Aw, Bob.
All right, all right.
Wait. Why do you
have to wear a hat?
Just let this
be fun for me.
Dad, you won't
regret this.
When I kiss Jimmy Jr.
under the disco ball,
it'll be like
we're all kissing Jimmy Jr.
under the disco ball.
I call first.
Really?
Well, if I'm gonna kiss him,
I don't want to go
after you guys.
I'll go last.
I'm fine with that.
We're not kissing
Jimmy Jr.
Yes, we are!
That's 10 pieces
of gum, Tina.
Chew! Chew!
[ Groaning ]
A kiss is like
a fight with mouths.
And... time.
Spit.
I'm going to
destroy this kiss.
[ Moaning ]
Ow!
Not yet.
There's my
Johnny Two-Jobs.
Making money
for the dream
birthday party.
Uh, okay.
Off into the night I go.
Bobby,
be safe out there.
And make chitchat.
You'll get more tips.
Yeah, and keep
the meter running.
Watch out for pukers.
And stay away from Route 1.
It's bumper-to-bumper
all the way to the interstate.
Tina, h-how did you
know that?
- I like traffic updates.
- Why?
I like when they say
"bumper-to-bumper."
- Bumper-to-bumper?
- [ Sighs ]
- Wow.
- Yeah. Uh, bye.
- [ Rat Squeaking ]
- [ Sighs ]
[ Scoffs ]
Stupid beaded seat cover.
[ Grunts ]
Oh, okay.
I get it.
♪ [ Radio: Soft Jazz ]
F.M.
Nice.
[ Whistles ]
Hey, guess what.
You're my first fare.
Oh, no! No. Oh--
[ Gags, Coughs ]
Ew!
Oh! No! Ohh! Aah!
Uh, where to,
ladies?
Fourth and Ocean,
doll.
Thanks for stopping.
Most cabbies are
too prudish to pick us up.
Huh. And, uh, that's
because you are--
Fabulous!
[ All Laughing ]
That's true.
Well, you're clearly
fabulous, yeah.
Eyes on the road,
mister.
Yeah, stop staring at us.
This ain't no library.
Don't fall in love,
Mr. Cabdriver.
You can't afford us.
Hey, who's
picking up who here?
[ Chuckling ]
Hey, don't worry, ladies.
I'm kidding.
I'm, uh-- I'm a married man.
So am I.
[ Laughing, Chattering ]
Now, Tina, anyone
can tie a cherry stem
with their tongue.
Let's see what you can do
with this banana peel.
Get it in there.
[ Muffled Grunting ]
Bobby!
Good morning!
You're home.
Yeah.
Guess who learned
a lot about transvestites
last night.
I was only on that Web site
for, like, two seconds.
What? No.
I was talking about me.
I picked up a group of
transvestite hookers...
who showed me
a side of this town
I never knew existed.
And, Gene, you're banned
from the computer
for two days.
After what I saw,
I-I'm fine with that.
[ Mumbling ]
What's a transvestite
hooker?
Bob, I'm not sure
this is appropriate
breakfast conversation.
I guess you're right.
Maybe I should just
try and go to--
Aah!
[ Snoring ]
Gene, honey,
I think he's sleeping.
I have to go to school.
Shh, shh.
Just hold still.
Ew.
Is this drool or sweat?
It's both. Your father
is a very moist sleeper.
[ Groaning ]
Aw, look at my two boys.
Nice.
Oh, a bow!
Let's put that
on Dad's head.
There's
your transvestite.
Get the camera.
I'm having a birthday party
this Saturday.
It's coed, because
I'm becoming a woman.
Coed?
My hands just got clammy.
Hey, Jimmy Jr.
Hi, Tina.
This is an invitation
to my birthday party.
Hey, I noticed you haven't
R.S.V.P.'d to my party yet.
Um, I need to ask my dad
for permission.
Can I let you know
later?
Sure, okay.
Butt.
♪ [ Rock ]
[ Man ]
♪ Lifting up the skirt
of the night ♪
♪ Look down, feel around
♪ Do what I do to get by
♪ Pulling down the pants
of the night ♪
♪ Fool, now it's not right
♪ To make fun of the night
Oh, how you
holding up, Bob?
Good.
I mean, I'm tired.
[ Yawns ]
And, um, I might be
a pimp.
You're gonna need
a bigger hat.
Well, you're still
Father of the Year.
Tina's party's gonna be amazing.
I got a disco ball
and streamers.
Right.
It's gonna be
like Buckingham Palace.
Yeah.
Studio 54.
Those are two
very different examples.
Well, you get the idea.
You know. It's a party.
So, is Tina happy?
Uh, she'll be happier
once Jimmy Jr. R.S.V.P.'s.
She's over
at Pesto's right now
to see if he'll come.
I told her
to show some skin.
[ Sobbing ]
So, how'd it go?
[ Thuds ]
Oh.
Jimmy Jr. isn't coming
to my birthday party,
even though he wants to,
because his dad
won't let him.
All because our dads
hate each other.
Oh.
Sorry, Tina.
Now I'll never know
how soft Jimmy Jr.'s lips are.
My guess is,
they're pretty soft.
Like a--
- Like a kitty cat's tummy.
- Gene, stop.
Without Jimmy Jr.,
I don't want to have a party.
Hey. Your father's been
working very hard
for this party, young lady.
It's going to happen.
Right, Bob?
[ Snoring ]
I'll refrost it.
It's still good.
Mmm. It's
delicious.
Bleh!
Tina, honey, your father's been
working his you-know-what off
driving a cab to pay for this.
Yeah, and we've rented
the smoke machine, so this party
is definitely happening.
You've been working
your you-know-what off?
I've been working
my ass off...
night and day,
training!
Louise,
take it easy.
Do you know what
she was like when I started
working with her?
She was a sick joke!
Now look at her!
Incoming!
Bob, you gotta
go talk some sense
into Jimmy Pesto.
This isn't fair.
Fine.
Uh, hey, Bob.
You look like crap.
[ Laughs ]
Nice.
Yeah, that was funny.
Jimmy, my daughter Tina said
that Jimmy Jr. isn't allowed
to go to her birthday party.
Whatever issues we have
shouldn't matter.
Just please
let Jimmy Jr. go.
Okay. Okay.
You know it's gonna
cost you, right?
- Oh, God.
- You see, Bob,
I'm a collector of rare
and exotic trophies.
- Well, that's pathetic.
- And you have something I want
to add to my collection.
Your mustache.
Your bushy, robust,
filthy eyesore
of a mustache.
What are you
talking about?
I want you to
shave your mustache...
and bring it over in a baggie,
and I'll pin it on the wall.
- Wh-Why?
- As a trophy.
Trophies!
Well, I'm not giving you
my mustache.
Well,
I'm not giving you
Jimmy Jr. then.
This is crazy.
Just let him go
to my daughter's party.
If you want
a bag of hair so bad,
why don't you just
pick it out of the food
you serve here?
Ka-boom!
How dare you.
No 'stache, no bash.
[ Bell Rings ]
So, what'd he say,
honey?
Are these lips
gonna see
any playing time?
Yeah, is Jimmy Jr.
coming to my party?
No, Tina.
I'm sorry. He's not.
[ Groans ]
What happened?
You two couldn't work it out?
No! We couldn't
work it out, Linda.
He said the only way he'll
let Jimmy Jr. go is if I shave
my mustache and give it to him.
So Jimmy Jr.
can come to my party?
What?
No, Tina.
But if all you have to do
is shave your mustache,
then he can come.
Yeah, it sounds to me
like you just said
that Jimmy Jr. can come.
That's what I heard.
Done deal.
I'm not shaving my mustache.
It's my mustache!
[ Grunting ]
Hey. No. Watch it.
You know, Bobby, you're
just as handsome without
the mustache, kinda.
Uh, so that's what we should
show our kids, Lin--
that it's okay
to negotiate
with terrorists?
I'd drive a cab every night for
the rest of my life for my kids,
but I'm not letting
Jimmy Pesto humiliate me.
You're
the most selfish father
in the world.
- Oh, Bob.
- Good night!
You can't shave it, Bob.
It's glorious.
Oh, I miss
having a mustache.
Miss it?
Honey, news flash.
I can see it from here.
You can see it
from space.
Stop it, Cha-Cha.
I will thumb your eyeballs
out of your skull.
Ay!
Hey, come on, Glitter.
Your-- I happen to like
the way your upper lip looks.
Thank you, Prince Valiant.
Your shift's almost over,
right, papi?
Uh, yeah, it is.
Why don't you join us
for a beer?
Yeah!
We'll throw back a few beers
and smoke some crack.
Crack?
Just the beer then?
What is that?
Oof! Your breath!
I know.
Bobby, listen.
Hmm?
All right,
I talked to Tina.
I told her how hard you've
been working, and she agreed
to come to the party tonight.
For a few minutes.
It's something.
[ Slurred ]
What party?
Bob, you're delirious.
Shh.
You are.
You're drunk.
I may or may not
have tried crack.
- Okay.
- Last night.
I don't think I did.
But if I did, I liked it.
Okay, Bobby, listen, go
take a nap, and I'll watch
the restaurant, please.
Take off your clothes.
Bobby!
I got to go to bed.
Bobby.
I don't want
to do this.
Stop it.
Get your hands off me,
sick idiot.
Such a freak.
Pull it together.
[ Groaning ]
I'm like an animal!
Keep your voice down.
I'm like King Kong!
Unbelievable.
I need to go to bed.
Good night.
Go get me
special pillow.
Hurry, hurry, hurry.
Hey, sleepy bear.
What time is it?
How much longer
till the party?
- It started a half hour ago.
- What?
Ow! [ Groans ]
You let me sleep all day?
Why didn't you wake me up?
I tried. That was not
the first pickle
I dropped on your face.
Oh.
♪ [ Pop ]
The boys hate dancing, and
the girls won't ask the boys.
It's a Mexican stalemate
out there.
Come on, boys.
You're the peanut butter.
Girls, you're the jelly.
Let's make
some sandwiches!
Oh, God,
why is Mort doing magic?
It's his gift to Tina.
Uh-oh.
I mean, ta-da!
[ Door Bell Jingles ]
[ Bob ]
Whoa.
Tina,
you look great.
[ Sighs ]
Maybe I can
cheer her up.
Louise, smoke me.
Whoo-hoo!
Tina,
dance with Mommy.
[ Grunting ]
It's a party.
All right!
- Did someone say party?
- They don't go to my school.
♪ [ Stops ]
I'm sorry, ladies. We're
closed for a private party.
We were invited
by Bob.
Bob?
You invited
transvestite prostitutes...
to our daughter's
birthday party?
No.
Maybe. I--
This week has been
kind of a blur.
All of you are coming
to my daughter's party.
We're gonna have so much fun.
Bring whoever you want.
[ Cheering ]
I might have
thrown it out there.
Is this
the sweet 13 party?
Dad, you brought
all your nighttime friends,
but you won't
shave your mustache
to get me Jimmy Jr.?
- [ Groans ]
- Where do I put my coat?
Oh, hey, Marshmallow.
So, Marshmallow,
how'd you get your name?
'Cause if you show me
a sweet potato pie,
I am on top of it.
I knew it!
Tina, I know you're upset
because Jimmy Jr.'s
not here,
and that there are
more transvestites
than you imagined, but--
Unless you're Jimmy Jr.
and you're here to kiss my lips,
I don't want to talk to you.
♪ [ Pop Continues ]
Come on, girl.
It's your party!
You might as well enjoy it.
It's like I always say.
When life gives you lemons,
tuck em'!
Uh, I think
what my girlfriend here
is trying to say is,
when it's time for you
to blossom into a woman,
you can't let anything
stop you.
Not a party,
not a boy,
and not a town full of doctors
who refuse to remove your penis.
And you have
a very good father, baby.
Never forget that.
It's true.
Not many fathers would make
the sacrifices your father made
to throw you this party.
Working two jobs.
The things he saw.
The things he smelled.
He deserves an award.
Bob, what'd you do?
You lost your nose cozy.
Oh, Bob.
You made yourself ugly
to save Tina's party.
Yes, Linda, this is why
I didn't want to do it.
But it's worth it
if it means Tina
will be a happy teenager.
Just stop staring.
Stop!
Don't do this.
I... just did it.
You don't need to.
I don't want you to.
You know how
mustaches work, right?
Well, don't give it
to Jimmy Pesto.
What about Jimmy Jr.?
Jimmy Jr. isn't gonna
make this party perfect.
You already have.
Really?
I'm sorry I didn't
appreciate everything
you've done for me.
I didn't appreciate it
as a girl, but I do
appreciate it as a woman.
It would have been nice to
hear you say that a minute ago.
Bastard.
Come and join
the party, Bob.
That's Jimmy Pesto, Cha-Cha,
the guy I was telling you about.
Wait.
That's Jimmy Pesto?
I know that guy.
We all
know that guy.
But we know him
as Baby Num Num.
Baby Num Num?
[ Laughs ] Wait.
Pesto is
one of your dates?
He wishes.
We run in the same circles.
He's a regular over
at the Desire Dungeon.
He's what's known
as a diaper lover.
You know what that is?
It's nasty.
[ Laughing ]
Jimmy Pesto is a diaper lover?
[ Chuckles ]
Hello, Bob.
Well, I see
I'm getting my trophy
after all.
Bup-bup-bup-bup.
Not so fast,
Baby Num Num.
[ Gasps ]
Baby-- How do you
know about that?
Hey, Baby.
Hi!
No.
[ Gasps ]
We just wanted to see
if "wittle" Baby Num Num--
Shh. Come on.
Quiet.
wanted to change his mind--
about letting Jimmy Jr.
go to Tina's party.
Or maybe he wants
the whole "westaurant"--
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
Come on.
to know about--
- Hey! We got fresh pie!
- how he likes to put on
diapers and poop in--
♪ [ Pop Continues ]
[ Gasps ]
I don't believe it.
Thanks, Dad.
You're the best pimp
I'm ever gonna have.
I've been waiting
to hear those words
all my life, Tina.
Happy birthday.
Bobby, come help me
with the candles.
This one goes out
to the birthday girl.
Pardon me.
Birthday woman.
[ Guests Applauding ]
♪ [ Man Singing Pop Ballad ]
I like your shirt.
Are those snaps?
Yes. Snap.
- One more.
- Snap.
[ Simultaneously ]
Wanna dance?
Yes.
It's go time, Tina.
I want his kids
to have hickeys.
[ Moaning ]
[ Man ]
♪ The rainwater drips
♪ Through the crack
in the ceiling ♪
♪ [ Continues ]
I just kissed
my first boy.
Me too.
Oh, boo-hoo.
♪ [ Continues ]
Mwah!
Hurry up and grow
that thing back.
I know. It's bad.
Now! Concentrate!
Push it out.
I'm trying, Lin.
Oh, let me cover it
with my finger.
That's okay.
I'm gonna glue this
to my chest
so I can wear V-necks!
[ Laughing ]
Glue it to your back!
Oh, glue it
to your palm!
♪ [ Continues ]
♪ Lifting up the skirt
of the night ♪
♪ Look down, feel around
Hold on now.
♪ Do what I do to get by
♪ Pulling down the pants
of the night ♪
Look at those tight pants.
♪ Fool, now it's not right
♪ To make fun of the night
♪ Ooh-ooh-ooh
♪ Hey, yeah
♪ Oh, yeah
♪ [ Vocalizing ]
[ Man Laughs ]
Huh?