本视频仅供英语学习交流，严禁用于商业途径
更多资源敬请关注公众号：晨雨资料库
[ Ukulele Strumming ]
Listen, pep talk.
Big day today.
It's our grand re-re-re-opening.
It's Labor Day weekend,
and it looks like Wonder Wharf
is getting mobbed,
You kids know where
you're supposed to be
while we're gone, right?
Tina,
you're on the grill.
My crotch is itchy.
- [ Both Groan ]
- Okay.
Are you telling me
as my daughter,
or as my grill cook?
Um, as--
Because my grill cook
would never tell me that.
Oh.
Also, my daughter...
should probably not say
anything like that to me.
Tell her. Tell your mom.
My crotch is itchy.
Come here, let me see.
Linda. Not now.
No, let's all see it.
No.
I'm just not sure
if I'll be any good
on the grill...
with just one free hand.
Okay, I'm just going to
keep moving here.
Louise,
you're working the counter.
I put your little step stool
back here.
But do not alter anything
on the chalkboard.
What if I think of
something better--
which would be
almost impossible
not to do.
You will not think
of something better, because
"New Bacon-ings" is perfect.
It's hilarious. Right?
You know what?
I'm taking the chalk.
[ Whispering ]
Like I don't have chalk.
Gene, you're outside,
nicely offering people
a free sample, all right?
I'm on it!
But people coming out
of the crematorium next door,
people obviously
in mourning--
Yeah?
Don't offer them samples.
Dad, when I'm in character
out there, I get in a zone!
I can't keep track
of who's in mourning
and who isn't.
Just-- Anyone with an urn--
Yeah?
Leave 'em alone!
I know you think
it's the Gene show out there,
Oh. Now my rash
smells like bacon,
and it doesn't itch anymore.
I think we're going to be okay.
Okay, Tina, thank you.
Dad, is the restaurant
gonna close?
[ Sighs ]
I don't know, Louise.
We're almost broke.
The whole town
thinks we're cannibals,
and I forgot our anniversary.
You'd have been better off
with Hugo, Linda.
Bob, please.
No, it's true.
I can't even satisfy you
with my kisses.
Sorry, kids.
No problem.
Thanks for the info.
Oh, Bobby!
Now you listen to me.