本视频仅供英语学习交流，严禁用于商业途径
更多资源敬请关注公众号：晨雨资料库
[ Ukulele Strumming ]
All right, listen.
You kids are gonna be on your
best behavior right now.
The landlord, Mr. Fischoeder,
is coming over to talk
about the lease,
and we don't know
if he's gonna renew.
He'll renew!
Well, we haven't always
paid our rent on time.
We never pay
our rent on time.
Thanks, Lin.
All right, listen.
Your mother and I are gonna
go make him some food.
That's gonna save us--
our food and our service.
You kids start cleaning now.
Pick that up!
And, Gene, you go outside
and try to drum up
some business.
I'll play
my triangle!
♪ Ding-da-da-ding
da-da-ding, da-da-ding ♪
No!
You don't understand
my music!
Shush. And here's
the other important thing.
When Fischoeder gets here,
you will not-- I repeat, not...
stare at him like he's
some kind of spectacle.
I don't ever stare at him.
I don't know what
you're talking about.
Yes, Mr. Fischoeder
is an eccentric.
Yes, he wears
a white suit.
And an eye patch.
And he drives
a golf cart everywhere.
[ Louise ]
He is one white cat away
from being a super villain.
[ Man ]
Mr. Fischoeder! Aah!
All right, but he
owns this building,
everybody.
He owns the amusement park
and just about everything
else in town,
so you're not
gonna stare at him
when he gets here.
♪ [ Whistling ]
♪ [ Nervous Humming ]
- Here we go!
- Bob, Linda.
Your children are refusing
to acknowledge me.
Uh, kids, stop doing that.
Acknowledge Mr. Fischoeder
right now.
Are you a superhero?
Can I feel your hair?
Stop! Stop!
Go clean something now,
all of you.
So, uh, Mr. Fischoeder,
you know, after all
these years,
I realized you've
never eaten my food.
Mm-hmm.
I want to present to you
one of my favorite
specialty burgers.
Oh, no offense, Bob,
but I have a policy
that I don't dine...
at any of my tenants'
establishments.
Oh. But I saw you eating
at Doucie Sushi.
That's different.
That place is incredible!
Have you had their starfish?
It melts in your mouth.
No? Nobody?
You?
No.
Anyway--
Quiet in here.
Like this a lot, Bob?
Yeah.
Well, I mean,
it's 12:30.
Sorta
the lunch lull.
The lunch lull.
That's what
we call it.
Huh.
Wow. Jimmy Pesto's
lunch lull is really busy.
[ Bob ]
Well, Jimmy Pesto's
is a pizza place--
if you're into that kind
of thing-- pizza.
- [ Chuckles ]
Stupid.
- I like pizza.
Pizza?
Where's pizza?
Shush.
Anyway,
when people want a burger--
a good American burger--
they have nowhere else
to go but--
Sorry. Sorry to interrupt.
Let me be honest with you.
I enjoy you, Bob.
Your mustache--
it's fascinating.
Thank you.
Do you mind if I--
You're touching it.
Yeah. I--
That's--
Yeah, you're--
It's really something.
- Thank you.
[ Moaning ]
Listen,
Jimmy Pesto has tendered
an offer on this space.
Jimmy Pesto?
He wants to move
over here?
Yes, he wants to move
his gift shop over here.
Gift shop?
This would be
an amazing gift shop!
[ Gasps ]
I can do all my Christmas
shopping here!
Yes!
No, no, no,
no, no, no.
Please, I-I think
if you tried my burger,
you'd see that--
Bob, you're always
late with the rent,
and Jimmy pays early.
Wait, wait, wait.
Mr. Fischoeder, please.
Before you make a decision,
just taste my burger.
Just taste it.
[ Sighs ]
Fine.
Another trip to the gym.
Jimmy Pesto may be
a good businessman,
[ Choking ]
but I think you'll find that,
unlike his microwaved junk,
my food is--
[ Choking Continues ]
Mr. Fischoeder?
Mr. Fischoeder.
[ Gasping ]
He's choking.
He's chok--
How do I do it?
You just push!
- What do I do?
- Push on his belly!
- Hit him in the crotch!
- No, Gene!
Don't hit him in the crotch.
- Yes! Hit him in the crotch!
- I'll hold his hair.
- Oh, my God! Oh, my God!
Linda, please.
Oh, my God!
Wow! He's turning blue!
Put his hand
in warm water!
He can't die!
- He cannot die in here!
- Let's move him outside.
No! Everybody,
hands around him!
Group Heimlich!
One, two, three!
Two, three!
- [ All Grunting ]
- [ Bob ] There it is!
- Holy crap!
- God.
Give him
some room, kids.
Give him room!
Oh. Ow.
So, um--
Ow.
Did you, uh--
Did you like it?
[ Groans ]
Your rent is due
Friday night.
And if you're late,
I'm giving your lease
to Jimmy Pesto.
Do you want me
to pack this to go?
You're gonna want
fries with that.
[ Linda ]
So, Mr. Fischoeder's okay.
But we've got to
pay the rent in full
by tomorrow night.
Paying the rent in full!
What's next?
Paying your other bills?
Don't worry.
We'll figure
something out.
- Right, Bobby?
- Jimmy fricking Pesto.
[ Linda ]
Oh, Bob.
You know,
Pesto's not his real name.
It's Poplopovich.
Of course it is.
The guy's a complete phony.
What is this
obsession with him?
I'm not obsessed
with him.
Yeah, you are.
You're both obsessed.
It's like you guys are
stalking each other.
[ No Audible Singing ]
[ Angry Scream ]
I could care less
about the guy.
I think you should both grow up,
at least for the kids' sake.
Let me see.
Ugh. The kids.
Why does Tina have to
like Jimmy Pesto Jr.?
Of all the
13-year-old boys
in the world.
Eh, she likes them too.
It's kind of romantic
though.
Two families at war,
a budding romance.
It's like
West Side Story!
[ Groans ]
♪ Du-dun, du-dun
du-dun ♪
Rumble!
Stop.
♪ Dun-dun-dun
You know, Louise is friends
with the twins now too--
Pesto's little boys,
Andy and Ollie.
No, no, no.
I'm calling a ban
on all the Pesto kids.
Our kids are going
to cease contact.
Let's be best friends
forever.
Okay.
Let's cut our hands
and press them together
and become blood brothers!
- Okay! [ Grunting ]
- No, spit brothers! Spit in
your hand and then shake.
Let's do both!
[ Spits ]
Sorry. I'm saving
my spit and blood
for my honeymoon.
Let's rub our eyes together.
You can get my pink eye.
Okay!
[ Both ]
Ow. Ow. Ow. Ow.
Ow. Ooh!
So hard to be friends
these days.
Hey, is that
your brother Jimmy
touching himself all over?
[ Ollie ]
Yeah, he's really
into slow dancing now.
[ Louise ]
He knows it's supposed to be
with other people, right?
It is?
Ugh. Look at Tina.
Kissed the guy,
and she still can't
get his attention.
She should try
pigs in a blanket.
That always
gets my attention.
Ahhh.
♪ [ Ballad, Faint ]
[ Grunts ]
[ Bells Dinging ]
Ugh.
What's he up to now?
What? Oh, my God!
"Now serving burgers."
Burgers!
That's it. It's time
for a showdown.
All right!
♪ We're going to a rumble
I'm gonna confront him.
♪ Gonna confront him
Confront him
right in the face.
♪ Yeah, right
in his handsome face ♪
- What?
You said
"handsome face."
You did.
It's a--
"Right in
his handsome face."
- I know what I said!
- You think he's handsome?
- God, yes.
- No! I'm saying it with anger.
Like, "you handsome face!"
He's so handsome you wanna--
you wanna punch him.
He looks
like Tom Selleck.
When I die,
I want you to cremate me...
and throw my ashes
in Tom Selleck's face.
[ Wheezing Laugh ]
That's a crazy request.
I get it.
All right, let's go.
Kids, watch
the restaurant.
♪ We're going to a rumble
♪ [ Man Singing: Operatic ]
Oh, Lord.
So many people.
Kids, watch
the restaurant.
Tina, watch
Restaurant, we both know
you can handle this.
Call me if you need me.
Love you.
Jimmy said he'll
be right out. You wanna
try a Pesto-colada?
Yeah, sure.
Lin!
What? Free drink.
Yuck. Look at that.
"Pasta la vista, baby"?
"Frank and Zelda
Oldies with Goodies"?
Ugh.
Some confrontation.
I want some action.
I need some action.
[ Gasps ]
There's Jimmy Jr.
[ Sighs ]
Busing tables has never
looked so sensual.
Yet so menial.
[ Tina ]
Yeah.
Here's Jimmy.
Now some fur's gonna fly.
Bob
of Bob's Burgers.
Jimmy so-called Pesto
of Jimmy Pesto's.
Let's skip the niceties,
shall we?
Pesto-colada
for the lady--
on the house.
Thank you.
Except for that nicety.
What are you doing,
Jimmy?
What?
Selling burgers,
coming after my lease.
What are you doing,
Jimmy Poplopovich?
Whoa.
Yeah.
Your name is not
what it says on the--
Mmm. Mmm!
Lin.
Mmm. Yum.
Stop.
That's good.
Bob, I run a business,
all right?
I don't know
what you're doing with
your fancy ingredients.
"I'm Bob,
and I like kale." Kale!
There's nothing wrong
with kale.
Why don't you call it
Snob's Burgers?
Snob's Burgers! Ha!
You think anything that
isn't frozen or rotten
is fancy, Jimmy.
Okay, Mr. Fancy Face.
Let's see who's
got customers.
Ah, da-di-di-di.
Ah, I got some.
Let's see who doesn't.
Oh, you.
[ Chuckles ]
I've-- I've got
customers, Jimmy.
They're not there right now.
They have a life.
Oh, yeah?
Well, good luck making rent
by tomorrow night.
Well, good luck trying
to steal my customers
with your Besto-Burger.
They'll never--
Oh, my God!
- Bob!
- Unbelievable.
We came to watch
the ball game.
I had the urge to sing Journey!
Come on, Linda.
We're leaving!
Go, go.
Go, go, go, go.
[ Slurping ]
♪ [ Continues ]
Hmm!
You're not gonna get
our lease, Jimmy!
- He's gonna get our lease.
- No, Bobby!
Forget about
Jimmy Pesto.
All we need is one
really good day of business,
and then we can pay our rent
and keep the place, huh?
Huh?
I guess
you're right.
- If we can pack
the house tomorrow.
- Sure! Packed house.
We can do that.
Let's have a family
brainstorm right now.
Gene, go!
Uh, live entertainment
featuring a mix of techno...
and Dad's favorite--
the triangle!
♪ A-ding-ding-ding
ding-ding, ding
ding-ding-ding ♪
No.
Tina, go!
Slow dancing.
Grind, grind.
No.
Grind.
Tina, stop.
What are you do--
Stop that.
Louise, what do you got?
When I was young and naive,
I would have said "arson,"
but I'm gonna go
with "voodoo."
Huh. I like arson.
No. Seriously, Dad--
voodoo.
I have a book.
No.
No, I have a book!
I'll go get it.
I got it!
Make some flyers
for half off, and good
for tomorrow night only.
You know, that might
bring some people in.
Yeah, yeah.
Okay, I found it.
Forget voodoo.
We're doing flyers.
What? Whose candy-ass
idea was that?
I'm out of the room
for five seconds!
Ah, we're on a roll.
Let's brainstorm something else.
Uh, Christmas card.
No, no, no.
We're done brainstorming.
We got it.
Oh. How 'bout we
shave our heads for
the Christmas card?
Spell our names wrong.
Shave our legs.
Totally soft, silky family.
I like it.
I have a book!
Nobody forget
what they just said.
I'm gonna go get some paper.
Mmm.
It's pretty good.
[ Laughs ]
[ Crying ]
It's not good!
Goin' in the garbage!
If I can get a lock of Jimmy
Pesto's hair, I'm pretty sure
I can control his mind.
Really?
I don't know.
I'm just skimming.
All I know is it works
on fools and imbeciles.
Oh, me, me. Can you help me
dance Jimmy Jr. back into
remembering we're going out?
Yes, I can. I just need
a lock of your hair.
Okay.
Can you help me get a gig
in the music business?
Hair.
So long, old friend.
♪ Bye-bye--
So if you stick the penny
into the potato,
you've just made a battery
out of a potato.
I've just made
a voodoo doll
out of a potato.
[ Both ]
Aww!
Who is it?
My sister, Tina.
She wants me
to make your brother
slow dance with her...
and remember
that they're going out.
Can you get a lock
of your brother's hair?
Yup.
- Aah!
- And you said I was crazy
for carrying this around.
Now who's laughing?
[ Laughing ] Me!
Ow! Ow! Ow! Ow!
[ Teacher ]
Settle down. Settle--
Hi, kids.
How was school?
[ Together ]
Good.
Yeah?
Mom, Andy and Ollie
are helping me with
a school project.
I'm gonna need 15 potatoes
and a lock of hair
from you and Dad.
Also rum and cigars,
if you have any.
- Wait. What's this for?
- English.
- You two have homework?
- A little.
- Not doing it.
Good, 'cause you're going down
to the pier to hand out flyers.
[ Grunting ]
Aah!
[ Blubbering ]
[ Rings ]
[ Tina ]
We're back.
Did you pass 'em out?
Yup. We saved the family.
Jimmy Pesto
even took one.
So did Jimmy One Wing.
He's a seagull I met.
What the hell?
"Tonight only
our competitor's flyers good
for 1/2 off your meal!
Plus a free T-shirt"?
- Oh, my God.
- Aw, Mort's bringing
his mother to dinner.
No. No. No!
Those are my customers!
This is a war now.
This is a war.
Listen, it's the theme
from Braveheart!
♪ Ding-ding-ding-ding
ding-ding-ding ♪
No!
Wait, wait.
This is the best part.
Dad, what are you doing?
Mm-mmm. Mm-mmm.
Shh! Gene, Tina, this
may be our last chance
to save the restaurant.
Your father needs
full concentration
right now.
He's attempting to make
the most difficult burger
known to man.
I've only seen him do it
once successfully.
And now he has to do it
in a mini sampler size.
- What is it?
- He calls it "The Meatsiah."
It's beef tartare
inside a burger,
medium-well,
inside
a burger Wellington.
Is Dad gonna die?
Maybe, honey.
Maybe.
Oh, he has to be happy
with that one.
So how is this gonna
save the restaurant?
Am I gonna put on
the burger suit and hand
these out in front?
Oh, no. We're going straight
to the source with these.
You're gonna be
handing these out
in Jimmy Pesto's restaurant.
- Whoa.
- That's right, whoa.
These samples are gonna
get us our rent money tonight,
so we can keep this place.
How are free samples
gonna get us money?
They'll try the samples,
and they'll love 'em,
but they'll want more. More!
They'll be craving
these burgers, itching
to get their fix!
- Like heroin.
- That's right, Son!
- Like heroin!
- Yes!
But this family's gonna
have to execute perfectly
to pull this off.
Where's Louise?
[ Louise ]
This one shall have
his first gig.
This one shall slow dance
upon that one.
♪ [ Drumming ]
And Mr. Jimmy Pesto's fate
is yet undetermined...
because I still need
to get some of his hair.
I'm gonna
go get it right now.
Wanna come?
We want to stay here.
Forever. We wanna stay
here forever and ever.
We want to be buried here!
Buried here!
Okay! I'll bury you
when I get back.
[ Jimmy ]
You're taking
hair donations?
That's right.
Mmm, for people
with mustache cancer?
Yeah.
It's a serious disease.
Hey, aren't you Bob's kid?
No! No, no.
Dad, Frank and Zelda both got
the scampi, and now they're
in the bathroom puking.
Oh, for God's sake.
Where am I gonna get another
piano player at this hour?
We could put on
some Boyz II Men,
and I could slow dance.
Hey, pepper, no!
For the thousandth time, no!
It's my passion, Dad!
Passion!
Ah!
I know a guy.
[ Rings ]
Hello. Bob's Burgers.
You tell Dad
where you were going?
Mm, he's working
on his burger bites.
Hey, there's a drum set.
Back me up!
Sorry, it'll just
be another minute.
We're really backed up in there.
Gene got his wish!
The voodoo is working!
How you doin'?
Nice shirt.
Oh, my God!
Gene's first
public performance!
[ Bob ]
These are almost done.
Is everybody ready?
Aw!
And my Tina's dancin'.
My little clam's
coming out of her shell.
I'm just gonna slip out
for one sec.
Okay, here we go.
Time to go win back
the restaurant!
Linda? Kids?
Oh, my God.
Gene was supposed
to wear the costume.
Well, you know what?
I'll do this myself.
This next number's
a slow jam.
It's called "Three Sides
Don't Make a Square."
♪ Ding, ding, ding
♪ Ding-ding
Ding-ding-ding ♪
♪ Da-ding-ding
Da-ding-ding ♪
[ Laughs ]
Thank you.
Ho-ho-ho! What happened?
Did you snap?
Did Mr. Fancy Face
take a trip
to the sexy store?
No.
It's a little small
on you.
A little tight
in the pickles, huh?
What's on the tray?
These are burger bites, Jimmy.
The best in the world.
I'm gonna show your customers
what real food is.
Here, try
a real burger, sir?
Hey.
Ah. Well.
Eh-eh.
I'm gonna go this way then.
Nah-nah-nah.
Yeah. Well, then I'm--
Deh-deh.
Don't poke me.
Aah!
Real burgers,
right across the street.
Hey, hey.
Just move.
[ Mocking ]
Shut-- What?
I didn't do it.
Yeah, I did--
[ Babbling ]
Oh, no.
Is that Dad?
And you people!
Traitors! Traitor family!
It's Gene's first
public performance.
You could've had me
at the ground floor, Dad.
Now I play the big rooms.
You gotta let the kids
have a little fun.
We have fun, Linda!
We have lots of fun!
- What's he wearin'?
- My buns.
With a few extra buns
hanging out the back.
♪ [ Rim Shot ]
Ooh! Hey, Dad!
I'm playing drums!
Oh, I'm so happy you're
playing drums, Louise!
Hey, you know what?
You should keep your freaky kids
locked up in your own place.
What did you say
about my kids?
- Hit him in his handsome groin!
- [ Both Grunting ]
Oh, watch it.
You-- I--
Ow!
Hey. Wait. Wait.
[ Grunting Continues ]
Get him, Dad.
Come on! Come on!
Don't worry, Dad!
[ Spits ]
Anything? Anything?
I got the samples, Bobby.
Aw, crap.
That looks silly.
Come for the rent?
Yes, I've come
for the rent.
Bob!
No, no. Let 'em fight.
Looks like a betting crowd.
Who wants three-to-one
against the burger?
Right here!
Here, let me see.
Let me see your money.
Here you go. Oh!
[ Quiet Grunting ]
All right.
It's a draw.
Who had "They end up
hugging each other"?
Me.
That's 10 to you.
Thank you.
Now, Bob, Jimmy,
let's all go over to
Jimmy's new gift shop--
I mean-- [ Chuckles ]
Sorry. Bob's place--
and settle this
over some nice
alcohol, hmm?
Bob?
[ Gulping ]
- Do you have the rent?
- [ Sighs ] No. Not all of it.
Okay then.
Here we go.
- Oh, God.
- Give me your hands.
- Um, sure.
- Do you cry easily?
Um, sometimes.
Well, let's
get it over with.
Bob, I will not
be renewing--
[ Sniffs ]
Oh, what is that
amazing smell?
Who's hungry?
- What are those?
- Only the holy grail of
hamburgers-- the Meatsiah!
Hmm. Are these
choke-resistant?
They're bite-sized!
Oh, good.
Mmm. Mmm. Mmm!
Huh?
I have never...
eaten a burger...
half--
[ Choking ]
Hit him
in the crotch!
I'm just kidding.
- [ Nervous Laughing ]
- ...as good as this.
This is great!
Yeah! Oh!
It's complicated.
It's-It's mystical.
It's-It's barbaric!
Thank you.
Mmm.
Mr. Fischoeder,
I-I wanted to--
I'm talking, Jimmy.
Yeah, I wanted--
I'm talking.
Bob, you might be
the worst tenant
I've ever had,
and I rent space
to a raccoon sanctuary.
I know. They're next door.
I've been meaning to
talk to you about--
Shh. It's okay.
Right.
I get it now.
You were trying to tell me the
other day, but I wouldn't listen
because I was choking to death.
Mr. Fischoeder,
I just have--
Jimmy, please! Please!
I was thinking about
my life, you see,
and how I didn't want it
to end in your pathetic
little restaurant...
on your sad,
filthy floor.
- Hey!
- But now I see it.
You're not
a businessman.
You don't care about
customers and money.
Ha!
No, I do. I do.
No, no.
You are an artist--
a beef artist.
A be-fartist,
a poet...
who writes with meat
and buns and pickles...
like a greasy,
heterosexual Walt Whitman.
Uh, thank you.
Okay. Well,
Mr. Fischoeder--
Jimmy!
No, it's fair--
Talk--
Please.
Which brings me
to your lease.
Things are a little greasy.
Shut up!
Which brings me
to your lease.
Let's extend it!
All right, Bobby!
- But I gotta make it
month-to-month.
- Oh.
Um, all right.
We'll take it.
- And I have to raise
your rent a little.
- Okay.
That's-- Yes.
Yeah. Right.
[ Together ] Daddy!
Andy, Ollie,
what are you doing here?
Voodoo!
What?
Yeah, and we switched
underpants!
[ Whispering ]
Ollie, that was a secret!
I couldn't hold it in anymore!
These are your kids?
And you thought my kids
were freaky?
Come on, boys.
We're leaving.
No, we wanna stay!
- Yeah, it's fun here!
- Yeah, Jimmy. It's fun here.
[ Grumbles ]
Shush.
All right!
Let's celebrate!
[ Cheering ]
Gene, uh,
do us the honor.
A little music?
[ Gasps ]
You believe in me.
Time to tickle the iron.
♪ A-ding, a-dong
A-ding-dong-ding ♪
Slow jam.
♪ Da-ding-ding
Da-ding-ding
Da-ding-ding ♪
[ Sighs ]
Come on, Jimmy Jr.
Let's get back to work.
No, Dad!
I'm gonna dance
with Tracy!
Tina.
Tina!
Ugh!
Yup. Voodoo works.
I am a god!
Am I doing this
right?
Mort, do I look sexy?
My pants aren't falling down,
are they, Mort?
When I dance,
sometimes my pants
fall down.
♪ [ Whistling ]
[ Gene ]
♪ A-ding-ding
♪ Da-ding-ding
♪ Da-ding-ding-dong
♪ A-ding-a, a-ding-a
a-ding-a, a-ding ♪
♪ A-ding-a, a-ding-a, a-dong
♪ [ Whistling Continues ]
Oh!
♪ A ding-ding
Bobby, go!
Come on, Bob.
Show us your
ding-ding!
[ Bob ]
♪ Ding-ding
♪ Da-ding-ding
[ Gene ]
♪ Da-da-da-da-da-da--