本视频仅供英语学习交流，严禁用于商业途径
更多资源敬请关注公众号：晨雨资料库
[ Ukulele Strumming ]
[ Crunching Loudly ]
[ Crunching Continues ]
[ Crunching Plays Back ]
Gene.
[ Crunching Continues ]
[ Sighs ]
Gene.
[ Burps ]
What?
Stop.
Bob, no more
newspaper, please.
My parents are gonna
be here any minute.
I know.
You know how I know
they're coming?
Because you go into a crazy
cleaning frenzy every time.
It's like the way animals
freak out before an earthquake.
That's nice.
That's not true!
She's spooked.
Louise, you're getting
cereal everywhere.
[ Voice Quavering ]
I'm having a seizure!
Put a wallet
in my mouth!
It passed.
Look at this place.
It's a disaster.
You haven't even
fixed the leak yet.
Come on.
Linda, the leak is contained.
[ Dripping ]
Bobby!
What?
You barely notice those.
[ Yelps ]
I'm okay.
Trust me, Bobby.
My mother will notice
that our ceiling is leaking.
[ Sighs ]
Yeah, you're right.
She will--
repeatedly and loudly.
Just fix it, please.
Be my all-American
fix-it man, Bobby.
Fine. I'll go up to the attic
and fix the leak.
But I also need you
and the kids to work out...
whose room my folks
are sleeping in,
because I have to go
check the bathroom
for stray hairs.
No one sheds
like this family.
It's like
a bunch of Chewbaccas.
So where are Grandma
and Grandpa gonna sleep?
Gene's room
smells like farts.
That makes sense.
Great. Well, we'll
put 'em in there then.
Maybe they'll leave sooner
when they smell farts.
Yeah.
Gene can sleep with me
in my room...
as long as he doesn't
mind my night terrors.
Huh?
Remember you let me watch
Night of the Living Dead
when I was eight?
So now I wake up every night
standing in the middle
of my room,
scratching the air
and kicking.
Oh, good.
Wait.
You still get those?
Yeah.
They're weirder now.
Oh, boy.
I think my subconscious fears
and my budding sexuality
are getting all mixed up.
Okay-- Tina, I don't
want to hear about this.
So I think I'm being
attacked by zombies
and I start screaming,
"Do you wanna make out?"
And I make out with it.
Hmm.
I might just bunk
with Gram and Gramps.
Okay, enough.
Gene, Louise,
you sleep in Tina's room.
Tina, you're quarantined.
You sleep alone.
We'll strap you down
or something.
Leave my lips free.
Hey. Hey!
Gene, just 'cause Grandma
and Grandpa are coming...
doesn't mean you're gonna
get out of doing homework.
How far are you
on that history report?
So far I just got the title--
"History: A Blast
From the Past."
Okay. After we get
my parents settled,
your father's gonna
help you with that.
- Right, Bob?
- Have it on my desk by 5:00.
I am not writing
your report for you.
Hey.
Okay, everybody, I have
an announcement to make.
I am on a ladder.
Stop shaking it.
I feel like I shouldn't
have to say that.
Dad, why do you get so mad
when Grandma Gloria...
and Grandpa Al
come over to visit?
Do you hate them?
I don't hate them.
Just Grandma.
Or-- I don't hate her,
just the sound she makes.
And her voice.
And the things she says.
Aye!
Al!
[ Gasping ]
[ Clears Throat ]
[ Groans ]
[ Shutter Clicks ]
Wanna hear
my impression of her?
Yes.
[ As Grandma ]
Al!
[ Linda ]
I'm not hearing
this, right?
Sorry. I mean,
she's your gram-gram.
We love her.
[ Whispers ]
We hate her.
I fixed the leak!
[ Linda ] Good!
Don't stay up there
too long,
'cause I want us all to
have a nice visit before
we open the restaurant!
Uh, I mean, almost done!
Huh?
[ Groans ]
Wow. This is amazing.
Whose room am I behind?
[ Tina, Muffled ]
Mine.
- [ Muffled ] Hi, Tina.
- Are you in the wall
or in my horse poster?
Please say "horse poster."
I'm a horse.
[ Imitates Whinnying ]
Oh, wait.
I can go sideways too.
Are you
in another dimension?
Do you see a lion or
a witch or a wardrobe?
A what?
A lion, a witch or a wardrobe!
- Why are you
saying that, Gene?
- It's a book.
Oh, right, right.
A kids' book. Yeah.
Yeah, by Salman Rushdie.
[ Scoffs ]
It's not
by Salman Rushdie.
Of course it is.
It isn't.
Yes, it is.
I'm not gonna talk
to you any more, Gene.
I'm in a wall.
Go look it up though.
I just did.
It's Salman Rushdie.
[ Doorbell Rings ]
[ Linda ]
They're here!
[ Linda ] Bob, come out
of the wall, please!
Yeah.
Hello!
[ Grunting ]
[ Grandma ]
Al!
Oh, my God.
Don't leave our bags
out there on the street!
Are you crazy?
[ Clears Throat ]
What are all these pots
doing on the floor?
Bob will
pick 'em up, Mom.
Bob, quit
fooling around in there.
You're gonna
get yourself stuck.
Uh-- Uh, uh-oh!
Lin? Lin?
Yes? What?
You're never
gonna believe this.
What is it? What?
I'm stuck!
[ Sniffs ]
Shouldn't have farted.
[ Grandma ]
Who's trapped in the wall?
Bob.
[ Bob ]
Me.
Bob can't fit in the wall.
He's overweight!
Mom!
What?
He can't hear me.
[ Bob ]
Yes, I can.
I'm right here.
Uh, I'd like to
order a hamburger.
No, Al!
He can't have a hamburger.
He can have a turkey burger.
There's no such thing
as a turkey burger.
Go read your Maxim.
Dad gets Maxim?
No. He found it
in the recycling
at the condo.
Who's on the cover?
The girls of Coyote Ugly.
I don't think they're
even alive anymore.
Lin, we need to open
the restaurant.
Hey, I bet
I can get down there.
What are you talking about?
You can go down?
[ Bob ]
Kids, you meet me
down there, okay?
You're gonna be
my eyes and my hands.
Okay. We're down there.
No, you're not.
You haven't moved.
I'm turning on the grill!
Beep, boop. Whoosh!
That's not the sound
the grill makes.
Go down to the restaurant.
Okay, so the special
comes with feta cheese,
and it's called
"Never Been Feta."
[ Chuckles ]
Did you hear that?
Are you laughing?
[ Laughing ]
I hear you laughing.
Are you writing it?
Yep. "Never Been Feta."
Good. All right,
I'm gonna go...
get Tina set up
on the grill.
This is going great!
[ Grunting ]
Hey, kids. Gene.
Louise.
Hey!
Hey. Take this.
That's my pee.
Oh.
Yeah.
[ Groans ]
Empty it out
and bring it back, okay?
This will be our system.
Uh--
You're my pee guy.
Dad's pee.
[ Groans ]
Bob, I called Teddy
the contractor.
He's coming right away
to get you out.
What? No.
Lin, that's not necessary.
Of course it is.
You're stuck in the wall.
No, I know. Just--
You know how Teddy is.
Talky Teddy.
Yap, yap, yap.
What, you don't have time
for his stories?
Are you very, very
busy today?
Uh, no.
You're in a tight spot,
huh, Bobby?
A little bit, Teddy.
Gee.
I've heard of buildings
like this, you know,
with false walls.
- Uh-huh.
- It's a prohibition thing.
Oh.
Yeah, this town, it used
to be a bootleggers' port.
A lot of people
don't know that.
That's interesting.
Yeah.
My great uncle used to run
a speakeasy here in town.
Uh-huh.
It was called Swanky's.
Place was called Swanky's.
You ever hear of a cocktail
called the Swanky Panky?
No.
It's made with
two parts vermouth--
Teddy, Teddy, Teddy. Listen.
Don't get me out
today, okay?
Tell Linda you have
to come back tomorrow.
I got the Sawzall
in the truck. I don't even--
No, no. Teddy, listen.
Tell her that you need
a permit or something.
You want to stay
in the wall, Bob?
Don't judge, Teddy.
Don't judge.
There's nothing wrong
with a man enjoying
his crawl space...
till his in-laws leave.
No, it's just, you know,
I heard about this guy...
that hid out in a wall
from the police.
He went bonkers, Bob.
Yeah.
When they found him, he was
chewing on a two-by-four--
Mm-hmm.
wearing nothing
but copper wire.
That's a great story, Teddy.
Just come back tomorrow.
Okay. I still gotta
charge you for today though.
Today? You just
stood there, talking.
Bob, you know, my therapist says
that if I don't value my time,
nobody's going to.
All right.
You're right. Right.
I'm just gonna write it up...
as a consultation though--
friend prices.
Do whatever you have to do,
and just drop the bill
down the shaft.
All right.
[ Teddy ]
Did you get it?
[ Bob ] Did you drop it?
[ Teddy ]
I dropped it.
I didn't get it.
[ Teddy ] Well, I can't have
the-- you know,
the things outstanding.
Teddy, I'll look for it,
all right?
Find it.
[ Bob ] Write another one then!
I don't have--
Now I gotta go to the truck.
Okay. As you can see,
I'm spending my first night
inside the walls
of my own house.
I borrowed Gene's camera
so I can document my experience.
[ Linda ]
Come on, Bob.
It's late.
And Louise has loaned me
her Kuchi Kupi night light.
[ Louise ] Kuchi Kopi.
Kuchi Kopi.
Kuchi Kopi night light.
Anyway, here's where
I'm gonna sleep tonight.
I'll show you.
[ Grandma ]
Oh! Al! Yes!
[ Grandma Moaning ]
Oh, my God.
Oh, my God. I think
Linda's parents are having sex.
[ Moaning Continues ]
I hope they're using protection,
'cause I am not
taking care of that baby.
I'm gonna sample it.
[ Grandma Continues
Moaning ]
[ Moaning ]
Well, hello.
Funny seeing you here.
Whoa.
Double trouble.
Okay, let's do this.
[ Groaning ]
- You sound like my grandmother.
- What? I can't hear you.
And you sound
like my grandfather.
[ Moaning ]
Please stop touching each other.
[ Screams ]
[ Grandma Continues
Moaning ]
[ Snoring ]
[ Barking Sounds ]
Gene, you ready
to give your report?
Oh. Uh--
My grandparents are staying
with us, and they were both
alive during prohibition.
So this is what it sounds like
when they have sex
in the room next to mine.
[ Grandma ]
Ow! Ow! [ Moans ]
[ Skipping ]
Ow-Ow-Ow-Ow-Ow!
[ Grandpa ]
What?
Ow!
Principal's office now!
[ Moans ]
[ Skipping ]
Ow-Ow-Ow-Ow-Ow!
[ Grandpa ] Right.
[ Grandma Moaning ]
[ Clapping ]
Father, in life, this
restaurant was your curse.
Now, in death, your restless
spirit haunts this place.
Speak to us, Father!
[ Bob, Muffled ]
Louise, is that you?
Did you hear that?
Yes. It's Louise,
your daughter.
Go to the light, Father!
[ Bob ] Oh, okay,
I see. Very funny.
I'm a ghost.
Ask him anything
you want to know
about the other side.
Are you the ghost
from the movie Ghost?
No. Louise already
told you I'm the ghost
of her dead dad.
Come on.
Next question.
Are you the ghost from
the movie Ghost Dad?
What did I just say?
This is what
you ask a ghost?
You know what this
makes me wanna do?
Eat your souls!
Run!
[ Screaming ]
Oh, God!
He got me!
Oh, at least
you're holding me now.
What is going on over here?
Uh, sorry, Lin.
Well, I'm glad
you're enjoying yourself.
I'll go back to running
the kitchen, bussing tables
and taking care of the kids.
Oh, boy. Lin, don't be mad.
Come here.
Oh.
Come over
toward my hand.
All right, all right.
Let me stroke your hair
the way you like.
Oh.
[ Chuckles ]
Isn't this nice?
[ Coughing, Hacking ]
Oh, God.
Excuse me.
I'm sorry.
Linda, that's your mom's
throat clear exactly.
Yes, and?
Well, first you make
sounds like her.
Next thing, you'll be yelling,
"No burgers! Read your Maxim!"
I mean, you already
kind of nag like she does.
Whoop.
Where's the hair?
I am not
turning into my mother!
That bathroom is filthy!
Who was the last person
in there?
You go back in there
and you wipe the seat!
[ Bob ]
Hey, no nagging
my customers!
Don't you yell
at my mother!
What's that,
Nagatha Christie?
Linda, sweetheart, you've got
more than you can handle here.
Your father and I have decided
to stay another night.
What? No!
[ Grandma ]
We'll stay as long
as we need to.
No, no, no! No!
Knock, knock.
Who's there?
I got detention.
Aw, come on!
Yeah. But I don't want
to beat myself up about it,
since it's really Dad's fault.
[ Gasps ]
It's your history report.
Yeah.
Thanks, Mom. We're gonna--
You know what?
We're gonna need you.
We'll take all the help
we can get around here.
No, no, no. No.
Linda, I'm gonna
get out of here.
They don't have to stay.
I have an idea, a new idea
I just thought of on how
I can get out right away.
[ Groaning ]
Oh, boy.
[ Feet Thud On Floor ]
Ow.
Ow! Son of a bitch!
Where did he go?
[ Grunting ]
I can hear--
I can hear him.
Lin?
Yeah?
I'm stuck.
Yeah, I know, Bob.
No, I'm really stuck.
What are you talking about?
[ Gasps ]
Are you telling me
you weren't stuck before?
No.
You were faking it.
I can't believe this.
[ Phone Rings ]
Bob's Burgers.
Hi, Linda.
It's Teddy.
Oh, hi, Teddy.
Hey, I'm on my way over
to get Bob out.
You know what?
We actually don't need you
to come and get Bob out.
Oh, really?
Yeah. He's fine.
What? No! We--
Teddy! Ted-- We need--
I need to come out!
Bye, Teddy.
[ Teddy ]
Hold on. I gotta--
- Teddy!
- Have fun in there!
Linda!
Okay, day three
stuck in the wall.
I sure would love to go poo.
That would be good.
[ Grunts ]
Ow!
Yep. Okay.
I can't get out that way.
[ Groans ]
I got a big splinter.
I'm feeling a little faint.
[ Groans ]
Keep it together, Bob.
Uh, there are
spiders everywhere!
[ Screams ]
On me! On me!
Spid--
You understand me,
don't you, night light?
[ Sniffling, Crying ]
[ Man ]
Tell me--
Why did you want
to have a séance
in your family's restaurant?
And when exactly
did your father pass away?
[ Sighs ]
I forget.
Give me your hands.
Let's summon his spirit now.
If that'll help, sure.
Okay. I need you to hum
with me, please.
- Hum with you?
- Yeah.
[ Both Humming ]
[ Humming Rhythmically ]
Big door.
Was this always here?
♪ [ Jazz ]
Wow. There's a speakeasy
in the crawl space.
What a great idea.
Nice to see you,
Mr. Bob.
Nice to see you, Kuchi Kopi.
What'll it be, Mr. Bob?
Give me some hooch.
Your best bootleg hooch.
[ Tongue Flapping, Chuckles ]
How are things going,
Mr. Bob?
Things could be better, Kuchi.
Things could be
a whole lot better.
Do you need to use
the facilities, Mr. Bob?
Go number two?
I'm glad you asked, Kuchi.
Yes, I do
need to go number two.
Yes, I do-- a lot.
Here's my creation.
I call it the Tunami.
You're gonna sell
a million of these.
Hmm.
You know, that tastes
so good, I say we make it
the Burger of the Day.
So, your mother-in-law
is quite willful.
Yeah, she is.
She needs to be corrected.
- What does that mean?
- Killed.
Wow. You turned into
a mean little
night light, Kuchi.
Did you know your wife
and your mother-in-law...
are trying to interfere
with your business?
They are?
My business?
Yes.
They are attempting to bring
an outside protein...
into this situation.
An outside protein?
- Tuna.
- Tuna?
[ Thinking ]
I'm so tired.
My grandparents
are haunting my dreams.
I need a nap.
I could crawl up
in the ceiling and sleep.
That's what dad would do.
Yeah.
I'm gonna make him proud of me.
Oh, it's nice up here.
[ Boy ] Man, you're ripped.
Your abs look like
challah bread.
[ Boy #2 ] Thanks.
You look pretty strong--
Oh, my God.
The boys' locker room
must be right over there.
I'll sleep later.
[ Bob Whispering ]
Poison.
What?
Mercury poisoning
in the tuna fish!
[ Laughs ]
Bob, stop.
[ Kuchi, Mocking ]
"Bob, stop."
[ Bob ] Good one, Kuchi.
Who are you talking to?
Oh, no one.
Just a friend.
He's losing it in there.
Okay, it's time
for you to come out.
There is no out, Linda.
Not anymore.
Where am I?
Am I here, or am I here?
Bob--
I'm everywhere!
I'm calling
the fire department.
[ Tina Whispering ]
Drop the towel.
There it is again.
Did you hear it?
Drop the--
[ Both Scream ]
[ Counselor ]
Three siblings in trouble
in two days?
That's a red flag right there.
What's going on with you guys?
Our father got trapped
in the wall.
Is that how he died?
Dad's dead?
Good job, Mr. Frond.
We were gonna tell her
on Father's Day.
Now we have nothing
to do on Father's Day!
Okay.
You know what you are?
You are kids in crisis.
We need to conduct
a home visit today.
Yeah!
Okay. Okay.
Let's get over there.
Oh, my gosh.
What are those?
- Grief puppets.
- Bring 'em.
We're gonna need 'em.
[ Gasps ]
What about those?
Are you gonna bring those?
- Crisis crayons? You think?
- Crisis crayons, absolutely.
I've got so many drawings
that I need to do.
[ Giggles ]
[ Linda ]
Hey, I'm sorry.
It's a little loud in here.
You're coming for
a home visit when?
Right there.
Chop.
[ Bob ]
Don't do it.
I'm staying in here.
He's loopy. Chop.
I'm never coming out!
Yeah, we see this all the time.
I'll chop a hole, but it's
probably not gonna do it.
You'll have
to put some food out.
What's going on?
They probably got complaints
about the smell...
and came to get
the body out of the wall.
You mean
it's still in there?
Well, parts of him.
Oh, my God.
It's a real crisis,
Mr. Frond!
- Yeah.
- It's a crisis!
- Yeah!
We're all in crisis!
I'm in crisis!
All right! Okay.
Don't you take my daddy
out of the wall!
Bob, I'm sitting here
with the counselor from school
who thinks you're dead,
so this would be a great time
to grow up and help out.
[ Footfalls ]
Counselor?
What is this, camp?
[ Chuckles ]
I'm funny in the wall.
Wait-- Ho, ho, ho, ho,
ho, ho, ho, ho.
Your husband is not dead?
No. Just aggravating.
Okay.
Why would Louise let me
think that he was dead?
Oh, she just likes messing
with people she thinks
are stup--
I know!
What? I--
How about a burger?
I don't-- I--
You want something from
the restaurant? A burger?
No. I don't eat meat.
Oh.
[ Kuchi ] Kill him.
[ Bob ]
Shut up, Kuchi.
I've got some nice
ground beef for you, Bob!
[ Coughing ]
Bob!
I'm starting to get
a better picture here.
Right now I'm looking up
guidelines...
for when and how
Social Services should get
involved in a case like this.
- What?
- Yeah.
- Social Services?
- What?
- Yeah!
[ Clearing Throat, Coughing ]
That throat-clearing sound--
it's coming from
inside the wall!
Bob!
Oh, my God!
Bob, come towards my voice.
I'll yell.
[ Yelling ]
[ Screams ]
[ Rapid Footfalls ]
My mother's visiting us.
[ Grandma ]
Stop crawling away!
[ Bob ]
This isn't happening!
[ Grandma ]
Get ahold of yourself!
[ Bob ]
Don't shake me!
I might go to the bathroom!
Here's Bobby!
I found him.
[ Yelps ]
Ow! That's hot!
[ Grandma Exclaims ]
[ Bob Coughs ]
[ Bob Moans ]
[ Grandma Moans ]
[ Bob ]
Ow!
[ Moans ]
[ Grandma ]
Ow!
[ Moans ]
[ Toilet Flushes ]
[ Groans ]
Wow.
Much better.
Bad modeling,
poor boundaries--
Well, really,
no boundaries.
[ Chuckles ]
I'm gonna have
to make some calls.
Wait. Mr. Frond,
now that I have
a clear head,
I want to apologize--
to everybody.
Hiding in the walls
was selfish and dumb.
And, Linda,
I'm sorry I called you
Nagatha Christie.
It was in the heat
of the moment,
and it was really dumb.
Aw. Thank you, Bobby.
I meant I can do better.
Like Spiro Nagnew.
[ Chuckles ]
All right.
Quit while you're ahead.
Naggedy Ann?
Secretary of Nagriculture?
Ha!
Now that one's funny.
That one's funny.
I like--
[ Chuckles ]
I'm not a-- I'm not a nag.
It's funny though.
I like it.
Social Services?
Now hold on there, pal.
Hey--
Are you married?
You have kids?
No, and no.
Listen to me.
My daughter is the best
mother in the world,
and this one--
he is nuts,
but guess what.
Having a family
makes you go nuts.
So if you don't
have kids,
I don't think
you know enough to be
calling in anyone.
In fact, I don't think you
come out looking so good
here yourself.
I wonder if you even got
permission from the school
to come over here today.
- He didn't.
- He took us away from learning!
We were in the car with
Mr. Frond, and he didn't
make us wear seat belts.
What?
[ Stammering ]
How about you put your phone
and your little notebook back
in your pocket there...
and leave this
family alone!
[ Gasps ]
Okay. All right.
All right.
[ Chuckling ]
Gloria, thank you.
Come back soon, you two.
Bye, Gram.
Bye, Gramps.
See you in my dreams.
Well, I have a room
to re-fart.
Dad, can I have
my night light back now?
No.
Give it to me.
Stop it.
Give it!
Stop it!
It's my night light.
Don't-- Stop.
This is embarrassing to me!
No!
You're a grown man!
I'm keeping it!