本视频仅供英语学习交流，严禁用于商业途径
更多资源敬请关注公众号：晨雨资料库
[ Ukele strumming ]
Okay, kids, thank you for
joining me here in the walk-in.
Thank you all.
You said we had to, so--
[ Bob ]
Shush.
Brrr! I should've
brought my cardigan.
I have an announcement
about the restaurant.
Here in this box is the beef
that will
make our--
Gene, drumroll,
please.
♪ [ Imitating Drumroll ]
- Okay, enough.
- ♪ [ Drumroll Continues ]
Gene.
♪ [ Drumroll Stops ]
Here in this box is the beef
that will make our
100,000th burger.
Wow.
Can I touch it?
I wanna touch it too.
I wanna feel it
between my toes. Mmm.
I wanna put a stick
of dynamite in it
and blow it up.
No. What is wrong
with all of you? No one's
touching this meat but me.
I have
an announcement too.
My bra's chafing me.
That's not
a real announcement.
- Oh, I have one.
I love... house music.
There. I said it.
♪ [ Imitates Beats ]
And I'm going to get
my gun license, finally.
- Oh, congratulations.
Can't believe they're
making you wait three days.
Stop stealing my thunder!
I found the banner!
It's from
our old printer.
You just have to tear off
the holes on the side.
We were supposed to hit
100,000 ages ago.
[ Chuckles ]
We were way off.
[ Gene ] Yeah.
[ Louise ]
Big time.
[ Chuckles ]
Can I--
Let me just--
- No. Stop it.
[ Tina Sighs ]
There it is.
Get it!
- Dive!
Oh, my God.
[ Sighs ]
[ Moans ]
[ Sizzling ]
Are you number 100,000?
[ High-pitched Voice ]
No.
[ Normal Voice ]
Are you mad at me?
[ High-pitched Voice ]
No.
[ Normal Voice ]
Oh, burger, you're cute.
[ High-pitched Voice ]
You're cute too.
[ Normal Voice ]
I'm not.
Whoa, whoa. Linda,
I think the news is here.
I wonder if they heard
about our 100,000th burger.
[ Squeaking ]
[ Shouts ]
What?
[ Clears Throat ]
Hi. How are you?
What can I do for you?
Are you Bob?
Uh, yeah. I am.
I'm Randy Watkins,
the documentary filmmaker.
Okay. Uh--
We're making a film
about the beef industry.
I heard you
were about to hit
your 100,000th burger,
and I wanted
to shake your hand.
Oh. Yeah. Um--
Because you, sir,
have blood
on your hands.
Ew. Is this ketchup?
It's the blood
of a hundred thousand
slaughtered cows.
You ketchup'd me.
We're here to force you
to face your victims.
Meet your meat.
- What the hell?
- Her name is Moolisa.
She's due to be "processed"
in five days, Bob,
unless you choose
to spare her life.
- Wh-Why?
- That's right.
You will decide her fate.
It's a cow-ntdown.
- [ Timer Beeping ]
- We'll see what your
conscience tells you...
when you're
looking your burger
right in the eye.
Ow. This is ridiculous.
It's not a crime
to make burgers.
There's no blood
on our hands.
[ Bell Rings ]
What's all
the yelling about?
[ Louise ] Turns out Dad's
been putting murdered cows
in our hamburgers.
And you made us
a part of it.
You make me sick.
Kids, please.
- Oh, look. A cow.
Hello, blondie.
Oops. I got some meat on you.
Dead cow on live cow. Gross.
[ Chuckles ]
Oh, my God.
Uh, not a good time, Linda.
[ Chuckles ]
Ooh.
Randy, stop.
Stop filming.
We're not gonna be in your
cow documentary anymore.
Well, you don't really
have a choice, Bob,
'cause I stop at nothing
to expose injustice
to animals.
Is that wig glued on?
Yeah. It's the only way
it would stay put.
It's to humanize her.
It's cute.
- Hmm. I've seen cuter.
Honestly, she's a four.
Randy,
I-I don't know where to begin.
This isn't even a female cow.
Beef happens
to come from steers,
which are male cows.
Then, uh, how do you
explain that udder?
Whoa. What an udder.
[ Bob ]
Get away from there, Tina.
That's, um, not an udder.
Oh, it's not?
Don't listen to him, Randy.
Go ahead and milk that cow.
Milk it good.
- Oh, we did.
You shouldn't have.
Milk doesn't come out of that.
Something came out of it
in that bucket over there.
You mean this bucket
of urine?
I know urine,
and that's urine.
Gene, put that down.
- No!
Well, it certainly
smells like urine.
But that's probably
because she's sick.
No, she's not sick.
Sick of your practices, Bob!
Okay. We're gonna go inside
and call Animal Control,
and then you'll have to leave.
[ Kids ]
Aw!
So you've got all
your permits, and you're
renting this storefront?
Yes.
Oh, yeah.
And this cow has had
all its shots?
Yes.
Sure, sure,
sure, sure.
All right. Well, great.
My job is done.
I'll see you guys later.
[ Both ]
Bye!
Bye, animal man.
What?
Will you sign a release
to be in the movie?
Yeah. A movie? Yes.
You're gonna be a star.
Excuse me.
Thank you.
Hello. The person
who called you.
Thank you.
You can't have a cow
on the sidewalk.
It's dangerous.
Sir, sir,
the only thing dangerous
about this cow
is how adorable it is.
Moo!
Put your hand on this cow
and touch it.
What?
I just know that
that's gonna help you.
[ Chanting ]
Touch the cow.
I'm walking away.
[ Gene ]
Touch it.
Oh, right.
Run away, tough guy!
Yeah!
Go take a meat bath...
or whatever it is
you people do!
[ Man ]
Dial "M" for Mooder,
interview one, take one.
[ Clears Throat ]
♪ Ma, ma, ma, ma,
me, me, me, me ♪
Perfect.
Do you think cows should
be ground up for food?
Personally,
I don't really care.
But my father,
he loves grinding them up.
Gives him a rush,
makes him feel alive.
Daddy's a bad, bad man.
Is this movie
gonna have a score?
You know, some music
to tug at the heartstrings.
I haven't thought
about it yet.
Well, check this out.
♪ [ Backbeat ]
[ Dog Barks ]
Think about it.
Louise, what does that
look like to you?
Cow poop.
Good eye, Tina. Good eye.
No. I mean
it's in the shape
of a smiley face,
like an emoticon.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
You think the cow
is texting you an emoticon
with its butt.
Very interesting.
Maybe this cow is trying
to communicate with us...
the only way it knows how--
with its feces.
Like Gram-Gram used to do.
Mom, let's say you had
a brilliant plan,
but to execute it, you
needed to write something
using cow poop.
- How would you do it?
- Oh. Is this a brain teaser?
Hmm. I would use
a frosting bag.
Do we have one?
Yeah. In the pantry.
Am I right?
Is it a frosting bag?
We'll see, Mom.
Bye.
[ Bell Rings ]
[ Chuckling ]
[ Sinister Laughter ]
[ Laughter Continues ]
[ Laughter Stops ]
Yeah.
Okeydokey.
Bye, kids.
Have a good day.
[ Louise ]
Murderer!
[ Groans ]
Oh. Hi, Randy.
Whoa.
Wink with open smile.
Is this for me?
It has to be.
What should I do?
Should I text back?
Coming through.
[ Squishing ]
Oh, no.
Ugh.
Hmm.
[ Woman ]
Aw. Look at him.
[ Man ]
So cute. Makes me hungry.
[ Woman ]
Honey, I want
a burger right now.
[ Voice Amplified ]
What's wrong
with you people?
[ Voice Amplified ]
Yeah. What's wrong
with you people?
Now, let's talk
about your music budget.
[ Voice Amplified ]
Is it a million?
We only need
one megaphone out here!
[ Voice Amplified ]
You know what you need?
You need this!
♪ [ Backbeat ]
[ Dog Barks ]
[ Voice Amplified ]
Think about it!
Wow! We're mobbed.
Thank you, documentary.
Linda, the documentary's
about me being
an evil cow killer.
[ Louise ]
Murderer!
Oh, come on, Bob.
There's no such thing
as bad publicity.
This could be huge for us.
Like a sex tape.
Ugh.
It's the best free
advertising we ever had.
I know.
It's almost sad.
For who?
- I don't know. The cow?
- The cow's going out
in a blaze of glory.
Everybody wins, Bob.
I guess you're right.
I mean, looks kind
of sweet out there--
enjoying the day,
meeting people.
Hi, cow. I'm gonna eat you.
Whoa.
Can it hear us?
[ Munches ]
[ Munching ]
Easy.
Like sands through
the hourglass,
there goes my teeth
right into your back.
That's my wife.
Ah, Bobby,
I'm friggin' starving.
Who could eat
that beautiful creature?
Shame on you!
Are you going
to be eating a burger today?
We wouldn't dream
of eating an animal.
We run a petting zoo
by the interstate.
It's called
Mother Goose's
Discount Petting Zoo.
Petting horses,
goats and sheep.
Precious memories
on the cheap.
It's basically
an animal sanctuary...
that we make money off of.
Exactly.
[ Chuckles ]
[ Light Switch Clicks ]
[ Timer Beeping ]
Oh, hey, Randy,
thanks for the business.
Oh, hey, Bob,
you're welcome.
I'm gonna go to bed soon.
What are you gonna do?
Oh, I'll probably
go to bed too,
'cause I'm a person.
Bye.
M-Moolisa, watch out!
No!
[ Gavel Pounding ]
Bring in the accused.
[ Crowd Jeering ]
Yeah, yeah.
Louise,
you're defending me?
[ Gavel Pounding ]
This so-called "man"
stands accused...
of murdering nearly
a hundred thousand
hamburgers worth of cows.
I call to the stand Moolisa!
Objection!
That cow's faking
his injuries!
And I can prove it.
Think fast.
[ Crowd Murmuring ]
Overruled.
Moolisa,
is the man who killed you
in the courtroom today?
[ Insects Buzzing ]
[ Bob ]
It's me.
I just make hamburgers.
I never wanted to be
a cow killer.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
[ Gasps ]
[ Snoring ]
Whoa. Heavy sleeper.
Wha--What happened?
What's the matter?
What's the matter? [ Snorts ]
Go back to bed.
[ Groans ]
I'm sorry.
Go back to bed.
[ Thunder Cracks ]
[ Cow Moos ]
[ Sighs ]
Hey! Randy!
Your cow's gonna freeze
to death out here.
Randy!
[ Bob ]
Shh. Easy. Easy.
Back up. Back up. Back up.
Oh, my God!
[ Chuckles ]
I know.
It's a cow.
You know what?
You won't even know it's here.
Uh, that was
like that already.
Definitely clean that.
Oop. Step back.
This is the best dream
I've ever had!
Everybody
pee on the floor!
[ Voice Raised ]
Who's with me?
Okay. Eat while it's hot.
Well, well, well.
Looks who's too good
for cereal now.
He's trying
to impress the cow.
Don't be ridiculous.
Someone knows
how to treat
a lady-slash-male steer.
Bob, I am
not comfortable
with this situation.
Lin, what was I supposed to do?
I had that crazy dream.
It was raining.
Well, I had a crazy dream
that there wouldn't be
a cow's a-s-s in my face...
when I'm eating
my breakfast.
I know what that spells.
Ass.
Mom.
[ Chuckles ] Ass.
Stop it.
Say good-bye, everybody.
It's going out on the street
where it belongs.
Of course, okay? Of course.
Right after breakfast.
Cows can't go down stairs.
What?
What's that?
Cows can't go down stairs.
- That's, like, a thing.
- I've heard that.
It's like a fun fact.
Bobby!
Hmm.
Cows can't go down stairs?
That better not be true.
[ Bob Grunting ]
Huh. What do you know?
We know you'll push
on a cow's butt
for half an hour...
without asking for help.
Gotta have that butt
all to yourself.
[ Yelling ]
Hey, Bob,
what's the deal, man?
What did you do
to Moolisa?
It's up here!
Come get it out!
Linda. Uh, it's not
up here, Randy.
My wife's crazy.
Shh. If he knows
I brought the cow in,
he'll think he won.
So what if he won?
Get the cow out
of the house now.
Stop.
You get it out
of the house.
Linda, please.
Come get--
Oh. Uh, this cow.
- This cow, yeah, is here.
- Aha!
Dad, I ran that bubble bath
for you and Moolisa
like you wanted.
Bubbles.
I'm not taking a bath
with Moolisa, Randy.
Two days left.
Two days to decide to send
that cow to slaughter...
or admit
you're a hypocrite
and a murderer.
Wow. What a movie.
- Bob, what a movie.
- It's not my movie, Teddy.
What, are they just
followin' you around
with a camera?
You're in it.
You're the star,
but it's not your movie.
Good luck, guys.
- Will you sign a release?
- Sure. Do you want
my Jock Hancock?
Yeah.
Anywhere?
No. On-On the line here.
Better get used
to this, huh?
Gonna be
in the movies. I--
Just on the line
where it says "signature."
Just on the line, right?
Just sign anywhere?
Yeah.
No. No.
Where it says signature.
Okay. What's your name?
Do you want it to you?
- No, I--
- [ Bob ]
Teddy, what are you doing?
I'm signing, uh,
an autograph, Bob.
[ Sighs ]
One big happy family.
Isn't this nice,
all of us here together?
No.
Are you gonna give me
a poop tonight?
Talk to me.
Hmm? Bob, hmm?
Well, it's nice.
They like each other.
It's good for Tina.
Come on.
Just relax and--
[ Blows Raspberry ]
It's all about
the communication.
[ Blows Raspberry ]
[ Squishing ]
Uh-oh.
Hi, Moolisa.
[ Gasps ]
Frowny face?
All I've been
is super nice to you,
and this is the thanks I get?
I loved you.
I loved you like a horse,
which is my favorite animal.
You know what?
Let's just stop...
before we both
say something we'll regret,
like that horses
are better than cows.
I regret that.
But it's true.
Where's the cow?
I believe you mean,
"Where's the steer?"
Yeah, don't forget
about that penis.
Yeah.
Moolisa?
Moolisa.
Ha!
Cows can go down stairs.
All you need
is four wool socks,
a mattress and the will
to make it happen.
You didn't.
Your girlfriend
is tied up outside.
Uh-oh.
[ Yelling ]
No!
What's wrong with Dad?
I think
he hates leashes.
It's not my fault, Randy.
She was stolen.
It's no one's fault.
Except for Linda's.
I did what I had to do
to protect my family
and my carpet.
Yeah, whatever.
So, who do we know
that would steal a cow
in a blonde wig?
Maybe some perverts.
[ Chuckles ]
We had a fight last night,
me and Moolisa.
I just wish I had a chance
to make things right again.
You wouldn't if you
heard some of the things
she was pooping about you.
Hey, guys,
take a look at this.
[ Talking Backwards ]
...on the cheap.
[ Tape Rewinds ]
You fellas just
leave her tied up here
at night all alone?
Oh, yeah, yeah.
She doesn't mind.
We could just
back a trailer
right up here, honey, huh?
We sure could--
get ourselves a cow.
Yeah. Get ourselves a cow.
Yeah, get ourselves a cow.
[ Both Laughing ]
[ Laughing Continues ]
[ Ticking ]
What a dump.
Yikes.
Hey, there she is.
Oh, dear God.
[ Gasps ]
Oh, the cow
that jumped over the moon.
See, that's nice.
Come on. Let's go get her.
We should come back
after dark.
Why?
It's more dramatic.
That is stupid.
No, no, no, no.
I can see it now,
the big rescue.
We'll shoot the whole thing
in infrared.
Ah, Randy, com--
In infrared?
This is nuts.
The kids should be
in bed, Bob.
It's infrared, Lin.
Show her.
- Oh!
- Yeah.
Coo! Coo!
Why are you doing that?
I'm signaling.
Everybody, serpentine.
[ Gene ]
Yes. We're a unit.
Dad, you should know.
If anything happens,
I am in full attack mode
right now.
Me too.
I'm hungry for blood.
And also candy.
Uh, thanks, kids.
[ Grunts ] Damn it.
I missed the signal
to stand up.
Sorry, everybody.
You let down
the unit.
I said I'm sorry.
Bob, we're here.
What do we do now?
We, uh--
uh, open the gate.
That was easy.
What do you think
you're doing?
[ Louise ]
Gene, attack!
[ Both Yelling, Munching ]
Your children
are biting my legs.
[ Bob ]
Randy, get Moolisa.
Let's move.
[ Munching Continues ]
High-five, Bob.
We did it.
High-five, Randy.
Nice job.
I mean, we couldn't have done it
without the kids
biting that woman.
[ Timer Beeping ]
She tasted like
sawdust and goats.
Three, two, one.
[ Buzzer Sounds ]
Beep.
[ Gene ]
Uh-oh.
Bob, the cow-ntdown's over.
It's time to decide
Moolisa's fate.
Seriously? Right now?
Uh, we just rescued her.
She's due at
the slaughterhouse, Bob.
What's it gonna be?
[ Louise ]
Murderer!
Louise, shush.
[ Gasps ]
Randy, can you stop making
your stupid movie for one minute
and just be a human being?
I don't know, Bob.
Can you stop making your
stupid burgers for one minute...
and be a human being?
Now you're gonna guilt-trip me.
That's what the whole
movie is about.
I thought we were friends now,
Randy, 'cause we saved
the cow together.
Maybe activists-slash-
documentarians can't
have friends...
no matter how
many cows they save.
Well, that's just sad, Randy.
[ Tires Screeching ]
I know!
[ Screeching Continues ]
Oh, my God.
That was close.
I don't know
what I would do
if anything happened to Moo--
- [ Gasps ]
- I didn't hit her.
I didn't hit her.
I-I stopped.
She's probably fine.
She's dead.
She must have had
a cow heart attack.
No.
You know what?
Let me get something
out of my van real quick.
Be right back.
[ Door Closes ]
[ Engine Starts ]
[ Tires Squeal ]
Moolisa!
Oh, my God. No.
Don't you die on me.
Don't you die.
Say something.
Louise, look.
It's a heart--
a heart-shaped poop.
What the hell?
I didn't do that.
I'm keeping it.
Bob, you all right?
You look a little pale.
[ Groans ]
[ Body Thuds ]
Are we dead?
I'm dead, Bob.
You just fainted.
I fainted? Wow.
That's embarrassing.
- Okay.
- I'm-I'm not a fainter.
- Yeah, I'm-- I'm dead though.
- Right. Yeah.
But listen. There's something
I want you to do for me.
Make burgers out of me.
- What? No. No way.
- Yes way, Bob.
Look, ever since I met you,
making burgers makes me feel
like a horrible person.
Bob, I'm a castrated steer.
Yeah, I'm a married man.
[ Both Snickering,
Chuckling ]
I'm kid--
Same thing, right?
Yeah. Think about it though.
I'm a cow, you know?
We're not wild stallions
or humpback whales.
But we wanna feel special too.
I do anyway.
You turn me
into something amazing.
Wait. Isn't this
my subconscious telling me
what I wanna hear?
Hey. No. You know what?
Yes, it is actually.
Well, it's working.
Keep talking.
Kiss me.
No. I can't do that.
You can, and you want to.
[ Sighs ]
Okay. One quick one
because I owe you.
Uh, maybe not.
Maybe I-- we shouldn't.
Oh, we should, absolutely.
Oh, my God.
What am I doing?
What are you doing?
I'm about
to kiss a cow.
Yeah.
Mmm.
- Bobby, are you okay?
- Mmm. Mmm. Mmm.
What's Dad doing
with his mouth?
Looks like he's kissing.
Mmm. Mmm. Mmm, mmm.
Well, this is awkward.
Somebody put
a blanket over it.
Tastes so good.
[ Linda ] Okay, all right,
kids inside now!
[ Tina ] Ohh.
Before Moolisa, I used
to say it's just beef.
- I couldn't have been
more wrong.
- [ Dog Barks Twice ]
Cows are living creatures
with beautiful hair...
and soft brown eyes,
soft mouths.
Whoo!
And also they are beef.
They're the full package.
Does that make me
a hypocrite to say that?
[ Randy ]
Yes.
No, it doesn't, Randy.
Or if it does,
I can live with that.
I present our
hundred-thousandth burger.
100,000th burger!
All right!
Right. Undo the banner.
Bob's Burger!
100,000! All right!
Hooray!
Do the banner.
Here's the banner.
Here comes the banner.
I humbly call this
the Rest in Peas burger.
[ Linda Chuckling ]
Ha.
Because it, uh, comes
with snap peas and carrots.
Thank you.
All right, funeral people,
it's time to party!
♪ [ House ]
♪ [ Continues ]
♪ Gene machine
♪ In the house
♪ Get ready
♪ To get it on
♪ [ Continues ]
[ Dog Barks ]