本视频仅供英语学习交流，严禁用于商业途径
更多资源敬请关注公众号：晨雨资料库
[ Ukulele Strumming ]
Bob's Burgers!
Fresh ground meat!
Great atmosphere!
[ Horn Blows ]
Gene, bring it in.
Get out of that burger suit.
We're going.
Baseball waits for no one.
[ Sniffs ]
It smells like urine.
Did you pee in that?
I had to go.
I told you not to pee in it
after I cleaned up from--
I'm the only one who wears it.
What's the difference?
Oh, my God.
What, you don't wanna
buy burgers from a guy
who smells like pee?
No one can place
where it's coming from.
I can't believe
you'll close the restaurant
to go to a baseball game.
Louise, this isn't just a game.
We bought an ad
at the ballpark.
That's worth closing for, right?
Oh, can't wait to see it.
It's gonna be so exciting.
We're famous.
It looks like
a hot dog wrapper
stuck in the net.
Like, a really
tiny hot dog.
I did think it was gonna
be a little bigger.
I think more people
would see your ad
if it was a urinal cake.
Are you kidding?
I wish I could afford
a urinal cake ad.
All this talk about cake
is making me hungry.
I'm gonna flag down
the ice cream sandwich guy. Hey!
Play ball!
Welcome to opening day
of minor league baseball.
Let's hear it for your
Wonder Wharf Wonderdogs!
[ Applause, Cheers ]
Please give a big
Wonderdog welcome to Phenom,
the Korean bunt specialist!
I never realized baseball
had so much butt touching.
That's how they
communicate, Tina.
It's like braille,
but with butts.
[ Gene ]
Read my butt!
[ Groans ]
I'm bored.
Boredom.
Boring sports.
Hey, it's
the seventh-inning stretch.
Time for the mascot race.
Well, hello!
Please welcome the owner
of the Wonderdogs,
Mr. Calvin Fischoeder!
Fish!
It's that time.
Now cheer for your
favorite mascot.
Mr. Fischoeder
owns the team?
He owns the ballpark,
the team, Wonder Wharf.
I'm gonna marry
that man.
No, you're not.
I wanna be rich!
Don't be frightened.
I have a gun.
So get set.
- [ Gunshot ]
- [ Fans Cheer ]
Where has this sport been
all my life?
You know, I wear
the burger costume
all the time.
Maybe I could race
in one of these races, Dad.
I bet it's impossible
to get in, Gene. I'm sure
you gotta know someone.
You do.
It's Mr. Fischoeder,
our landlord.
Well, I can't ask
a favor of a guy
I've never paid rent on time to.
You're his son, Gene.
He'll ask him.
Yay.
No, I won't.
Now taking
the mound to pitch,
former major league sensation,
Torpedo Jones.
That can't be the same Torpe--
Kids, that's the
Torpedo Jones.
I can't believe
he's still playing.
God, he must be... my age.
I speak for everyone here
when I say I don't know
what a Torpedo Jones is.
Let me tell you, nobody--
We don't care.
Gene, let me finish. Nobody--
That's what I was
trying to prevent.
Nobody pitched like Torpedo.
I was there for his
greatest moment-- "The Pitch."
It was 15 years ago,
but I remember it
like it was 10.
His pitch was
the split-finger skadootch.
- [ Cheers ]
- Torpedo clinched the pennant
for us with that pitch.
If he's so good,
why have we never
heard of this guy?
Because he didn't
last long in the bigs.
The skadootch is just
one of those pitches.
When it was on,
it was really on.
But when it wasn't,
it's like hitting candy
out of a baby's hand
with a bat.
Wait. You mean it's hard
because babies hands
are so small?
No, it's easy because--
How could you hit a baby?
Nobody would hit
a baby's hand
with a bat in real life.
I don't understand.
Was he fired
from the bigs...
'cause he hit a baby
with a bat?
I'm not interested
in talking to you.
Sorry, Gene. I don't
see Fischoeder anywhere.
Let's get going.
That's all right.
I only wanted to do it
really, really bad.
Oh, there's Torpedo!
Dad, ask Torpedo
about the mascot races.
Maybe he can
get Gene in.
Yeah!
Kids, come on.
I can't bother Torpedo.
He's, like, my role model.
Oh, that's creepy.
Your role model
is the same age as you?
I would never have
another nine-year-old
as my role model.
Hey, Torpedo!
Louise--
My dad is a huge scout
for the Baseball League
of America.
Kidding. But he has
a favor to ask you.
[ Chuckles ]
Hi. I'm a huge fan.
I was there
for "The Pitch."
So, what can I do for ya?
Picture? Autograph?
Three bucks each,
both for five.
Uh, yeah,
both would be great.
Dad!
Oh. And, uh, my kid wants
to run in the mascot race.
You don't think--
Hey, Russell!
Some kid here wants to run
in a mascot race.
For you, Torpedo,
I'll make it happen.
I've gotta free up
one of these outfits.
No, you don't.
I got my own.
It's a burger.
Easy enough.
Thanks a lot, Torpedo.
- Good luck out there, sport.
- Linda, did you hear that?
Torpedo Jones
called me "sport."
He didn't call you "sport."
He called Gene "sport."
No, he was looking right at me.
Yeah. He called me "sport"
and he tousled my hair.
It was great, Gene.
You were great.
I'm a great
tousle receiver.
Wow. Wearing the burger suit
in the mascot race, Gene.
That's advertising, huh?
Don't touch me!
It was so nice of Torpedo
to give us these seats
so we can watch Gene's race.
You can really make out
the players' tattoos
from here.
Makes you wonder
about the tattoos
we can't see.
[ Quietly ]
On their butts.
How you doing, Gene?
You feeling fast?
No.
I feel queasy.
Got some butterflies, ace?
Torpedo.
Want my advice, kid?
It's a mascot race.
All you gotta do
is stay on your feet.
Let the other guys
trip over themselves.
It's time
for the mascot race!
Whoo-ee!
Goody.
Remember,
you're an ambassador
for our restaurant.
So just try and run well,
'cause you don't run well.
Good luck
out there, sport.
Oh.
Yeah, I thought earlier
you called me "sport," so--
Nah, that was a nickname
for the kid there, Flash.
I'll take Flash.
Kids, call me Flash from now on.
Let's split the diff
and call you Kiki.
Kiki. I like it.
Oh, Torpedo, here's
a little thank-you for
getting Gene in the race.
I make burgers
for a living,
so it's not weird
for me to give you this.
I don't think
it's weird at all, Bob.
Like a good burger.
Mmm.
That's a good burger.
Finish this guy
back on the mound.
Ha! Torpedo Jones just said
I make a good burger.
I want that on my tombstone.
Seriously, okay?
No, I already
got your tombstone
picked out for you.
What? What is it?
It says, "Order up."
[ Chuckles ]
That's good.
Let's go with that one.
Joining your
Wonder Wharf mascots today
is a special guest food--
a burger-- a boy
who is also a burger.
And I have my gun.
Ready! Set!
[ Gunshot ]
Go get 'em, Gene!
I reinforced the crotch
so he wouldn't tear it.
Win, Gene!
Avenge Dad's death!
[ Crowd ] Ohh!
[ Announcer ]
Down goes Sammy Sea Lion!
- [ Imitating Explosions ]
- [ Groans ]
Ooh! It's a two-mascot race.
Burger and Captain Pel I. Can.
They're they go,
like two, fast, fiery-- Bew!
[ Grunts ]
The burger is your winner.
[ Imitates Trumpet Fanfare ]
All right!
Yeah, yeah, yeah!
Well, congratulations,
young burger.
Ladies and gentlemen,
you can purchase
delicious burgers...
that look somewhat like him
right here at the park.
And at my family's restaurant.
And, uh, what's the name
of that restaurant?
Ah-- It's-- It's--
God, I'm there every day.
Bob's Burgers!
It's-- Oh, my God.
Gene! No!
Never mind. Never mind.
That's okay.
Bob's Burgers! Oh, my God!
You can get everything
you expect from a burger...
at whatever the name
of his restaurant is.
Bob's Burgers!
Oh, oh, I just remembered.
I just remembered.
It's too late.
But you can get them
here at the park today.
No! Say it!
I won something!
I won! I won! I won something!
Yeah, and you
didn't fall down
like everyone else.
- Tell that
to your grandkids.
- I will.
Gene, are you kidding me?
The name of the restaurant
is Bob's Burgers!
Well, I call you Dad.
I think of it as Dad's Burgers.
You live above it!
You work in it every day!
Bob, calm down.
Calm down. Calm down.
I'm sorry, Dad.
Fine. He did great.
You did great, Gene.
A gold medal!
Oh, we should
get that bronzed.
Strike three!
You're out!
Torpedo's split-finger skadootch
has suddenly started clicking.
I love that burger
of yours, Bob.
Hey, after the game,
let's all go to Bob's Burgers.
[ Fans Cheer ]
Whoo-hoo!
Now that's
advertising, huh?
[ Cash Register Rings ]
[ Crowd Chattering ]
Ooh, Angel!
Do they call you that
'cause you're such
a good boy?
I did many bad things
to escape Cuba--
[ Gunfire ]
[ Man Groans ]
things that haunt me
in the dark of the night.
Aw!
How about another beer?
Man, you kids got
a great dad, you know that?
One wife, one family.
That's the way to do it.
In the majors, most guys
got a whole bunch of families
spread out over the 50 states.
When spring training starts,
you get your Florida wife.
When it's regular season,
it's open season, if you
know what I'm talking about.
You kiss your home-field wife
and kids good-bye.
You tell 'em
you'll miss 'em,
and you do.
But you still take
some of their toys and
re-gift 'em for your away kids.
I bet you're a great dad.
And three great husbands.
Mr. Torpedo,
I couldn't help but notice...
that the ball boy was
looking a little lethargic.
Yeah, he's got lupus
or rickets or something.
I don't know why
we keep giving that job
to these sick kids.
I was wondering if I
could offer my services.
I'm very healthy.
[ Grunting ]
Okay, okay, okay.
Whoa, whoa. Hey.
You got the job.
Just stop doing that.
Here's your
first ball-girl duty.
Bring me one
of your dad's burgers
before every game.
Okay.
Here's the chewing tobacco
you wanted.
[ Grunts ]
And your comic books.
[ Spanish ]
[ Scattered Cheers ]
Phenom, is it possible...
to be in love
with 25 people at once?
You're my favorite.
Don't tell Angel.
He's fiery.
- Strike three!
- [ Cheering ]
Sound the alarm
because Torpedo is on fire.
[ Imitates Fire Alarm ]
Fire! Fire! Fire!
Not a good idea, Burt.
It's a crowded stadium.
That Torpedo is amazing.
Has he always been this good?
No, he hasn't been good
in a long time.
He says my burgers
have helped him pitch better.
How does a burger
help someone pitch better?
Here you go, Bob--
a little souvenir.
[ Chuckles ]
Thanks, buddy.
Oh, slippery.
It's greasy, huh?
[ Sniffs ]
What does this smell like?
Hey, stop sniffing
Torpedo's balls.
[ Laughs ]
Get it?
It's like you're
in love with him.
Wait.
That's our burger.
Oh, crap.
Torpedo's putting
my grease on the ball.
That's how his skadootch
is skadootching so much.
Your hero's using
your burger grease to win.
That's great.
No, Lin.
Torpedo is using
my burger grease to cheat.
Oh.
♪ [ Organ ]
[ Crowd Clapping Rhythmically ]
So you helped
Torpedo cheat.
If that means
the Wonderdogs keep coming
to the restaurant...
and bringing all sorts
of business with them,
I say big whoop.
Let the old man
throw a greasy skadootch.
[ Sighs ]
I don't even know
what to think about this.
I-I gotta go take a leak.
Oh, get me an ice cream
in a mini helmet!
[ Urinating ]
[ Zipper Unzips ]
Bob, you look glum.
[ Urinating ]
Oh, I, uh--
You don't hold your--
when you pee.
Why? It's not going anywhere.
Okay.
Um, well,
what if you found out...
that someone you knew
was doing something
sort of bad...
and you were helping them
do that sort of bad thing--
Is it me?
Is it abortions?
Wait. What?
Uh, what were you saying?
Torpedo Jones
is greasing the ball,
and he's using
my grease to do it.
Mm-mmm. Oh.
Come walk with me.
Come behind the scenes.
Torpedo's dazzling pitching
is putting more butts
in seats...
than this stadium
can handle.
Is the roller coaster
gonna be okay without
those huge planks of wood?
Sure, sure.
[ People Screaming Excitedly ]
These people aren't paying
for extra wood, Bob.
[ Roller Coaster Chugging ]
No one wants to ride
Extra Wood Mountain.
Whoa! Watch out!
Extra nuts and bolts.
[ Nuts, Bolts Clanking ]
Ow!
People come
to baseball games...
for the same reason
they come to
the amusement park--
to be entertained!
Does it really matter
if the games are rigged? No!
The games are rigged?
Yes!
Oh. My wonderdog
is hanging out.
Yes. Yes, it is.
I got so caught up
in our conversation,
I forgot to zip.
Yeah, I didn't want
to say anything.
Why not?
I, uh--
Compliments are welcome.
Where was I?
You were saying
the games are rigged.
Yes. The games
are all rigged.
I'm not letting my kids
play these games anymore.
[ Fischoeder ]
But look
at these smiling faces.
Just like those
smiling faces--
smiling at every skadootch
the Torpedo throws.
They don't wanna know, Bob.
They don't wanna look
behind the curtain.
I don't know. It just seems
like bad karma or something.
Karma?
There's no such thing
as karma.
[ Laughs ]
Not in this town.
[ Roller Coaster Chugging ]
[ Grunts ]
Oh, just kick 'em.
- Kick 'em
right into the ocean.
- Okay.
That's it.
Wait. Why does Tornado
want our old grease
in a jar?
It's Torpedo, Gene.
Oh.
Uh, it helps him
pitch better.
And don't forget.
It's a secret.
Why? Is it
against the rules?
Technically, yes.
So then
it's cheating.
No. What it is
is helping people
enjoy baseball more.
It's entertainment.
I'm confused.
Are you and Mom
getting divorced?
What?
Oh, my God.
You are.
I call Mom!
I call Dad!
You guys took both of them.
Enough.
Go fill the condiments.
I call ketchup!
I call mustard!
Aw.
You can do horseradish.
There's not-- Okay.
Thanks, Bobby.
Hey, who wants a burger?
On the Torpedo.
Hooray!
Gene, you're
defending your title.
Are you nervous?
Why don't you ask
my diarrhea?
You should be nervous.
You're a chubby kid
in a mascot suit.
That's what I'm saying.
I should cheat.
Dad says it's okay
when it's for entertainment.
That's right. Let's cheat.
- You see that pelican?
- [ Gene ]
Yeah.
You're running, right?
You have a switchblade
taped to your shoe.
- He does?
- He will.
And on your other shoe,
you'll have a lemon.
Stab, stab, stab!
Sting, sting, sting!
"What are you doing?"
"I'm squeezing lemon
into your wound."
Sweet baby blade foot.
Or... I can give him
a nudge and tip him over.
[ Groans ]
Really?
Yeah. He's top-heavy.
I'll just give him
a little tippity-tap.
Well, I'm still gluing
a knife to my foot.
[ Gunshot ]
Yay, Gene! Go, Gene!
That-a-way, Son.
- [ Panting ]
- [ Fans Cheering ]
Tippity-tap.
[ Grunts ]
[ Phil ]
Ooh! it's
a three-mascot pile-up.
Go, Gene! All right! Go!
[ Burt ]
The Boy Burger wins again!
How about that?
Hey, how about this, Phil?
[ Imitates Whooping Siren ]
I don't know, Burt.
I'm not so sure about that.
Yay!
I won! I won again!
My brother won.
Guys, take off
your shirts.
[ Grunting ]
- Good arm pumping, baby.
- That's how I disguised
the push.
- What push?
- He pushed the Cotton Candy
mascot so he'd fall over.
- Hooray for cheating.
- Gene, how could you?
You know that's wrong.
Uh-uh-uh.
Not when it's entertainment.
You said it yourself.
You told them
cheating is okay?
No, I didn't, Linda.
Yes, he did.
Oh, Bobby.
Oh, crap.
Go get me
a soft serve.
And make it a swirl!
Look, Gene,
when I said it's okay to cheat,
I meant for Torpedo,
not for you to cheat
in your mascot race.
You should
really give back
one of those medals.
Ooh, but I wanna get a picture
of you wearing them
before you do.
I'm not giving back
my medal!
Those suckers got
their money's worth, Pops.
I'm good for business, Dad.
From now on,
there'll be no more cheating.
- Does that mean I shouldn't
give Torpedo this grease?
- That's right, Tina.
Yes. No more cheating
for anyone
in this house.
From now on, I won't wear
my tummy-tuck jeans.
And good-bye, Brazilian.
Hello, rain forest.
Sorry, Dad.
But if I win tomorrow,
I'll be the first mascot ever
to win three races in a row.
- I'm a top.
- You mean you're on top.
No. I'm a top.
[ Grunts ]
[ Fans Cheering ]
Shew. I was
starting to think...
maybe you were
gonna leave me
high and dry here.
Well, what's in this jar
is worth the wait.
What the--
"You don't need to cheat.
You can win without me.
If you try your hardest,
you've already won.
Love, Bob's grease."
That's right, Torpedo.
You can win without my grease.
It just took me
believing in you.
Now, listen.
Gene's about to race,
and since you're his role model,
I'm hoping you'll tell Gene
he can win without cheating,
just like you.
- Who the hell's Gene?
- That's... my son.
You're his role model,
and you're my role model too.
Wh-- I can't be
your role model.
We're the same age.
What's this mean?
You cutting me off, Bob-O?
Torpedo, I'm cutting you free.
Come here.
Wait. What are you gonna do?
I'm gonna hug you.
Slow down there, tiger.
Guess I'll have to make
this grease last
the whole season.
I should have never
given you my grease.
I created a monster.
You think you
started my greasing?
I've always cheated, Bobby.
Not "The Pitch."
Oh, definitely "The Pitch."
That game, I had a pat
of butter in my right nostril,
sex jelly in my armpit.
Hell, I was on prescription
drugs to stimulate
production of earwax.
And "The Pitch"?
That was courtesy...
of some
black-market whale blubber
I bought off some Eskimos.
Cute note though, Bob.
Bit of advice:
If you want a role model,
pick an old guy.
By the time you grow up,
they're dead.
[ Sighs ]
Didn't go great. Gene!
I'm sure it was fine.
Torpedo seems like
a reasonable guy.
Torpedo Jones wants you
out of his seats this second.
What a schmuck.
Gene!
[ Phil ] It's
the seventh-inning stretch.
Mascots are lining up.
All right,
maybe I have an idea.
Hi, fellas. I'd love to say
a few words to my son,
the burger, over the P.A.
Excuse me.
Uh, okay.
[ Chuckles ]
Highly unusual.
Doesn't matter.
None of this matters.
Gene. Up here.
Jesus?
No, Gene, it's your father.
I'm up here.
You're dead?
[ Chuckles ]
Yes.
[ Gasps ]
No, I'm-I'm--
[ Chuckles ] I'm kidding.
I'm up here in the booth.
Right here. See me?
[ Sniffs ]
Boy, this microphone
smells like beer.
Well, let's just say A.A.
was "A" waste of time.
Winning isn't everything, Gene.
Yes, we're all here
to be entertained.
But if you, um,
cut corners now,
the next thing you know
you'll be hiding lard
in your nose...
or taking wood
out of roller coasters.
Hey, hey, all right,
that's enough of that.
Let's start the race.
I'm trying to talk to my son.
Gene, run clean.
On your mark!
- Gene, what are
you gonna do?
- I don't know.
You're gonna cheat.
That's what you're gonna do.
You're gonna win
by cheating!
♪ [ Organ: "Call to the Post" ]
[ Gunshot ]
[ Panting ]
Who wants to see the burger
win three in a row?
[ Cheering ]
Gene, listen to me.
You know what to do.
Bob, triple crown for burger.
- Good for your business.
- See?
No, Gene. Don't worry
about the advertising.
What are you doing?
It's a starter's pistol.
- It's a real gun. Get down.
- [ Gunshot ]
- What?
Stop shooting.
This is crazy.
[ Gunshots Stop ]
Oh, good. He stopped.
He's just out of bullets.
And down goes Cotton Candy.
It's a two-mascot race.
Gene, do the right thing.
Yeah! You can win
on your own, Gene! Probably.
[ Pants ]
[ In Slow-motion ]
Hey.
All right. Fine.
[ Groans ]
Whoa, whoa!
Don't push him!
He was gonna push you!
[ Burt ]
Congratulations
to Captain Pel I. Can.
Oh, Gene, sorry, buddy.
Looks like karma
caught up to you.
Bob, I told you
there's no such thing as karma.
- Uh, yes, there is.
- No, I'm afraid there isn't.
I'm afraid there is.
Is not.
[ Fans Gasping, Chattering ]
[ Wheels Screech ]
[ Metal Clanging, Stops ]
Oh, crap.
See, Gene,
this is what happens
when you cheat.
That was incredible.
Cheating is amazing!
[ Groans ]
Bob?
Oh. Uh, hi.
Sorry about
your roller coaster.
Ah, roller coasters
come and go,
but Bobs are
once in a lifetime.
I admire you.
You do?
You remind me of my father.
He was honest,
and he worked hard.
You an immigrant, Bob?
Um, no.
Just swarthy?
I guess.
What's swarthy?
Um, dark and hairy.
That's you.
And me in the future.
Well, unlike you,
my father made
a fortune.
But in many other ways,
you guys are the same--
two decent,
swarthy peas in a pod.
One rich and one...
just scraping by.
Thanks.
Well, we're off
to get a massage.
Come on, Wonderdog.
Down, boy.
He's gone, Dad.
My future husband's gone.
You drove him away!
Tina, what you
got there?
The team signed a ball
so I'd have something
to remember them by.
And I took
this jockstrap.
Okay, sweetie.
[ Chuckles ]
Let's throw that in the wash.
No. Mm-mmm.
Come on. Give it to me.
Do you know
how many venereal diseases
those baseball players have?
I don't care.
Whose was it?
Smells like Angel.
Angel.
[ Tina ]
But don't tell Phenom.
♪ [ Organ ]
[ Fischoeder ]
Ladies and gentlemen,
you can purchase
delicious burgers
that look somewhat like him...
right here at the park.
[ Gene ]
And at my family's restaurant.
[ Fischoeder ]
And, uh, what's the name
of that restaurant?
[ Gene ]
Ah-- It's-- It's--
God, I'm there every day.
[ Bob ]
Bob's Burgers!
[ Gene ]
It's-- Oh, my God.
[ Bob ] Bob's Burgers!
Gene! No!
[ Fischoeder ]
Never mind. That's okay.
[ Bob ] Bob's Burgers!
[ Fischoeder ]
You can get everything
you expect from a burger...
at whatever
the name
of his restaurant is.
[ Bob ]
Bob's Burgers!
[ Gene ]
I just remembered.
[ Fischoeder ]
It's too late.
[ Bob ] No! Say it!