本视频仅供英语学习交流，严禁用于商业途径
更多资源敬请关注公众号：晨雨资料库
[ Ukulele strumming ]
It looks like
a pickle slice,
but furry.
I think it's a message...
from someone or something,
trying to warn us
about someone or something.
[ Gene ]
It's a booger.
Kids,
off the seats.
Oh, sorry, sir.
That was my butt.
Hmm!
What are you looking at?
Smart money's
on boogers.
It's not a booger.
Let the man
think for himself!
I don't think
it's a booger.
Who asked you?
It's getting bigger.
It knows
what we're
thinking.
[ Bob ]
Huh. It is
definitely growing.
I just hope it's not
that green mold.
It's called green mold.
You see it in a lot
of beach towns...
and filthy, disgusting,
poorly managed
restaurants.
Hey!
They had to send you, Hugo?
No one else does this?
I just got mold-certified.
In a month, I'll be cleared
for vermin too.
Oh, congratulations.
Okay, Gene.
If you eat this mold,
I'll give you five--
[ Munching ]
Whoa.
Mmm!
Gorgonzola.
So what do I gotta do?
Use bleach on it
or something?
[ Laughs ]
Use bleach on it? "Oh,
I'll just put bleach on it."
No, of course not, Bob.
- I hate you.
- This is big.
You have to close.
The whole building will have to
be tented for 48 hours.
Great. There goes
our weekend revenue.
Ooh, two days off.
Bobby, we could use it.
I guess it has been a while
since we've had a break.
Yeah. Ten years.
What? That's--
Can't be right.
Ten years!
You're really
living the dream,
Linda.
Aren't you done, Hugo?
Sure, Bob.
I'm done.
[ Shouting ]
Mold! Dangerous killer mold!
Floating death spores!
Everyone move!
Gene, how are you feeling?
Kind of nauseous,
a little light-headed.
Pretty good.
Glad I ate it.
You say that
about everything.
Yeah.
Green mold, huh?
You ever dealt
with this stuff, Mort?
Oh, sure.
We get all kinds
of moldy bodies
at the home.
Not on the bodies.
I mean on the walls or--
And you should see
the shut-ins.
Stop.
One guy's back
looked like a putting green.
Oh, dear Lord.
Hey, you got to
get out of the apartment
while the mold guys work, right?
Yeah. We're gonna go
to a motel.
And we're going to tear into
that minibar!
We're gonna go on a bender.
No, we're not.
Yes, we are.
I'm gonna drink
some Baileys
and unwind.
Hey, guys. Stay with me.
No, I mean,
I appreciate the offer,
but I--
Listen to me.
I live alone...
in an enormous apartment...
that happens to be
above a funeral home.
Hmm.
So come on.
Stay with me.
Aw.
- Thanks, Mort.
- Yeah, yeah!
Linda, seriously,
you want to stay
in a funeral home?
Yes, yes, yes!
Why not? It'll be fun.
Is it spooky?
You mean, do I have
a medicine cabinet
full of corpse moisturizers?
Ooh!
Yes. Do they make
my skin soft as a baby?
You decide.
[ Gasps ]
It's not greasy either.
Tina, touch.
[ Groans ]
Come on!
Go get your toothbrushes.
Yeah, yeah!
Yes, yes, yes,
yes, yes!
[ All ]
♪ Weekend at Mort's
♪ We're gonna have
a weekend at Mort's ♪
[ Linda ]
Uh, uh, uh!
♪ Weekend at Mort's
[ Doorbell Rings ]
♪ We're gonna have
a weekend at Mort's ♪
Follow me to your rooms.
Urn.
Another urn.
That's an award I won
for best urn.
Okay, kids.
Don't climb on anything.
Don't touch anything.
If you do touch something,
don't touch me afterwards...
and don't play
with dead bodies.
Do you think
he's gonna have skulls?
What do you think
he eats soup out of?
Do you think he's gonna
have a drawer full of gum that
he takes out of corpse pockets?
'Cause if he does,
I want some.
Shh!
Here we go.
[ Door Creaks ]
[ All Gasp ]
[ Linda ]
Hey, I'm not
horrified at all. Aw.
[ Bob ]
Wow, I didn't know
you were rich.
Kids, off the furniture.
Well, I get a lot
of stuff cheap.
Everything in here
had someone die on it.
Kids,
off the furniture!
Your room's
right down the hall.
All right, kids. Let's go.
No, leave the kids.
This weekend, I'm Uncle Mort.
You seriously want to
watch my kids?
[ Clicking ]
♪ [ Fragments ]
[ Mort ]
Uhh.
[ Nervous Chuckle ]
Yes! The whole weekend.
This should be a vacation
for you two.
Oh, we can make it
the honeymoon
we never had.
Sure. You know,
I got the bed you're sleeping in
because a man died in it...
making love, huh?
Good God.
Mm-hmm.
It's a haunted
honeymoon.
[ Ghostly Moaning ]
[ Kids Moaning And Groaning ]
Ah!
[ Grunts ]
[ Linda ]
Two whole days off
from the restaurant. Oh!
I know.
What are we gonna do
with ourselves?
I know what I'm gonna do.
First, I'm gonna take these off.
Oh!
These bad boys.
Bobby.
Hmm?
You gonna slip into
something more comfortable?
And I'm gonna get
these on.
[ Gasps ]
Oh, are those your, uh--
My lazy pants?
Yes.
Well, I guess
they come off easy.
And, uh, now
I will get this guy out.
Ah, uh-huh, uh-huh.
And let
the vacation begin.
What the hell
is that?
- It's my model.
- Since when do you do models?
It's a hobby of mine, Lin.
From back when I could
still have hobbies.
I just relax, turn my brain off
and enjoy the thrill
of the build.
The bus from Speed?
Yeah, the bus from Speed.
[ Chorus ]
♪ Bus from Speed
I didn't know you liked
that movie so much.
I never saw it. I don't
like to see the movie
until I finish the model.
Hmm.
Makes it more fun.
Wouldn't it be more fun
if we did something together?
Like, uh,
like couples manicures?
Or couples waxing?
[ Gasps ]
You could get a manzilian.
That stuff is for people
who are dating, Linda.
We-We do other couples stuff.
We couples live together.
And that's even better.
You know what?
I'm gonna go.
Okay, good.
I mean, okay.
Yeah.
Gonna be all by myself.
On my honeymoon,
I might add.
It's not our honeymoon,
Linda.
Hey, look!
Comes with a little Keanu.
Hi, guy.
[ High-pitched ]
"Hi, Bob. Missed you, buddy."
Oh, for Pete's sakes,
you big freak!
Bet you never knew washing out
rubber tubing could be
such a blast, huh, kids?
Well, I had a feeling.
Who wants to help me
glue a toupee
on an old man's cadaver?
Yay! This is like camp.
[ Groaning ]
Tina, what's bothering you?
The wig or the cadaver?
The cadaver.
Wigs can be scary.
You know what?
Why don't you kids go ahead
and take five?
Explore the morgue.
But stay away
from my computer.
- Not because of porn.
- This computer?
Come on, now.
What's this?
"A dating Web site
for morticians."
Mort,
you got a message!
Yeah. Well, this lady and I
have been messaging.
I sent her a wink.
She sent me back
a kissy face.
Kissy face?
That's a big deal.
You need to take
this relationship
into the real world, Mort.
Yeah! Reality, Mort.
MeetSpace!
Get into it.
Nah,
I'm not ready.
Ah, you're right, Mort.
You're wh-what, 50?
Wait till you're ready.
Fifty?
I'm 35 years old.
Huh?
If you believe
my dating profile.
[ All Laughing ]
Yeah.
And... send.
[ Beeps ]
What?
What'd you do?
Wash your hairpiece, Mort.
You're going on a date!
Oh, Keanu.
[ High-pitched ]
"Give me long sleeves."
Why? You look great
in a "T."
"I don't know.
Just switch it up."
Okay.
"No, no. Make me one
of those tuxedo T-shirts.
Do that.
That'll be funny."
That's stupid.
I don't like those.
Ah, I see
you're still playing
with your dolls.
Mm-hmm.
I just got back
from salsa boot camp.
I was the lonely
little salsa-ita.
All by myself.
"She's back."
Hey,
just be cool.
[ Louise ]
Mom, Dad, come quick!
Oh, my God!
What? What is it?
What's wrong?
Oh, nothing.
This is just silly.
Mort asked a girl
on a date.
A date?
It was the kids' idea.
Yep. I proposed
a romantic rendezvous
for 8:00 p.m. tonight...
at the elegant
Jimmy Pesto's.
What? Jimmy Pesto's?
What? I only know
two restaurants.
And they have
cloth napkins.
Don't rub it in.
Calm down.
Hey, she replied!
Already?
Too soon. Am I right?
It's not a good sign.
"Mort, it's a date.
See you at eight."
She's a rhymer.
Go, Mort. I mean,
it could be fun, two morticians.
Hey, what if
you and Linda come too?
No, no.
Yeah! A double date!
Oh, but who would
watch the kids?
Right. Yeah.
Tina can babysit.
I can?
Oh, come on.
We're a little old
to be babysat.
Isn't that
an outdated concept?
No.
Need I remind you what happened
last time she was "in charge"?
Free swim!
Special delivery!
Hobo dinner!
Oh, pshh. We'll just be
right across the street.
Tina can call us
on the emergency cell phone
if she needs to.
All right.
You bought the ticket.
You take the ride.
Come on, Linda.
We shouldn't go to this.
It will be bad.
Bob, we are going out tonight.
All right, fine, fine.
Yay!
But just for a couple hours.
And I'm wearing my lazy pants.
Okay.
And I'm gonna drink...
a lot.
Yay! Double date!
All right!
[ Linda Laughing ]
Oh! I love it.
I feel like
we're in Jamaica.
Ooh! Jamaican honeymoon.
You be just in time
for "pastafarian" night
with garlic "dreadsticks," mon.
Stop.
Groove with me to--
Uh-uh.
I--
No.
[ No Accent ]
You're such a jerk.
[ Thinking ]
I'm a born babysitter.
Tina brings the fun.
Now... sparkle.
Hi, Gene.
Would you like to play a game?
Maybe sing a song?
[ Grunts ]
Uh, Tina, will you
join me in the corner
for a little powwow?
Okay.
You're dying out there,
kid.
Yeah.
Everybody hates you.
I know.
I'm blowing it.
Should I call for help
on the emergency phone?
Hold on.
Maybe you should
think outside the box.
Okay.
How many times in our life
will we get a chance to wander
unsupervised in a morgue?
Yeah. Won't that be scary?
Tina,
you don't babysit from here.
You babysit from here.
My boob?
[ Sighs ]
Yes, your boob.
Really?
Yeah.
What's your boob
telling you, Tina?
I don't know.
[ High-pitched ]
Explore the morgue.
Explore the morgue?
That-a-girl!
[ Gene Screams ]
Sorry, just hungry.
♪ [ Reggae ]
♪ Try da ziti tonight
♪ Oh, yeah
It's on da special tonight ♪
Bobby,
they're playing our song.
What? Our song
isn't "Ziti Tonight."
[ Gasps ]
Oh, I think that's her!
Mort? I recognize you from
the picture on your Web site.
I'm Samantha.
Well, it's quite a pleasure
to meet you, Samantha.
This is my friend Bob
and his lovely wife Linda.
Hi.
Hi. We're
on our honeymoon.
Oh. Congratulations?
- Thank you.
- It's not our honeymoon.
Well, technically--
Not technically.
First time to Jamaica.
Oh, my God.
Sorry for the smell.
Long day slaving over
the old embalming table.
Well, let me just say that
I've been embalming you
with my eyes...
since the moment
you walked in.
[ Giggles ]
Mort!
[ Chuckles ]
Ugh.
Hush. It's their
special language.
Waiter,
do you have
anything bigger?
Come on, everybody!
♪ Try our dessert
♪ You gotta have
a cannoli ♪
Ooh, cannolis!
Let's move.
Oh, how thoughtless
of me.
Tina, I'm sure
you want to go first,
to protect us and stuff.
Yeah, Tina.
Earn that sweet
babysitter cash.
Wait, wait.
First, how 'bout a hug?
Hmm?
Aw.
- [ Louise ]
Mmm.
- Come here, Gene.
You're a good boy.
[ Grunts ]
Uh, weird.
Mmm.
All right.
Let's wrap this up.
Okay, I'm ready.
I'll go first.
Like a lamb
to the slaughter.
Oh, guys!
I, uh, I forgot
who sang "Funkytown."
I have to go look it up,
or it's gonna
bug me all night.
You're not going anywhere.
Aah!
Keep walking,
Tina.
[ Groans ]
[ Whispering ]
Are there bodies
in those coffins?
With all this green mold
around town,
better hope not.
What do you mean?
You're joking, right?
[ Scoffs ]
Only that green mold turns
bodies into the living dead.
[ Groans ]
Tina, you're a zombiephile.
You should know this!
I'm not a zombiephile.
I have a complicated
relationship with zombies.
They're dangerous,
but I love their swagger.
"Funkytown" is by
Lipps Incorporated.
I just remembered.
The morgue.
Well, here goes nothin'.
[ Tina Groans ]
♪ [ Reggae ]
[ Laughing ]
Every time they say
something horrible,
take a drink.
Bob, stop.
I'm doin' it.
So, what's the weirdest thing
you've ever found
in a human body?
- Here we go.
- You first.
- Lightbulb.
- [ Slurps ]
- A football.
A Far Side calendar.
[ Slurps ]
Really? Huh.
But most of the time,
what I find is
lots and lots of--
[ Together ]
Tumors.
Oh!
[ Both Laughing ]
Aw, already finishing
each other's--
Oh, my God, no.
Linda.
Senten--
Stop.
Tencences--
Sentences.
[ Slurps ]
[ Creaking ]
How long does it take
to open a door?
Okay.
[ Electrical Buzzing ]
- Aah!
- [ Lock Clicks ]
Smells a little moldy...
and corpsy.
Bad combo.
I don't think we should be here.
Yeah, let's go
back upstairs.
You're totally right, guys.
[ Rumbling ]
It's locked.
[ Tina ]
Louise, no!
[ Screams ]
[ Vibrating ]
[ Laughs ]
Silly us.
It was only a phone.
[ Sighs ]
Hello?
Who is it?
Some stranger.
Hello?
[ Low-pitched ]
Have you checked
the children?
Mom?
[ Sighs ]
No. I'm a zombie.
Oh.
[ Regular ]
No, I'm--
[ Low-pitched ]
I am also a murderer!
[ All Scream ]
♪ [ Reggae ]
[ Laughing ]
You go, girl.
Yeah, mon.
Hey, I gotcha!
Come on. Dance with Mommy.
Come on.
You drunk enough
to be any fun yet?
Yeah, I guess.
Bob, Linda.
Hugo, my man!
[ Buzzing Vibration ]
[ Indistinct ]
Linda,
I can't do it anymore.
Come on.
No.
I'm going home, Lin,
to Mort's.
Don't you ignore my lasso.
Whoa, doggie.
You got me.
[ Chuckles ]
Not you, Hugo.
Fair enough.
Fine, Bob.
We don't need you here anyway,
you big, sour blanket.
Who wants to see
what I learned today
in salsa class?
Ah, guess I can go
finish Speed bus.
[ Chorus ]
♪ Speed b us ♪
Then I can watch the movie.
Hope it's as good
as the model.
"It is."
Keanu?
[ Gene, Tina Screaming ]
Kids? Kids!
Keanu, where are they?
Downstairs?
"Yeah, probably."
Thanks.
Oh, I hate stairs.
"We've been drinking, huh?"
You got that right, buddy.
Oh, I feel
like I could pass out.
Anybody in there?
Hmm. What is that?
Satin?
Oh, man, that is
calling our name, Keanu.
"Get in there!"
Will do, buddy.
[ Grunting ]
Somebody close my bed.
[ Grunts ]
I'll get it.
Unlock the door, Louise.
We know you have the key.
Nope. I ate it.
We'll have to wait
till it comes out.
You never poop.
We're doomed!
Yep.
[ Snarling ]
What the hell?
[ Snarling Loudly ]
It's coming
from the next room.
She's messing
with us again.
No.
I swear. I did this,
but I am not doing that.
[ Snort ]
I won't get fooled again.
I'm the babysitter.
- [ Rumbling Snort ]
- [ Tina Screams ]
- [ Snorting Continues ]
- [ All Scream ]
[ All Shouting ]
[ Pounding ]
Kids, stop doing that.
It's me.
[ Bob, Muffled ]
Stop hitting the coffin!
Duct tape!
[ Louise ]
Hit it! Smash it!
I don't want to die!
♪ [ Reggae ]
[ Grunting ]
Let me out!
Now what?
Now...
we cremate it.
Cremate? No!
No cremating Dad!
[ Bob, Muffled ]
It was a drunk nap!
It's trying to
sweet-talk us.
That's classic zombie.
La, la, la.
La, la, la, la, la, la, la, la!
Open the casket!
La, la, la, la!
Let me out!
[ Kids ]
La, la, la, la, la, la, la!
Kids, it's your father!
For the love of God,
let me out!
La, la, la, la--
I'm gonna die alone.
And I'm in my lazy pants.
Linda hates these pants.
Damn it! They're coming off!
For you, Lin!
Now what?
Now we turn it on.
How?
Just pull all the levers...
a lot.
But they look like
robot wieners.
I know!
Okay!
[ All Grunting ]
It's not so bad.
Keep pulling
the robot wieners.
Whoo-hoo!
I love reggae.
Don't listen to anyone who says
you can't have a perfectly good
honeymoon by yourself.
[ Nervous Chuckles ]
Hey, hey!
I'm not done.
Let me tell you something.
I haven't known Samantha
very long.
But a woman knows
when another woman is aroused.
Whoo!
[ Nervous Chuckle ]
Heh.
[ Tina ]
Turn that thingy
while I pull this thingy.
You don't know how.
Let me.
I'm in charge.
[ Muffled ]
All right. Here it goes.
Superhuman strength.
You can do it!
Oh, what happened?
Dad?
- Uh-oh.
- Oh, my God!
I'm gonna die in here!
Dad, I've got you.
[ Bob ]
Oh, burning.
Coffin on fire.
Aah!
[ Panting ]
Oh, yes, air.
Kids, come here!
[ Gene, Louise ]
Tina's in charge!
Mmm.
Oh.
[ Laughing ]
Oh!
Aah!
Oh, now you come off.
What happened here?
My shop's a wreck!
Mort, lady mortician,
how's the date going?
Good.
Good!
- Are you okay, Bob?
- I faced death, Mort.
I know things now.
I know. You don't just
build a model of life.
You-You watch
the movie of life.
You-You get in the mood
and make some mortician babies,
you two.
Mort, your name,
kids are amazing.
Even if they try to
burn you alive in a coffin,
and they will do that.
[ All ]Yeah.
But it's good.
Because you see your
whole life pass before
you as you're burning.
And every pair of pants
you've ever worn.
And you'll see the love
of your life, dancing salsa
in Jamaica by herself.
Mort, and you,
what is your name?
Oh, Samantha.
Yes! That's beautiful!
Are you two in love or what?
Hopefully.
- Can I hear you say "yeah"?
- Yeah!
Yes, we are.
Yes, Bob.
Yeah!
Great!
Then feel it!
I can feel it!
Love!
I feel it!
Say "love"!
- Love!
Would you watch my kids
for ten minutes?
Sure.
Good. I gotta go.
Nice embalming table.
Is it disinfected?
Uh, Tina, do you think
maybe you could--
Say no more.
Gene, Louise, now!
Ow, my ear.
[ Kissing ]
No, no, no!
No! No! No!
[ All Scream ]
[ Mort ]
Wrong door.
[ Bob ]
Hello, baby.
[ Linda ] Bob!
Ah, disgusting!
I can see your
downstairs dreadlocks.
Go ahead and look,
Jimmy.
No, mon.
Yeah, mon.
Oh, Bobby, you big goof.
I took off my lazy pants.
Did you notice, Lin?
Yes, I did.
[ Hugo ]
God!
Care to couples dance with me?
On our haunted
Jamaican honeymoon?
[ Chuckles ]
That's green mold.
Right there
on Jimmy's wall.
What?
You see it?
Right there.
[ Linda Laughs ]
Yes.
Oh, crap.
She's right.
We win! We win!
[ Chuckles ]
Ah, just put
some bleach on it.
What?
[ All ]
♪ Weekend at Mort's
♪ We're gonna have
a weekend at Mort's ♪
[ Linda ]
Uh, uh, uh!
♪ Weekend at Mort's
♪ We're gonna have
a weekend at Mort's ♪
[ Bob, High-pitched ]
What?
♪ Weekend at
Mort's ♪
♪ We're gonna
have a weekend at
Mort's ♪
♪ We're gonna
have a weekend at
Mort's ♪
[ Linda ]
Uh, uh, uh!