本视频仅供英语学习交流，严禁用于商业途径
更多资源敬请关注公众号：晨雨资料库
[ Ukulele strumming ]
Bachelorette party!
All right!
Going to the strip club.
All right. Going to Pickles.
Boy, am I gonna need some
quarters tonight.
[ Laughs ]
Quarters?
Yeah.
Mm-hmm.
What are you gonna
do with quarters, Lin?
Oh, I'll plop 'em
in their G-strings.
You'll-- [ Scoffs ] You'll plop
quarters in their G-strings?
Plop 'em right in.
Plippity plop.
- At Pickles?
- Pickles.
Why do they call it Pickles?
They actually serve pickles.
Mmm.
No, I'm not kidding.
They really have good pickles.
You'd think they wouldn't,
but they're delicious.
You're going to dinner theater,
aren't you?
Nah--
[ Nervous Laughing ]
Wha--
What do you mean?
Wait-- That is crazy.
Fine, Bob.
You got me.
I know you don't approve
of dinner theater,
so I fibbed.
You know what? I'd rather
you go to a strip club.
What do you have against
dinner theater, Dad?
Well, first of all, Gene,
it's neither dinner nor theater.
It's like the imitation
cheese of theater.
Sounds fun.
Imitation cheese
is delicious.
That's my boy.
That's my star.
Linda, you know what
the real problem is?
What?
It's the result
of dinner theater--
what it does to you.
Makes you sing everything.
Who was that?
♪ Wrong number
- [ Groans ]
- ♪ Yeah
So what's for breakfast?
♪ Eggs, eggs
♪ Eggs, bom-bom
Eggs, eggs, eggs, eggs ♪
Oh, my God.
♪ Bom-bomp
So, Lin, it's, uh--
All right.
♪ Not tonight
No ♪
Okay.
♪ Not tonight
No ♪
I get it!
And so you're gonna be doing
that all week, right?
♪ No
[ Holds Note ]
♪ Yeah
[ Laughs ]
[ Man ]
♪ We drink, we loot,
we rape, we shoot ♪
[ Man #2 ]
♪ We sing, we dance,
we twirl, we prance ♪
[ With Singers ]
♪ We're the Pirates
of Panache ♪
Ow. Ow. Ow.
Linda,
tell me everything.
Oh, Mort, I'm telling you,
to be in dinner theater--
If I could do my life
over again, if I could--
[ Groans ]
If I could just have
one chance--
[ Laughs ]
You'd do that?
Yeah.
Linda, what are you
talking about?
You've got a great life.
You work in a restaurant.
- You get to feed
the world, right?
- Right.
There was someone in here from
Canada last week. Remember?
And we learned
all about that country.
That's great.
I hate that country.
You know, Linda, you've got
the dinner part already.
You know what that means.
You're halfway to doing--
- Yeah?
- Your own--
Say it. Yeah. Say it.
What? What?
Dinner theater!
Your very own
dinner theater!
- Dinner theater. Yes!
- No--
Yeah! My own din--
[ Laughs ]
Yay!
- Why are we excited?
- Hamburger dinner theater?
Ah, come on, Bobby!
We work hard every day
to make your dream come true.
Why can't we
do my dream too?
About how long do you think
your dream will take?
Like an hour, hour and a half?
Are you crazy?
It's got to be at least
a three-week engagement.
Three weeks?
How about three days?
All right.
We'll take it.
[ Chuckles ]
This is gonna be wonderful!
What's the show
gonna be?
[ Sighs ]
Murder. Murder mystery.
- [ Scoffs ]
- How about
mass murder mystery?
Okay, sure.
And a musical?
Of course.
Can it also be a love story?
Aw! A mass murder
mystery musical
love story set in, uh--
Nazi Germany.
Oh! In Montreal.
Enough with Canada!
In a ketchup factory?
A sexy ketchup factory?
[ Air Squeezing ]
I got it!
In a morgue!
I have props.
Oh, come on.
Yes, yes!
Mort, that's it.
We'll call it Dreamatorium.
Really?
♪ Dreamatorium
♪ It's a Dreamatorium
[ Groans ]
♪ Bom-bomp
Look at this set.
Am I in a morgue?
Oh, it feels like I am.
I am just so happy
we've all been bitten by
the dinner theater bug.
Now, Gene, you're on
sound effects, naturally.
[ Man Screams ]
Ominous.
Chills. Oh!
Remember-- every character
gets some intro and outro music.
- You got it.
- ♪ [ Bouncy Theme ]
- Don't. Don't score me.
- [ Deflating Sound ]
Mort, you're
on visual effects.
Fake blood. Or is it?
Now, script.
As you know,
everyone who enters my morgue
is mysteriously killed.
- Mort-- body delivery guy,
victim one.
- ♪ [ Single Note ]
Gene-- flower delivery guy,
victim two.
♪ [ Higher Note ]
Tina-- tree,
victim three.
♪ [ Lower Note ]
Louise-- the butler
who everyone thinks
is the killer.
You're the red herring.
♪ [ Suspense Note ]
Tina's a tree
that gets killed?
She wants to be a tree,
she can be a tree.
Tina's got stage fright.
I have stage fright?
Yes, sweetie. Ever since
you were a little baby.
Tina, say "Mommy."
"Mommy."
Uh--
"Ma."
Huh?
No.
I'll keep cutting.
You say when.
Uh--
Uh-- Uh--
[ Female Operator ]
911.
What's your emergency?
Uh--
Tina! Help!
Uh-- Uhh--
Hello?
Tina! Fire!
Uhh--
That explains a lot.
Now, Bobby, there's a small part
I'd like you to play--
the tree surgeon, who tries
to save the tree but instead
becomes victim number four.
I'd love to,
but absolutely not.
I'm already doing
the dinner part of this
dinner theater, Lin--
by myself, I might add.
- It's one line!
- No.
What's the matter?
Afraid you might get bitten?
[ Buzzes ]
Gotcha!
[ Laughs ]
Yeah. Yeah, good.
Let's do a scene right now.
Come on.
Let's do an improv.
An improv?
Yeah, an improv. I--
Hi. What's your--
Hi. How are you?
I'm just standing out here.
[ Mutters ]
So am I.
It's cold out.
Not really.
Uh--
I have
a big coat on.
See? You're good.
You're good.
That was good. Yes!
I don't like it.
That was a whole scene.
It just becomes a play.
I love that.
That's the play
we should do.
We'll call it Big Coat.
[ Barking ]
Red leather, yellow leather.
Um, are you talking
to me?
I'm warming up my instrument!
Unbelievable!
I am sor--
Uhh--
Hey, I'm sorry.
It's preshow nerves.
Come here.
Hug for luck.
You freakin' idiot!
You don't hug for luck
in the theater!
Uhh--
Shh, shh, shh.
Shh-shh.
I'm sorry, baby.
Shh, shh, shh.
I didn't mean it, baby.
You know how I get
before a big show.
You know how I get.
Get off of me!
Uhh--
You're smudging my makeup!
You want me to go out there
in front of these people...
with this makeup all smudged,
you clumsy oaf!
[ Sighs ]
Sorry, baby.
Come here.
♪ [ Bouncy ]
[ Bell Dings ]
Good evening, ladies.
Please enter and be 'tained.
I don't get it, Bob.
Why are people buying tickets
to eat a burger?
Linda's putting on
a dinner theater,
so you're paying
for the entertainment
plus the burger.
What if someone only wants
to eat a hamburger?
I guess you could just pay
for the burger and turn
your back to the stage.
I could kind of watch
like this, you know,
with my peripheral vision.
It'd be the honor system, Teddy.
I mean, if you find yourself
watching the show,
you should probably
buy a ticket, right?
[ Teddy ]
Oh, that's fair.
That's more than fair.
- [ Bob ] But, Teddy, you can't
talk during the show.
- No. No. No, I get it.
One time I was
at the movies, right?
♪ [ Fanfare ]
- Teddy, shh!
- This guy's phone goes off--
[ Bob ]
Teddy, they're starting.
[ Whispering ]
And this guy's phone
goes off--
And he picks up
the phone--
Don't tell the story, Teddy.
He picks up the phone, but
everyone in the theater's like--
Don't tell-- Shh!
"Stop it!"
You know, just "stop," right?
Teddy, stop!
Stop telling the story.
He just--
And everyone is like,
"Who's the killer?"
Shut your mouth.
Right. No.
That's what that guy did.
Shut your mouth.
[ Linda Clears Throat ]
♪ Everything dies
♪ But love
♪ [ Keyboard Continues ]
Good evening.
This is the story of love,
but there will be a murderer,
and it's up to you to guess
who that murderer is.
Hint-- It's not me.
Because I'm just Gladys,
a lonely morgue owner.
You know, they say most people
find love where they work.
Well, look where I work.
Corpse delivery
for a lonely morgue owner.
♪ That would be me
[ Mort Screams ]
I'm being murdered... to death!
[ Screaming ]
So no actual murder tonight,
just a lot of fake blood
and fake organs.
[ Chuckles ]
Right. Right. Fake.
[ Radio Chatter ]
Yeah, we might have overdone it
a little on the gore.
Well, no harm done.
Except for the people
being treated for shock.
Yeah, and the people
who demanded their money back.
Eh.
Well, the next performance
is gonna be really great.
Next performance?
Wasn't tonight's debacle
the end of dinner theater?
I just need to tweak
some stuff for tomorrow's show.
Maybe tone down
the blood a smidge.
What?
I've been thinking.
I want to get over
the stage fright.
I think I'd like
to have a line.
Aw, Bob!
Our tree is growing up
and sprouting words.
Let's write you a speech for
tomorrow night's performance.
Can I say, "No. Don't"?
That's exactly
what a tree would say!
I'll have it memorized
by tomorrow night.
Lin, you lived out
your dream on stage
for a couple minutes,
and since there were
no charges filed--
They can never take that
away from you, right?
Bob, my dream has not been--
♪ satisfied
The show must go on, Dad.
Yeah. Did you give up after
you made your first burger?
It ain't over
till it's over.
No. You added
garlic powder.
Luck is 90%
preparation and--
Gene, enough.
[ Gene Groans ]
[ Sighs ]
Two more shows.
This tastes nothing
like real blood!
Flowers for a lonely
morgue owner.
That's me!
Oh, God! That feels like
a sharp knife in my belly.
[ Groans, Screams ]
[ Groaning ]
[ Whispering ]
Psst! Gene. Hey.
[ Groaning Continues ]
Gene. Gene.
Yeah? Uh-huh?
Are you done?
No.
I need you to serve this
to table 3.
[ Linda ] Bob, shh!
He's dying. Stop.
I'm sorry.
Come on--
[ Clears Throat ]
Come on, butler.
Let's go out
into the garden.
Uhh--
Tina! Tina,
it's your big line.
Uhh--
- Go!
- No. Don't.
The tree!
It's been murdered.
Oh, butler,
who is committing
all these murders?
Beats me.
Oh, there's my knife.
Well, I sure don't know
whodunit.
Do you?
♪ [ Keyboard ]
Is the tree the murderer?
♪ [ Continues ]
Or is the flower
delivery man the murderer?
Or perhaps
the suspicious butler?
Well, you're all wrong.
♪ The murderer was me
[ Keyboard: Bark ]
Ha, ha!
What?
You explicitly told us...
at the beginning of the show
you weren't the murderer.
That's right.
It's a twist!
No, it's a lie.
A lie is not a twist.
Don't be nervous.
You do this all the time.
The cast will be signing
autographs if anyone
would like one.
Everyone back in their seat!
Now!
This is a robbery!
♪ [ Suspense Note ]
[ Woman ] Ooh.
A robbery--
Now that's a twist.
This is not part
of the show, people.
This is a real robbery.
Kids, get behind
the counter.
[ Whispering ]
We can take this guy.
I go high, you go low.
Wait. What?
Never mind.
Wait--
You blew it.
You blew it, Tina.
Everyone stay where you are!
Give me everything
in the register.
Yeah, fine. Listen.
There are kids here,
so don't do
anything stupid...er
than rob this place.
Shut up, greaseball.
Don't call me greaseball.
♪ [ Note ]
Uh, mask face.
[ Laughter ]
It's not part of the show.
- Show?
- ♪ [ Continues ]
- Gene, stop.
- Just take it easy.
Oh, I'll take it...
easy.
[ Crowd Murmurs ]
[ Police Radio Chatter ]
Hmm! They added a robbery
element to the show.
That's clever.
The ski mask
is a little cheesy.
I think it looks
pretty good.
Okay, that's all of it.
You've got your money.
Now be on your way.
- Give me a little music.
- Oh, come on. Just go.
♪ [ Scatting ]
♪ [ Keyboard ]
[ Scatting ]
Do your last line again.
Go!
[ Flatly ]
You've got your money.
Now be on your way?
♪ Maybe I'll leave
♪ And maybe I'll stay
♪ Maybe it's the limelight
♪ [ Keyboard Continues ]
♪ Could be the singin'
♪ 911 should be a-ringin'
♪ But I can't stop
♪ And neither can I
Sit down, sit down!
I'm kidding. I'm kid--
Everyone up. Come on!
It's not part
of the show.
Play me out.
♪ [ Bouncy ]
[ Applause Continues ]
Can you break a five?
I'd love to tip out
the cast.
♪ [ Stops ]
No! I can't
break a five, lady!
I was just robbed!
Did you not just see that?
You were standing
right here, idiot!
Oh, you people commit.
Get out!
We feel terrible
we didn't stop that
robbery last night.
Oh, that robbery
was horrible!
[ Shudders ]
Though I have to admit,
it felt so good to hear
the audience applaud.
- [ Bell Rings ]
- Hey, are you guys talking
about that show last night?
I thought it was dazzling.
Oh, yeah?
You saw Dreamatorium?
Yeah, I caught the end of it.
I thought the guy
who played the robber
really stole the show.
Is that
why you guys are here?
No, they're here because
the robber was a real robber...
and he stole 227 bucks.
- Eh, a little less than that.
- It'll be hard to catch
this guy.
Nobody got
a good look at him.
Put this down
in your report.
He was leading-man handsome.
He was wearing a ski mask.
Well, he had the presence
of a young Burt Reynolds.
And the pipes
of an old Debbie Reynolds.
Hey, the online
reviews are in.
Listen to this one.
It's from whosyourdaddy1997.
"The plot
made zero sense,
and the set looked
like children
made it."
Yeah!
Children did make it--
my children!
"But the reason to go see
Dreamatorium is the
closing musical number.
The chemistry between
the robber character...
and the lonely morgue
operator was sparktastic."
Did anyone
mention the food?
Uh, no.
Great. So the robbery
got rave reviews.
Bob, we're a hit!
- No, Linda. We were hit.
- Good one.
Yeah.
That's good.
Thanks.
- I don't get it.
- We were hit.
A hit is a ro--
Am I wrong?
It's a robbery, right?
- [ Chattering ]
- Right. A hit is a robbery.
Well, technically,
for the cops--
Technically, no,
it's not--
Wait--
- Forget it. Forget it.
- In layman--
In layman's terms.
Forget it. Everybody.
Nobody got hit.
Everybody, forget it.
There we were, putting on
the show of our lives,
when in walked a man
with a gun in his hand.
And he was looking
for you-know-who.
- We will now take questions.
- Here, here, here!
- Me.
- Large Tommy.
Question for Tina.
Were you scared?
Um, uh--
Uhh--
No, she wasn't.
- Ooh! Ooh!
- Normal-size Jenny.
How big was the gun,
and did anyone get shot?
That's a two-part question.
I don't answer those.
- Aw.
- Tiny Peter.
Does this mean
you're in a gang now?
That is correct.
Our gang is called
the Broken Glass Kids.
- We'll cut you.
- [ Gasping ]
Wow!
[ Linda ]
Oh! I can't wait
for the show tonight.
What, tonight?
I thought maybe you'd
consider canceling,
but you're really committed
to making me unhappy.
The show won't be the same
without the robber.
What?
You're all thinking it!
I got to agree.
That guy could really
sing... and rob.
Well, again, our apologies.
We'll follow up as soon
as we hear anything.
So happy for you though.
Thanks.
[ Sighs ]
Mort.
[ Bell Dings ]
You're right.
What am I gonna do
without the robber?
You'll just have to--
♪ Take it easy
Wait a minute.
That voice.
Oh, my God! It's you!
You're the robber!
Guilty.
[ Exclaims ]
Last night was something,
wasn't it?
Oh, I know.
We were electric together.
So let's do it again tonight.
Yes.
I want to report a, uh--
What are you doing, Linda?
I'm getting this guy arrested.
[ Dialing ]
No, but he wants
to do the show again.
[ Grunting ]
He robbed us with a gun.
[ Stammers ]
Hey, everyone, relax.
It wasn't even a real gun.
Fake. And currently
in my other jacket locked
in the trunk of my car.
Bob, he wants to perform.
This guy is the missing
ingredient to my show.
He's my garlic powder.
Yes. The man who robbed
my restaurant
is here right now.
He's about 5'8",
maybe 150 pounds.
I'm bad at guessing weight
though, so--
Yeah, I'll say.
Yeah.
Uh-- 160?
Oh, flatterer.
All right, 170.
Ooh!
[ Yelps ]
Uh, call you back.
You said the gun
was in your car.
- I lied.
- What about it being fake?
Also a lie.
See?
A lie can be a twist.
Since you did that,
I'm gonna do this.
Register.
Great. Again.
Good luck tonight without me!
We forgot to give this
to you.
A little
"Sorry we let the robber
get away" Bundt cake.
You're doing it again.
He just ran right past you.
[ Radio Chatter ]
Hold that thought, Bob.
The guy who robbed us
just robbed us again!
Hold on. Can you
repeat that, Dispatch?
Suspect--
[ Continues, Indistinct ]
He's saying what I'm saying.
The guy who robbed us--
he just left.
We got to go, Bob.
The guy who robbed you
was just spotted in the area!
[ Bell Rings ]
[ Panting ]
Don't catch him,
don't catch him,
don't catch him!
[ Grunts ]
Ah, they got him.
Geez.
Julia packs a wallop.
Ah, you couldn't just let me
have my dream, could you?
What? You mean 'cause
I called the police?
The guy committed
armed robbery, Lin-- twice.
But you committed murder, Bob.
You blew my dream's head off.
That's a little
dramatic, Lin.
Yes, Bob, 'cause I used
to be an actor.
Only two tickets left
for Dreamatorium,
the show over three people
have been blogging about.
Final performance, people.
Do you think you're gonna
say your line tonight?
Probably not.
You know, a good way to
beat the stage fright--
imagine
the audience naked.
I already do that.
I imagine everyone naked.
Everyone?
All the time?
Yeah. You don't do that?
No.
Oh.
Well, try
picturing the audience
with clothes on then.
Like all their clothes?
Well, maybe just
a condom and a hat.
Okay.
Tonight's show is
officially sold out.
Packed house.
Are you feeling it, Mom?
Whoo!
Are you feeling it, Dad?
Eh, who cares?
The audience is expecting
to be dazzled,
but thanks to your father,
we have no star.
[ Sighs ]
Let's just go do the version
everyone hated.
Whodunit?
Was the murderer
the corpse delivery guy?
♪ [ Keyboard ]
Or was it
the flower delivery guy?
Or was the murderer
the shifty butler?
♪ [ Continues ]
Wrong.
The murderer was me.
Thank you. Good night.
Hold on. I saw
the show last night.
Trust me,
it's about to get good.
That's our show, everyone.
Thanks for coming out.
What about the you-know-who
surprise performer?
Yeah, well, the show is
what it is, so-- Good night.
I'll tell you what it is.
It's garbage.
Okay, all right then.
Drive safe.
[ Bob ]
Nobody move!
This is a robbery!
I said sit back down,
lady, or I'll shoot!
Oh, Bobby,
you're in the show!
Garbage.
I don't want your money.
I just want the money
of the big shot
who owns this place.
Ooh, way to commit, honey.
Boy, I thought
we did better today.
Oh. Well--
[ Clears Throat ]
All right, here it goes.
♪ So I'm singin' words
to a song
I'm making up right now ♪
♪ 'Cause it's
the singing that matters
and not the song ♪
♪ So it's up to me
♪ To
♪ Sing
♪ In
[ High-pitched ]
♪ Key
Ow!
[ Both, Out of Tune ]
♪ Key
♪ Ee
That was great.
Yeah, just go--
[ Laughs ]
What? I--
It's a little high.
Well, I nailed it.
You were a little high.
So you go higher.
Oh.
I think we can--
Everyone's gone.
Yeah, I think
we can stop.
- We cleared them out.
- No. Don't.
I did it.
Tina, take a bow, girl.