本视频仅供英语学习交流，严禁用于商业途径
更多资源敬请关注公众号：晨雨资料库
[ Ukulele strumming ]
[ Groaning ]
Tina, if you're gonna
lay on the floor,
at least roll around
so I don't have to mop up later.
What's wrong with Tina?
Puberty.
Oh.
Yeah.
She's pubing out
right now pretty bad.
Jordan Sturman moved away,
and now I'll never play
kickball with him again.
Oh, you should
kill yourself.
Yeah!
Gene and Louise, be nice.
You're gonna go
through adolescence too,
you know.
Like that? Oh, sick!
Is she contagious?
You shut up, Mom!
- Watch it.
- You can't hurt me.
I'm already dead.
Can I have
your mustache, then?
It's only one hair.
It's the beginning
of a great thing.
It's a huge hair.
I can't cut it.
[ Linda ]
It's beautiful.
Leave her alone.
You're beautiful, Tina.
Let me pull it out.
Let me put my foot
on your chest.
Gene, get off.
Enough.
Come on, Gene.
Let's go have
a childhood.
My heart.
Shh, sweetie.
I'm on the phone.
Ginger is very upset.
[ Laughs ]
Go on, Ginger.
What?
[ Laughs ]
No!
Come on, Tina.
Get up.
You're on the grill.
Why?
Come on.
Cheer up, you know?
We're having fun.
We are?
Yeah.
Plus, it's father-daughter time.
Why don't Gene and Louise
have to have fun
like this?
Tina, you're the oldest,
and you have added
responsibilities here.
Like on Saturday mornings,
for example,
you're on the grill.
I can't trust them on the grill.
You know that.
I mean, fire comes out of it.
[ Laughs ]
I know. It's awful.
All right. Bye.
Ginger's cat died,
but in a really funny way.
[ Laughing ]
- [ Bell Rings ]
- Tina!
We just saw the most
amazing thing ever.
This might be
the best day of my life,
besides the day
you kids were born.
Words can't explain this.
You just have to see it.
Come with us.
Come on, Tina!
I can't. Dad won't let me
leave work-- I mean, fun.
He won't let me leave
fun father-daughter time.
You fell for that?
That's not a real thing.
Come with us.
Aw, Bob, let her go.
All right, fine,
but you're gonna miss
when I scrape off the grill.
It's the best part of the day,
although today
has been pretty slow,
so there's not gonna be
as much gunk as there--
[ Bell Rings ]
Oh. Everyone's gone.
Oh.
Ow.
Oh!
Aren't you supposed to lead
someone who's blindfolded?
It would ruin
the surprise.
Where are we going?
At first, we thought
it was a break dancing class,
and then we thought
it was a special-needs class.
Now we think it might be
a special-needs
break dancing class.
Also, it's Brazilian--
Slash, hilarious.
- Sounds interesting.
- Stupid?
Oh, it's even more stupid
than you could possibly imagine.
Just wait till we get near it.
They take off their shoes,
so when they open the door,
the whole block smells
like feet.
Feet that have been cooked
in feet.
Yes!
[ Gene ]
Still funny.
[ Laughs ]
Oh! Ooh. Ooh.
Can you smell that?
That's just what's
coming through the walls.
[ Sniffs ]
It smells exotic,
like ranch dressing.
Whoa! He's beautiful.
That's a man?
Where are you going?
I'm signing up
for that class.
What? Why?
Ow.
Don't open the door!
The smell will kill us all!
[ Grunting ]
Let me go.
Let go of me.
No!
Oh! The feet smell.
The feet smell.
Wait. What is it?
It's capoeira.
Capo-what?
Tina, are you really sure
you want to do this?
Yes, Dad.
[ Grunts ]
Wait till you see it.
Jairo is amazing.
I have a DVD.
Oh, by the way,
I need 14.95 for the DVD.
Wait. What? What's "gyro"?
[ Grunts ]
Olá. My name is Jairo.
Welcome to the world
of capoeira.
Capoeira is the most
seductive form of self-defense.
It combines peacefulness,
fighting and cardio
in perfect harmony.
Capoeira is breathtaking,
but it is also breath-giving.
[ Blows ]
You can advance
through the stages...
by earning
different colored cords
at the troca de cordoes.
Wow, I thought maybe
you were doing it wrong,
but that's actually
what it looks like.
They're bringing
the tambourine back.
That's a pandeiro,
a Brazilian frame drum.
It's a tambourine.
I'm gonna get mine.
Those guys don't know
how to shake it.
I don't get it.
I mean, what am I
looking at here?
What is it?
Is it some kind of dancing?
Jairo says it's not dancing.
- It's a deadly form
of street fighting.
- Oh, yeah?
Well, you don't need
some male model
to teach you how to fight.
That's what dads are for.
Come on.
I'll show you some stuff.
Box with your old man, huh?
Tambourine! Tambourine!
There you go.
Just got to--
There it is.
[ Groans ]
Whoa, Tina.
Good fight. Good fight.
That was fun to watch.
Jairo says if there's
any capoeira inside me,
he'll find it
with enough classes.
Jairo knows
a lot about life.
Mmm.
Jairo says
he can hypnotize animals.
Shh.
But only if they want
to be hypnotized--
Tina, shh, shh, shh, shh.
which they almost always do.
Tina!
Jairo says toothpaste
insults your teeth.
[ Sighs ]
Tina, go to bed.
[ Snoring ]
Jairo only needs two hours
of sleep a night...
'cause he regulates
his heart.
Tina, get out.
Jairo sleeps
with his eyes open.
Tina!
[ Jairo ]
Okay. Just follow my lead.
[ Grunts ]
Brazil!
[ Jairo ]
Class is over.
We now have an hour
of open practice time,
which is completely optional
unless you're serious
about capoeira.
[ Grunting ]
[ Grunting Continues ]
Oh, I'm definitely staying.
[ Sighs ]
Tina is supposed to be here
to cover the grill.
It's after 4:30.
She's at a kookaburra class.
Dad, the grill is doing
that thing again.
[ Groans ]
What is your problem
with fire?
You know what?
Go. Go away.
Go down and collect trash
and bring it
to the Dumpster.
Does it have to be
from around here,
or can we go anywhere?
Just go.
Yeah!
Yay!
Trash! Trash!
Trash time!
[ Gene ]
Yesterday I found
a necklace.
It's time for
my afternoon meeting,
you know, in the bathroom.
Your 4:30 meeting?
Yeah, my 4:30.
- So go.
- [ Sighs ]
No.
Tina made a commitment
to be here at a certain time.
I'm going down there
to remind her that
she has a job here.
Wait.
What about your meeting?
Well, I'm postponing it today.
Bob, you can't do that.
I'm gonna set a time
for 10:30 tonight.
This is why
I tell you, Bob,
just have little meetings
throughout the day,
instead of one big one.
Little poops.
Ugh! Oh!
That is horrible.
Wash your feet.
I have an infection.
Tina. Tine.
Psst, psst, psst.
Dad,
what are you doing here?
You're supposed to be
back at work, Tina,
to cover me for my,
uh, 4:30 meeting.
Dad!
Oh, hello.
Please remove your shoes.
Oh, I don't want
to take off my shoes.
I'm just picking up
my daughter Tina.
Oh, you are Tina's father.
Olá.
My name is Jairo,
like "gyrate."
Oy. Mine-- Mine's Bob.
Are you sure
you don't want to stick around?
I enjoy helping elderly men
repair their aging bodies.
Thanks, but I got a job
I gotta get back to,
and so does Tina.
Plus, I don't really dance.
Although capoeira
incorporates elements of dance,
it is a highly dangerous form
of martial arts.
[ Chuckling ]
Right. I'm sure it is.
It seems like a great way
to stay in shape,
like Jazzercise.
- Not... like Jazzercise.
- Whatever you say.
Class, would you like to see
a demonstration?
Come on.
Tina, let's go right now.
[ Grunting ]
Okay, okay.
I saw your movie.
It's very cute.
- Ponytail!
- Hey! You can't do that.
You just hit me with your hair.
- Ponytail!
- Stop that!
- [ Groans ]
- Uh-oh.
- [ Students Clapping ]
- Dad, let's go.
Come on.
Give me a second here.
What about your meeting?
I just had my meeting.
- Right now?
- Mm-hmm.
Uh--
[ Panting ]
Don't. Don't.
What do we do?
Grab me that flag.
No, Dad.
[ Groans ]
Tina, we're gonna
get out of here.
All right?
Just let me think. Shh!
All right.
I got an idea.
You go into the corner
and yell.
What?
Go in the corner
and start yelling you're
having a heart attack,
and I'll run out.
Okay.
Go. Go.
Fast. Wait. Come back.
I'm having a heart-- What?
Don't-- Shh!
Don't do that.
It's a dumb idea.
Dad!
I'm so embarrassed.
Oh! Oh, are you?
I'm sorry 'cause
I'm not embarrassed at all
because I just pooped my pants.
I would do this every day
if I could, Tina.
[ Linda ]
No, no. He's in the shower now.
Well, sometimes
it's hard to feel clean...
after something
like that happens.
It's very embarrassing.
Okay, kids, your father
is very tender right now,
all right?
Whatever you do, do not mention
what happened today
at Tina's class.
Just act normal.
- So you pooped your pants!
- Linda, let's not talk
about it.
Wasn't a fair fight.
He's younger,
and he's cute and strong.
- Linda, this isn't helpful.
- Hey, when you got to go,
you got to go.
Linda, stop.
Are you on the phone
with Ginger?
No.
I got to go.
[ Laughs ]
I'm sorry!
Bobby, I'm not laughing at you.
I was thinking
about Ginger's dead cat again.
Dad, Dad, Dad.
Yes, Louise?
Dad, hi.
Did you know that it only takes
two pounds of pressure...
to drive someone's nose bone
into their brain?
- That's-- What?
- Two pounds. That's it, Dad.
Why are you telling me this,
Louise?
[ Growling ]
Revenge.
Revengeourine, revengeourine,
revengeourine.
Cut it out, Gene.
All right,
listen, everybody.
What happened today
is in the past,
and we're never gonna
talk about it again,
ever.
I'm just glad Tina is quitting
the class, right, Tina?
But my body needs it.
Your body needs to work
in the restaurant
with your father.
[ Groans ]
Oh, fine.
If you need me,
I'll be down here
on the floor... dying.
All right.
Sounds good, honey.
[ Groans ]
You have to learn
to groan right, Tina.
[ Groaning ]
Hey, she groans fine.
It sounds weird.
So you groan then
if you're so good at it.
[ Groans ]
That's a groan?
Yeah. [ Groans ]
I'll do it.
Let me do it.
[ All Groaning ]
[ Groaning Continues ]
[ Groaning ]
Tina, enough already.
Come on.
- [ Bell Rings ]
- [ Louise ]
Tina, it's your boyfriend.
- Oh, God.
- Olá.
- What do you want?
- I got a message
that Tina was very upset...
and needed to be
encouraged to come back
to the art of capoeira.
A message? From who?
You're welcome,
and... you're welcome.
Well, I'm sorry.
Tina is busy.
She's working the grill.
It's okay. I'll wait.
Hmm.
[ Groans ]
[ Mutters ]
What's wrong?
I'm looking
for your fresh-squeezed
juice selection.
Is it on another menu?
[ Clears Throat ]
Oh, sorry. Oh--
Yeah. Here it is.
- This is the same menu.
- Yeah-- 'cause we don't have
fresh-squeezed juice.
[ Imitating Jairo ]
Fresh-squeezed juice is stupid.
That is not how I talk
at all.
[ Imitating Jairo ]
Yes, it is. So is capoeira.
It's stupid, okay?
Dad, stop.
[ Jairo ]
Oh, hello, Tina.
- I didn't notice you.
- That's okay.
Is everything all right
with you, Tina?
My dad won't
let me train anymore.
Tina.
- What?
- It's because you made him
poop in his pants.
- Oh, my God.
- Tina!
Bob, please.
There is nothing
to be embarrassed about.
It is quite common
for a wounded animal
to make a bowel movement...
as he is defeated
by a much stronger predator.
Hey, it wasn't you.
It was 4:30.
Here, Bob,
let me show you...
some very convenient
sphincter-tightening
exercises.
No, thank you.
Tight! Relax.
I don't want--
Tight. Relax.
- Stop it!
- Tight.
Don't do sphincter-tightening
exercises in my restaurant.
Okay. Fine.
Thank you!
I'll be feeling this
in the morning.
[ Sighs ]
[ Bob ]
Gene!
[ Groans ]
Now my stomach is full
of negative energy,
so I've lost my appetite,
which is just as well.
It's time for me
to go to class.
Tina, you should come
with me.
Remember, the troca de cordoes
is next week.
The troca de cordoes?
What's
the troca de cordoes?
I feel if Tina trains hard,
she has the potential
to receive a promotion
to yellow cord.
Tina, listen to me.
You're not going anywhere.
I'm your father.
Yes, Tina,
but I am your capoeira
instructor.
Wait. I'm going to class
with you.
Tina, what are you doing?
Dad, you don't understand.
I understand
you're grounded,
effective right now.
Bob, let her go.
No. She's grounded, Lin.
We all just need a minute
to calm down.
Hey, Tina,
you walk out that door,
and you're no longer
my grill cook.
Dad, calm down.
I'll go get her.
You get out of here!
You hear me?
Never look back!
You are dead to us.
Sorry, Dad.
There's no getting
through to that one.
Thanks, Louise.
That was very helpful.
Big day.
Mm-hmm.
Big, big day.
Mmm.
The troca de "cordios."
I know.
I know it's
the troca de "cordios."
I told you, I'm not going.
Okay. Fine.
I'm just gonna say
one more time,
I think that you should
come support your daughter.
Linda, I just grounded her.
You let her go.
Bob, I'm sorry. Okay.
Come on.
It's just a phase.
I know you're afraid
you're gonna lose
your little girl.
That's sweet,
but what'd you think?
She's gonna spend
the rest of her life...
standing next to you
grilling burgers?
[ Both Chuckling ]
[ Chuckling Continues ]
[ Both Laughing ]
That's silly.
[ Scoffs ]
Spending the rest of her life
standing next to me
grilling burgers.
Of course not.
I mean, nothing wrong with it.
I mean, it would be fun.
Tinarine, Tinarine,
cha-cha-cha, Tinarine!
Tina, Tina,
Tina, Tina, Tinarine!
We're ready.
Okay! I'm coming.
I'm sorry, Tina.
I'm not going.
I love this restaurant.
You can't abandon the things
you love just because
of sexy dance fighting.
If I were a hamburger,
you'd come watch me fight.
Good job, Bob.
Gene, Louise, come on.
We're going to Tina's
karate concert.
So you're not going
to get revenge today?
- No, Louise. I'm not.
- Okay. Got it.
Then I won't bring
your credit card,
which I cut into a ninja star.
- Oh, you cut my credit card?
- Into a ninja star.
Tambourine, tambourine,
ninja star, credit card,
tambourine.
Family drama
at Bob's Burgers, huh?
Bob. Bob.
Bobby.
What, Teddy?
What's a troca de cordoes?
It's a ceremony.
It's like a graduation.
Oh.
Yeah, but this guy's
a creep, and I gotta
stand my ground.
She made a commitment
to this restaurant, period.
Mmm.
"Exchange of strands."
What?
I just looked up
troca de cordoes.
It's Portuguese
for "exchange of strands."
Sounds momentous.
This very day,
she's becoming a woman,
exchanging her strands.
Wait.
That's what it says?
Yeah. That's what it says.
It says
she's becoming a woman?
Well, yeah. Take a look.
What are you
gonna do about it, Bob?
Doesn't say becoming a woman.
No. Read into it.
It says,
"exchange of strands."
It's exchanging strands.
Has nothing
about her becoming a woman.
What are you saying, Bob?
What are you saying,
Teddy?
I just-- If my daughter
was becoming a woman,
I would want to be there.
She's not
becoming a woman, Teddy.
No, but if she was, I'm saying.
She's not my daughter.
You were the one
who just said it again.
Get out.
Get out, Teddy.
I want to pay my bill!
Get out of my restaurant!
I want to pay my bill.
Here's your bill--
$4.16, pervert.
Four dollars and--
Pervert? Pervert?
Pervert.
Who you calling pervert?
It's written on the bill.
Here's your $4.16, Bob.
Best of luck.
There's
a million restaurants
I can go to.
Then go to them all,
Teddy!
I'm sorry, Teddy.
I get carried away.
No. I blew my stack.
I'm sorry.
It's just,
she's growing up so fast.
Also, I crapped my pants
yesterday.
Yeah, I know. I heard.
[ Laughs ]
[ Clears Throat ]
Listen,
I got to close up shop.
I have somewhere to be.
So you really do
have to get out.
[ Grunts ]
[ Groaning ]
Brazil.
That's my son.
[ Jairo Grunting ]
Ugh! God.
Brazil!
[ Grunts ]
[ Grunting ]
And I'm, uh-- Brazil.
Finished.
Congratulations, Neil.
You have earned
your yellow cord.
Tina, you're next.
All right!
Go, Tina!
You're doing great.
[ Jairo Grunting ]
[ Grunts ]
Hyah!
So glad you came,
Bobby.
She looks like
she's having a good time.
[ Grunting ]
Hyah! Brazil!
[ Grunts ]
Thank you.
The test is complete.
I'm sorry, Tina,
but you have failed.
[ Scattered Applause ]
Have a seat.
The next student testing
for her yellow corda
is Janelle.
Hey, hey, hey, hey.
Wait, wait.
Wait a minute. Wait.
Please do not interrupt
the ceremony, Bob.
Give her the stupid cord.
Can't you see how much
this means to her?
I'm sorry, Bob,
but she did not perform
the five elementary motions,
so she will not be receiving
her yellow corda.
What?
She did better than Neil.
That kid was a mess out there.
What?
Oh, you know it's true.
Tina did all five
of the elementary
weird motions, I think.
She did that one.
She did that one a lot.
Is this because
I made you poop
your pantalonas?
- [ Onlookers Murmur ]
- This isn't about me.
It's about Tina.
Oh, is that what you think?
All right. That's it.
I'm taking a corda.
Ow!
Don't touch.
Ponytail!
Stop that.
Make me.
[ Gasps ]
Fight, fight,
fight, fight, fight!
Nose bone!
Nose bone into the brain--
Then skin him
and wear him like a costume.
All right, Louise.
All right.
All right, here we go.
Bobby, don't do this.
I have to stand up for Tina.
But, Bob, look at the clock.
It's 4:28.
I know, Lin.
I know, and if I poop, I poop.
Oh, Bobby.
[ Jairo ]
Come on!
[ Chanting ]
Jairo! Jairo!
Jairo! Jairo! Jairo!
[ Chanting Continues ]
[ Grunts ]
Ow!
[ Chuckles ]
All right, hold on.
I wasn't ready
that time, so--
Brazil!
- Ponytail!
- Ow!
Keep your sphincter tight,
Bobby.
- I'm okay, Lin.
- Use this, Dad.
- Ow! Louise--
- [ Louise ]
Sorry.
- Ponytail!
- Ow!
Brazil!
[ Groans ]
Hey, you want
some more?
Um--
Hyah!
- Ow!
- Make it stop, Mom.
[ Jairo ]
Brazil!
[ Bob Groans ]
[ Thinking ]
Dad was right.
Jairo is just a jerk--
Ponytail!
a sexy, sensual,
creepy, sexy jerk.
Go, Dad! Come on.
Dad, Dad!
[ Chanting ]
Dad! Dad! Dad! Dad! Dad! Dad!
[ Chanting Continues ]
Thanks, Tina.
I got him right where
I want him.
[ Chanting Continues ]
Ow!
Keep going.
Hyah!
Ow! Ow!
- Hey, nice form.
- Thanks.
Sorry Jairo
knocked you down
25 to 30 times...
in front of everyone.
Yeah. Sorry I couldn't get
your yellow corda.
It's okay.
Thanks for getting
beat up for me.
Hmm.
Anyway,
I'm kind of interested...
in Russian kettlebell
strength training now.
[ Bob ]
Don't make me watch this
'cause I--
I'll show Mom.
Yeah.
Well, I have a surprise
for you.
You got a promotion.
Really?
I get a raise?
No, but you get
these yellow dish gloves.
I present to you
your yellow gloves.
So much fun.
Well,
we better get going.
Yeah. That dead seal
down at the pier
isn't gonna poke itself.
Wait, wait. Hold on.
You two are working today.
What?
We're not on the schedule today.
Read! Learn how to read
the schedule that you write.
Tina, honey,
we're giving you the day off.
Go do something fun.
Do you know where
this dead seal is?
What's that about?
Its a dead seal, Mom.
A washed-up seal.
They go poke at it.
And we're gonna slap it.
It makes a great sound.
And I sample the slaps.
Sounds like an orgy.
I like dead seals, but...
I think I'm gonna
stay here instead.
I'm actually having fun
at work today.
Besides, it's our
father-daughter time.
Aw!
Sucker!
Gene, run.
Run, run,
run, run,
run to the seal!