本视频仅供英语学习交流，严禁用于商业途径
更多资源敬请关注公众号：晨雨资料库
[ Ukulele Strumming ]
[ Man On TV ]
Ocean Avenue is gearing up
for this year's Lobsterfest,
and that mean old tropical storm
we've been watching is
movin' out to sea,
which means perfect
weekend weather!
Ugh! Damn it!
So if you think
you hear thunder,
it's just my stomach growling.
[ Laughs ]
I love lobster.
This guy is unbelievable.
Stop pimping for Lobsterfest!
And start primping
for Lobsterfest.
Mmm.
[ Growls ]
Looking primpy.
No! No primping for anything!
- Why are you so grumpy?
Come on.
- You know why.
It's no fun
being a burger man
in a seafood town.
I hate lobsters
and their
stupid fest.
Plus, I'm allergic.
No, you're not.
Yeah. I'm allergic.
Remember our first date?
Yeah, I remember our first date.
You were a nervous wreck.
♪ [ Funky Guitar ]
[ Man ]
Ahhh! Uhh!
Oh, yeah.
♪ [ Woman Vocalizing ]
I was having
an allergic reac--
Never mind.
Hey, what are you guys
looking at over there?
Um, nothing.
Just pictures of people--
[ Quietly ]
doing it.
Oh. Hey, wait a minute.
That's not porn.
You brought
a Lobsterfest brochure
into this house?
Can we please go
this year?
Absolutely not.
Ugh! But there's
so much fun stuff happening.
Unveiling of the world's
largest butter vat,
for instance.
The coronation
of the Lobster Queen...
and her court
of lovely lobster maidens.
Entertainment
by John Van Horton
and the Music Extrusion.
Mmm. I do love those guys.
As a matter of fact, Gene,
you were conceived
to a J.V.H. song.
And I plan to return the favor.
- [ Rings ]
- Oh, great.
I mean, hi, Hugo.
I couldn't help but notice,
yours is the only window
on the street...
without a Lobsterfest poster
in it.
Yeah.
Why might that be?
Because Lobsterfest
is stupid!
What?
I'll handle this, Ron.
Put the sign up.
It's the law.
- It's the law?
- Martial law.
I'm Grand Marshal
of the fest this year!
Hugo, such a fancy sash.
You look like Sissy Spacek
in Carrie.
[ Laughs ]
Oh, thank you.
But, Hugo, as a health
inspector,
you must know how disgusting
lobsters are, right?
They're bottom-feeders
that eat garbage all day.
Huh. They like garbage?
Then they must eat here!
[ Laughing ]
In your face, Bob.
And now in your window!
Come on, Ron.
Let's make like a lobster
and get the shell out of here.
All right.
[ Bell Rings ]
- [ Rings ]
- Hey, my two best customers!
- Two burgers coming up.
- No burgers for me, Bob.
I'm saving my appetite
for Lobsterfest.
None for me either, Bobby.
I just come by to show you
my new lobster cracker.
Check it out--
Titanium with
butter-resistant grips.
It's the one
the astronauts used.
Teddy, you think the astronauts
brought a lobster cracker
to space?
Yeah. That's what
it says on the box.
Look.
"The one the astronauts
used in space!"
I spent $49 on this.
Hey, I bet you kids
are old enough...
to crack your own claws
this year, right?
- We don't celebrate
Lobsterfest.
- What?
We're like Jews on Christmas.
Or Jews For Jesus on Hanukkah.
Or me at a lesbian bar...
last night.
Watched a hockey game
at a lesbian bar, Bob.
It was like
I was invisible.
Uh--
And who knows the name
of the delicious paste...
that collects here
in the pancreas?
Tomalley!
Correct.
- [ Clears Throat ]
Excuse me, Miss Labonz?
- Yes, Louise.
My family
doesn't observe Lobsterfest.
I should be
excused from class,
and/or given an "A."
Thank you. Good night.
Louise, I don't normally
use this argument,
but if everyone else
is doing it, you should too.
- [ Thunderclap ]
- [ Grunts ]
Attention, students.
The tropical storm
has changed course,
and has been upgraded
to a hurricane.
It could hit town
at any moment.
Don't worry.
We have an emergency plan.
It's called
"Talking it Through."
Now who here thinks
the hurricane was caused
by something bad they did?
What about you, Nicholas?
That thing you told me?
In confidence?
Say it.
- I rub my genitals
on the couch.
- Mm-hmm.
We're all gonna die
because of you!
[ Students Scream ]
It's weather
only a lobster could love,
but sadly, there will be
no Lobsterfest.
This reporter
is getting his bib off.
Ha, ha!
Stupid, failure weatherman...
and your failed Lobsterfest.
Where's your ugly red
sea bug god now?
All right, hold hands.
Come on,
down to the basement.
Bob, we have to close.
A hurricane is coming!
I know. Isn't it great?
Lobsterfest is canceled!
So this town
is gonna be crawling
with empty bellies...
ready to eat Bob's Burgers,
baby!
Bob, you're crazy.
I think you're crazy!
'Cause it's crazy
not to sell burgers
during a hurricane!
Bob's Burgers
is open for business!
Oh.
[ Crackling ]
Is that all you got, storm?
[ Tinkling ]
Wind chimes! Aaah!
[ Muffled ]
Bob, I'm not sure
staying open is safe.
Suppose the hurricane
tears right through here.
I'll chance it!
[ Bell Rings ]
Look who I found
trying to stay dry
in the bounce house.
The entire royal court
of lobster maidens.
[ Gasps ]
Oh, you poor things!
Welcome,
Your Highnesseses.
Uh, you are henceforth known
as the Royal Cows.
Bob!
Uh, well,
something like that.
[ Chuckles ]
I'll go throw on
some burgers.
Hot coffee coming up!
I'd really rather
get my lips
around that beer tap.
Hi, guys.
Hey, Gretchen!
Hi!
Oh, lobster maiden!
Teddy, this is Gretchen.
She cuts my hair.
How you doing?
Hey, are you still
working nights at the cop bar?
Nah, there was
a groping incident.
[ Gasps ]
I apologized,
but they fired me anyway.
- [ Laughs ]
- Oh, she's too much.
- Really is.
- [ Bell Rings ]
Hey, you open?
Mm-hmm.
- You got food?
- Yup.
- Beer?
- Absolutely!
- Atmosphere?
- Yeah-- N--
Ah, good enough.
Whoa, Bobby.
I think this might develop
into a party-type situation!
You kids stay down
in the basement.
I already picked a corner
for the bathroom.
That one, where I went.
And I picked that corner.
Hey, we've got two bathrooms!
Mom, I'm coming up!
[ Linda ]
Just stay down there.
They're gonna need you
to help repopulate the Earth
when this is all over.
Ew! You want us to mate
with each other?
[ Linda ] No.
You'll mate with the other kids
in other basements.
Keep talking.
All right!
J.V.H. unplugged!
Look at all that
wet gray hair.
Oh, Bobby, look at Hugo.
Oh, and poor wet Ron.
Yeah. Isn't it hilarious?
Bobby.
All right, I'll let 'em in.
I just want to give 'em
a pressed ham first.
- Stop it!
- Come on, let me.
All right.
Sorry for using
all of your napkins.
I want to thank you
for bringing us in, Bob.
It was totally Linda's idea.
She is so damn considerate!
You have everything,
and I have nothing.
God, so alone!
Mmm.
[ Slurps ]
Lobsterfest was all I had,
and now that's gone too.
Look at me. I'm a joke!
Yeah, that's too bad.
Hey, Bobby, some
of the lobster maidens...
are open to the idea
of a wet-gown contest.
Want to put up a prize?
Uh, how about a towel?
[ Laughs ]
Oh, my God.
That's so funny.
[ Laughs ]
Gretchen, have you,
uh, met Hugo?
He was gonna be
Grand Marshal at,
uh, Lobsterfest.
Ooh. Nice sash.
Ever take it off?
Well, actually, on Monday...
I have to dry-clean it
and give it back.
Hugo, Gretchen
is into authority figures.
Cops, firemen--
even mailmen, if they have
an important route.
Oh, my gosh. So am I!
What, you're into mailmen?
Well, if they have
an important route.
I think what Bob's saying is,
she likes a man
with a badge.
You have a badge.
Hey, Gretchen!
Huh?
Hey, Hugo's also
a health inspector.
That's like
being a food sheriff.
This is my badge.
Mmm. Kind of small.
You got a gun?
Uh, no.
Actually, I'm not, uh--
Mmm.
licensed to carry a firearm.
I do have
a food safety thermometer,
and it's very sharp.
Pull it out, Hugo.
Yeah, pull it out,
Hugo.
[ Laughing ]
Whoa! Watch out.
Here it is.
Ooh.
"Unsafe range."
I like my pork
a little pink.
♪ [ Funky Guitar ]
[ Man ]
Ahhh! Uhh!
Oh, yeah!
Mmm.
Tina,
what are you doing?
I'm working
on my mating list...
for when we have to repopulate
the world.
Let me see.
Gay. Gay.
Mythical creature.
Gay mythical creature.
Mmm. Good luck.
Guys, we're wasting time here.
We gotta sneak out.
Sneak out?
But there's a hurricane.
That's my point.
We should be out there,
in the wind and rain, looting!
Looting?
So how do we do this
looting thing exactly?
It's easy.
You grab anything
that's not nailed down.
Anything?
Like this brick?
It's yours.
Free brick!
- Free quarter.
- Free phone numbers.
- Free seaweed.
- Gene, free plywood.
Whee!
Hey, Bob, the cash register
won't open,
and you're serving
burgers so fast,
I don't even know
who to get an I.O.U. from.
Relax, Linda.
I'll take care of it.
[ Groans ]
Hey, hey, hey, hey.
Listen up, listen up.
You're all my friends,
and friends don't
charge friends.
The burgers are free,
people!
[ Cheering ]
Everything is gonna be free!
Bob, I thought the point
of staying open during
a hurricane was to make money!
This is way more important
than money, Lin!
Lobsterfest is dead.
Bobsterfest killed it!
[ Cheering ]
[ Man ]
Long live Bobsterfest!
Looting is hard.
[ Sighs ]
I think I'm getting
loot glutes.
This stuff sucks.
Let's go home.
Hello!
What have we here?
Maybe he's lost.
Check his collar.
Get him, Gene!
Looks like this little guy
got into some
office supplies.
Yeah, those rubber bands
don't look comfortable.
You should take 'em off.
Aaah!
This is our one chance
to see what everyone else
is talking about.
What do you mean?
Aaah!
We're gonna eat lobster tonight!
But that goes against
everything we were raised
to believe in!
Aaah!
It doesn't
go against everything.
Okay? But it's a start.
Aaah!
Now's our chance to taste
the forbidden fruit...
that has been kept from us
our whole lives.
Are you with me?
Yeah!
Okay.
And one man's generosity
has turned Lobsterfest
into Bobsterfest.
We're trying to get a word
with Bob himself here.
[ Slurring ]
I love you, Scott Bags!
[ Chuckles ]
Yeah, there's
a cable on that.
You can't go over there.
You come with me!
Yeah, okay.
Can I get
my mic back, please?
You come up and get it.
Give me the mic!
- [ Chanting ]
Bob! Bob! Bob!
- Whoa! Oh, wow!
This feels weird!
- Hey, bro.
- Did I hook you up
or what, Hugo?
Whoo!
Hey, where are we going now?
Over here?
Who decides which way we go?
There's Linda, my wife!
Hey, Linda, you look mad.
Let's go the other way.
Turn around.
Bye, Linda.
How you feeling, Bob?
[ Groans ]
What?
Oh, my God. Lin!
The restaurant's destroyed.
The hurricane swept
right through here.
We got hit!
Actually, the hurricane
missed us, Bob.
[ Birds Twittering ]
It's beautiful out.
♪ [ Humming ]
Hmm.
You were the hurricane,
schmuck!
[ Groans ]
Hey, Gretchen.
Do you have some sweat pants
I can put on?
[ Groaning ]
Linda.
Uh, Linda.
I don't feel well.
I can't even look at you.
I did this?
You and the mob you incited
with free beer and burgers.
Oh, who bent
my little spindle thing?
That's what you notice?
Okay, Lin,
it looks bad now,
but we made a lot
of new friends last night.
Once word spreads
that Bob needs help,
this place
will be jammed again.
The biggest problem
is gonna be finding a job
for everybody who wants one.
Do you remember
where we bought this?
I really love it.
♪ [ Funky Guitar ]
[ Man ]
Ahhh!
Okay, technical problems
from last night
have been resolved.
Hair dryer plus waffle iron
plus toaster...
equals boiling water.
So how do we kill this guy
before we boil him?
We could teach
the lobster to drive...
and wait until
it gets into an accident.
Orwe could hire an assassin.
No, idiots,
you boil lobsters alive.
What? That doesn't sound right.
Yep. Until he's dead.
And then we boil him
some more.
Here we go.
Wait, this doesn't
feel right.
Doing it in a dark room
with toilet paper
around my neck?
I thought my first time
eating lobster
would be special.
[ Man ]
And now please join
Mr. and Mrs. Jimmy Jr....
as they eat their
first lobster!
Mmm, mmm.
Mmm. Mmm.
I thought my first time
eating lobster
would be different too.
[ Crowd Chanting ]
Gene! Gene! Gene!
[ Gene Farting ]
They're waiting for you
in the hot tub, Gene.
Excellent!
Whee!
[ Chomping ]
And the next day do it again--
same songs, different lobsters.
What's the matter
with you two?
Come on, Louise.
Is this really
how you imagined
your first time?
Yes.
[ Sighs ]
Okay, not quite.
[ Man ]
Louise, today you pay
the super price...
for your super crimes.
Enjoy your last meal.
It'll do just fine--
in a pinch!
[ Both Screaming ]
Maybe we have
been rushing things.
I want to wait till
I'm ready. Let's not
give in to peer pressure.
Let's release the lobster
back into the supermarket
from whence he came!
I guess you're right.
Looks like this guy's
the one that got a--
Oh, whoops!
I guess we're
having lobster.
It was meant to be.
When you get married,
just pretend it's your
first time eating lobster.
No problem.
[ Man On P.A. ]
Down it comes!
This stunning butter sculpture,
the likeness of Julia Child,
was made from every available
stick and pat of butter...
within the local
and outlying communities.
Oh! And there goes Julia's feet!
What? Lobsterfest is back on?
Hey, guys, um,
you're not going
to Lobsterfest, are you?
Uh--
I'm in kind of a bind, fellas.
There's a mailbox
in the middle of my restaurant.
Oh! Can you mail this
for me?
Wait. Hey, guys?
There he is, my buddy, Hugo!
Hi.
Oh, hi, Bob.
Hi, Bobby.
What are you both
doing right now?
My, uh, place, uh,
happened to get destroyed
last night.
Oh, really?
Yeah.
In the middle of--
Bob, I'm very busy.
I have tables and tables
of bisque to judge.
Hey, I hooked you two up
last night,
and you guys kind of broke
the baby-changing station
in the bathroom.
[ Chuckles ]
Slap him
with a citation, Hugo.
I want to watch.
Baby likes civil authority?
Yes, I love civil authority.
I'll show baby civil authority.
Stilts guy!
You fell through my window.
Lot of glass on the floor.
Where you going?
Got to go, Bob!
If I stay still too long,
I fall over!
P-People! Wait! Stop!
Wait! People!
Do you think you can
just ignore me?
[ Both Slurping ]
Well, as far
as accidental death goes,
this one was pretty tasty.
I feel tingly.
Do you feel tingly?
I think he's having
an allergic reaction.
We should do something.
Yeah, let's sit on him
and see if he pops.
[ Shouts ]
[ Groans ]
No, we should take him
to Lobsterfest.
They have a medical tent.
And I could get more lobster!
Oh, pop!
I'm trying!
Let's hear it
for John Van Horton
and the Music Extrusion!
Uh, it's me. Bob!
- [ Man Shouting ]
Lobsterfest rocks!
- Bob. Bob.
- Bob.
- [ Man ]
Get off the stage!
[ Chuckling ]
Okay, settle down.
Listen, what's going on here?
What are we doing?
♪ [ Guitar Tuning ]
Last thing I remember,
you were all in my place
and it was Bobsterfest.
I want to get back to that.
Let's go back to that!
Or at the very least,
40 or 50 of you
come with me right now...
and help me clean up
the restaurant!
♪ [ Guitar: Sour Note ]
Not all at once.
[ Man ]
Clean it yourself!
Whoa, Dad's on the stage
at Lobsterfest.
My eyes don't work.
Paint me a word picture.
Kids? What are you doing here?
- Nothing.
- What's wrong with Gene?
He looks horrible.
- He looks like
he always looks.
- No, he doesn't. Does he?
Looks like an allergic--
[ Gasps ]
Did you eat lobster?
I, uh--
He refuses
to answer that.
What's wrong with you people?
- Look at my son!
- Hello.
You did this!
You and your disgusting
food fetish!
Bob, get off the stage.
You're disorderly.
Oh, yeah?
Maybe I should get disorderly
with this lobster pot here.
That's right, you heard me--
You trash my restaurant,
I trash Lobsterfest--
starting with this lobster pot.
[ Sizzles ]
Ow! It's hot.
Let's leave that alone.
Oh, but I-I see some butter.
You wouldn't like it
if someone messed
with your precious butter!
Like stuff a big,
hairy toe in it!
Bob, put your foot back
in your sock slowly.
I'm authorizing myself to use
my brand-new beanbag gun
to subdue you.
Excuse me. I'm sorry.
Excuse me. excuse me.
Bob! No! This isn't you!
This is me, Linda!
This is the me that they made.
And look what they did
to our son.
That's not
how he normally looks, is it?
Bobby, listen to me.
Excuse me. I'm sorry.
Oh, sorry.
You don't have
to keep moving!
You're not a bottom-feeder, Bob!
No, I'm not a bottom-feeder.
I'm a burger man.
[ Sniffles ]
All right, I'm leaving.
I'm sure that's
what everybody wants.
- Oh, what happens if I--
Oh, whoops!
- Ow!
Ow!
[ Crowd Exclaims, Murmurs ]
Bobby, are you okay?
Excuse me. Uh, excuse me.
Oh, my God!
All the butter's
been contaminated by Bob,
and there isn't any more
in town!
Aaah!
[ Chattering ]
Bob destroyed Lobsterfest!
Can't you just eat lobster
without butter?
[ Crowd Shouts ]
Well, why don't you
call it Butterfest?
- It brings out
the succulence, jerk!
- Yeah!
- So what should we do with him?
- Throw him in the shell pile!
- Shell pile?
- [ Muffled ]
Shell pile! Shell pile!
[ Chanting ]
- Oh, boy.
- Excuse me. Excuse me. Sorry.
Maybe Bob shouldn't have
threatened your butter,
and he definitely
should have charged you
for the burgers--
[ Booing ]
but he opened
his beautiful heart last night,
and you boiled it alive
like a lobster!
All you're doing
is making us hungrier!
- Shell pile!
Sorry, Bobby.
I used a bad analogy.
Hugo, this doesn't
seem right.
What? I have a girlfriend;
Bob's about to be thrown
onto a shell pile--
I've had this exact fantasy.
[ Ron ]
Come on, Hugo.
If Bob hadn't been
your wingman last night,
you'd be another lonely guy
in a satin sash.
I was doing fine!
I don't need a wingman!
Oh, no?
[ Ron ]
♪ Wingman,
flying with the eagles ♪
he's trying to help you out ♪
♪ Wingman, Wingman
♪ Wingman
[ Groans ]
Damn it, Ron!
All right, attention,
people!
Stop it, everyone!
Slow down!
I'm the health inspector.
Someone once told me
that's like being
the food sheriff.
This vat of butter
isn't contaminated by Bob
until I say so!
I have with me
a dairy purity spectrometer.
- Oh!
- Now, give me some room.
Give him some room!
Thank you, Gretchen.
Ow! You stabbed me!
That's just epinephrine.
You're in anaphylactic shock.
Mm, you're a handsome shrimp.
You just jumped
to the top of my list.
It's a mating list
for when the world ends.
Can I get your e-mail?
No.
I have finished
my butter analysis.
Bob's skin flakes, arm hair
and fingernail dirt
are all present.
- [ Together ]
No!
- Let me finish!
They're present,
but not at threatening levels.
The butter
is grade "C" to D-minus.
Fit for everyone
except babies and people
with compromised immune systems.
In other words, get your bib on!
[ Cheering ]
Man, that was
the best Lobsterfest ever.
Yeah. Turns out people
are hard on the outside
and soft on the inside.
Like, uh--
Uh--
Oh, I don't know.
Like a-- like a crab.
Yup. People are just like crabs.
And we witnessed the birth
of a new tradition--
Every year on Lobsterfest Eve,
we trash Bob's place.
No, no, no, no.
Right?
Let's start now!
Gene, you swear
you didn't have lobster?
You've always
looked like this?
I was born like this.
Uh, I need a picture to compare.
Oh, my God.
You do always look like this.
[ Gene, Muffled ]
Hello, gorgeous!
[ Growls ]
[ Bell Rings ]
Bob, Linda.
Hey, Hugo.
Where's Gretchen?
She's a firecracker,
that Gretchen.
You sure she's
not more than
you can handle, Hugo?
Gretchen just
broke up with me.
She said she was more
than I could handle.
Oh.
It was ugly.
She said she didn't mind
a small badge,
but said I didn't know how
to use it, Bob!
[ Together ]
Ouch.
Oh, that's too bad.
I don't need your pity!
- So! Here we are.
Surprise inspection!
- Oh.
Pencil!
[ Ron ]
Pencil.
Pad!
Pad.
Ooh, bent spindle.
Ron! Shut it down!
[ Lobsterfest Announcer ]
Let's here it
for John Van Horton...
and the Music Extrusion!
[ Man ]
Check.
♪ [ Drumroll ]
[ Amplifier Feedback ]
♪ [ Electric Guitar Tuning ]
[ Man ]
It's this one here!
[ Feedback Continues ]
[ Man #2,
Indistinct ]
It's this one.
Turn it off!
[ Feedback Stops ]
[ Man #3 ]
You suck!
♪ [ Guitar
Chord ]
Play something!
[ Man #1 ]
One, two,
three, four!