本视频仅供英语学习交流，严禁用于商业途径
更多资源敬请关注公众号：晨雨资料库
[ Strumming Ukulele ]
[ Whirring, Chirping ]
Okay.
Burn Unit, commence.
You go first.
Oh, I play soccer, 'cause
I forgot I have hands.
Burn! I'm on the news
because I have a huge head.
Burn!
I can't outrun a lawn mower
'cause my dress is so tight.
- Oh! I'm dead.
- Burn!
♪ [ Western ]
Whoa. It's Banjo.
Oh, I'm a cowboy,
and I got--
Wait, wait, wait.
Suspend Burn Unit.
This is a great movie.
It's a spaghetti western--
the best one--
underappreciated.
He plays a banjo.
♪ [ Strums Chord ]
Yeah, I can see that.
They made
a whole bunch of these.
Dad. Do we have anything
bigger than this?
Oh, Gene.
What did you do?
Nothing yet.
Just planning ahead.
What are you guys watching?
[ Bullet Ricocheting ]
Nothing.
Go back to bed.
The Burn Unit
is just me and Dad.
[ Gunfire ]
Whoa! Did he just shoot bullets
out of his banjo?
- Yes.
- Damn!
Oh, you like that, Gene?
'Cause we're changing
the channel.
No, no! Let's watch it.
This is pretty much
the beginning.
What?
Gene, sit here.
[ Shouts ]
What?
[ Grunts ]
It's like pushing
a couch off the couch!
Yah!
Here.
Hold my plunger.
Yah!
[ Thuds ]
[ Gene ]
Ow!
Ah! We are just
so thrilled that you
chose us to cater the event.
Mom. Mom.
Fill me up.
I just hope we can live up
to last year's event.
Mom.
That Colleen Caviello--
Mom!
She really outdid herself...
and never lets anyone
forget about it.
Just fill up
the little mug.
Ouch.
Right. Right, right.
[ Laughing ]
Okay, Mr. Frond.
Good-bye. Good-bye.
So, what
are we catering?
That sounded promising.
Oh, it's a real
big deal, Bobby.
It's a fund-raiser for Tina's
Conflict Resolution Club.
Colleen Caviello
made the food last year.
This year she can go...
blow a balloon.
Yay! You're catering
our fund-raiser.
- That's great.
How much does it pay?
- Nothin'.
- Nothing?
- It's a benefit, Bobby.
- It's a spaghetti dinner.
- But we don't make spaghetti.
This is school
fund-raising, Bob.
It's a pasta game.
You make spaghetti,
or you go home.
Besides,
it's for a good cause.
Oh, yeah-- to one-up,
uh, Colleen Caviello.
That's a-- That's a great cause.
You weren't there, Bob!
You don't know
how awful it was.
[ Voice Slowed Down ]
This is delicious.
Oh, my God,
I love this ziti.
[ Laughing ]
[ Both Laughing ]
They love my ziti.
And that was
the worst day of my life.
Anyway,
this isn't about Colleen.
This is about Tina.
We're raising money
to buy a bulletproof
trash can...
so gang members can finally
throw out their guns.
Aw.
And we're teaching
conflict resolution skills
you can use in your own lives.
That's right, Tina.
And Mr. Frond is runnin'
the whole thing.
Ugh. Mr. Frond?
He's a tall drink
of... annoying.
-That may be true, but you're
gonna drink that drink, mister!
-I don't want to.
I have worked too hard
to get us this event,
so you'll be nice to Frond,
and you'll make spaghetti
and meatballs!
- No.
- Yes.
- No!
- Yes!
I'm gonna
half-ass it.
Yay.
Dad, check it out.
Little Princess Guitar.
Gene, that's mine!
You never use it.
I'm like Banjo.
- What's the bad guy's name?
- Ceviche.
Ceviche, yeah.
He reminds me of this kid
at school-- Choo-Choo.
- Choo-Choo?
- Yeah. He's kind of my nemesis.
If I'm telling a joke,
he'll say the punch line
before I do.
Vampire walks into a bar
and says, "I'll have a--"
I'll have a blood lite.
Huh?
What do you call
a Spanish guy
with a rubber toe?
Ruberto!
Ruber--
[ Frustrated Grunt ]
What kind of bees
make milk?
Boo-bees!
[ Screams ]
So, I'm gonna
use this guitar...
to stand up to Choo-Choo
like Banjo.
♪ [ Chord ]
That's, uh--
That's great, Gene.
- But I think
your face is wrong.
- My face is wrong?
Yeah, you should do
the Banjo icy stare.
Like this?
[ Laughs ]
N-- No. Not like that.
- [ Growling ]
- No, no, no. Don't growl.
- Like this?
- Hmm. Maybe try that.
Is Choo-Choo scared
of stroke victims?
Terrified!
[ Man ]
♪ Banjo, Banjo
Hey, Gene, Gene.
"How do you plead?"
"I'm innocent."
"Your fingerprints were all over
the murder weapon!"
"I don't have fingers."
"Your Honor!"
I don't have time
for this.
What?
You don't have time
for Food Court?
Where are you going?
Hey.
Wanna hear a good one?
[ Groans ]
What's green and sings?
Go ahead. Do it.
- El--
- ♪ [ Chord ]
- Elvis P--
- Elvis Par--
- Ah!
Forget it.
I'll tell you
what's green and sings.
Elvis Parsley.
[ Laughing ]
You don't say the punch lines
to other people's jokes anymore!
You got that, poo-poo?
♪ [ Chord ]
[ Laughing ]
What the hell?
Thank you. Thank you.
Thank you, everyone.
Thank you.
Anyway-- Gene, look.
They're about to announce
the verdict.
"Guilty!"
"No!"
"Take him away!"
Gene, where are you going?
"What's up with Gene?"
I don't know, lasagna.
I don't know.
You know, cooking spaghetti
isn't even cooking.
It's just, like,
boiling water.
- Hey, Bobby,
can I come to this thing?
- Uh, I don't think so.
Why not?
Some of these moms
are divorced, right?
They meet me,
I meet their kids,
maybe throw
the ball around--
not inside, but--
Uh, we agreed,
no more school events
for you, Teddy.
- Hey, Dad. Guess what?
- What?
I acted like Banjo
and took Choo-Choo down.
♪ [ Chord ]
- Everyone laughed.
- Well, one kid laughed.
Peter Pescadero.
He has a learning disability.
Yeah, but he knows
what's funny.
Now that you've
stood up for yourself--
oh, congratulations, Gene--
can we stop
talking about it?
[ Chuckling ]
Okay, tonight,
I propose, Dad,
that after everyone else
goes to bed-- Gene--
we fire up the Burn Unit
and we watch Canine Criminals...
and then that
stretching show...
and then maybe
a little Beetlejuice
in español.
Beetlejugo.
Beetlejugo. Beetlejugo.
Ayayayay!
I would, except a certain
best dad in the world...
went out and got this!
It's the complete
Banjo box set!
All 12 DVDs
and over 28 hours of extras.
Yeah!
Twenty-eight hours?
Dad, can I see that fork
for a minute?
- Um, here.
- Thank you.
And I just want to--
[ Shouting ]
Hey. Hey, hey, hey!
Hey!
No!
♪ [ Banjo Chord ]
Best part
right here, Gene.
There's only gonna be
two shots--
me shootin' you,
and then me drinkin'
this shot of whiskey.
[ Gunshot ]
[ Puts Shot Glass On Table ]
Wow.
Oh, what a line!
Go ahead,
watch your stupid movie.
There are other people
for me to hang out with
around here.
Tina, get up.
Let's hang out.
Okay. Maybe we can practice
conflict resolution.
Say something mean to me
so I can not react.
Anything I want?
Yeah.
Ha-ha! Well,
your room looks like...
it was decorated
by a perverted jockey.
When you say that,
what I feel is that you're
trying to hurt my feelings.
Oh, my God.
[ Speaking Slowly ]
Why do you talk so slow?
When you say that, what I feel
is that you're trying--
Oh, man, Tina.
This is really,
really boring.
Okay. Well--
Hey, Mom,
you want to hang out?
Oh, I'd love that!
Aw, mother-daughter
bonding time.
Just like me
and my mother.
Oh! Makeover!
Mmm.
Okay,
my little cowpokes.
Time for school.
You can watch
the rest tonight.
Mom! How could you?
How could I what?
How could you
encourage this?
Oh, Louise,
don't be a pill.
A little father-son bonding
is going on here,
and that's a good thing.
These two don't always
do it so well.
Tambourine solo!
♪ [ Electronic Beats ]
Eesh.
[ Water Lapping ]
All right. This is how
you throw a spiral.
You ready?
Here comes a bullet.
Hmm.
Oh, stupid ball!
It's 'cause there's no laces.
- I'm hungry.
- All right, we're done.
Go inside.
I want peanut butter!
It turns out
we bond better...
over movies
that I like to watch...
that I make Gene watch.
- Yeah.
- Oh, that's--
that's adorable.
- I'm going to school.
- Good.
Great. Why don't
you learn something
and become a lawyer.
ABS--
the conflict resolution program
sweeping our school.
You all know my system,
and at the spaghetti dinner,
so will your parents
or legal guardians--
um, Becky, 'cause
your mom's in jail.
Tina, Jocelyn, Jimmy Jr.,
let's rehearse.
Becky, you just watch.
Tina here just found out
that her best friend Jocelyn
told Jimmy Jr....
that Tina is "wack."
And... acting.
Tina, Jocelyn told me
you are wack.
Jocelyn, you skank.
I hate you.
Whatever.
It's true.
You are wack.
[ Both Grunting ]
And... freeze!
Well, that resolved
nothing.
Let's rewind,
shall we?
[ Imitating Voices
Speaking Backwards ]
Let's work out
our ABS.
"A"!
Access your feelings!
When you gossiped
about me to Jimmy Jr.,
it hurt my feelings.
"B."
Be apologetic!
Sorry.
"S."
Slap it!
Well done.
Do it just like that
at the dinner.
- [ Bell Ringing ]
- Oh, enjoy your lunch,
everyone.
If you ever gossip
about me to Jimmy Jr....
outside of
a conflict resolution skit,
I'll punch you in the face.
It was just
a skit, Tina.
I will punch you
again and again...
and again and again
and again--
My God.
What a psycho.
and again and again...
and again
and again and--
Well, the important thing is,
I shared this movie with Gene,
and it helped him
stand up for himself
at school.
Eh, I beat up
a lot of kids like Gene
when I was his age.
Not that I was a bully.
Just kids like Gene, you know,
they get beat up.
Bob, how are
the meatballs comin'?
'Cause they need
to be perfect.
[ Bell Rings ]
Hey! It's just like
your burgers, only spherical!
Hey!
"Hey" what?
They're not for you!
They're for me to show off
in front of the other moms
at the fund-raiser.
Bobby, make one extra big
for Colleen Caviello
to choke on.
Okay.
All right.
Looks like I'm sitting
with you today.
Here's the pecking order.
Me, then either of you.
Which sticker do you like
better-- my purple ladybug
or Susie's red one?
And good-bye.
Hey there,
spew-spew.
Funny seeing you here.
In the cafeteria
during lunch?
Yeah!
♪ [ Chord ]
- Why do you keep doing that?
- Keep doing what?
- ♪ [ Chord ]
- You're weird!
Weird? I think
you mean "antihero."
Look at the hat.
It's Mom's sun hat,
you dork.
You like
finishing my jokes?
[ Munching ]
Well, finish my food.
Gene, you are being
a class-act jerk!
This is all about jokes
from your stupid joke book.
You've insulted
Jokes for Blokes
for the last time.
Mmm.
Oh, don't you even
think about it, Gene.
[ Grunts ]
Food fight!
[ Grunting, Shouting ]
[ Men ]
♪ Food... fight
No!
♪ Food fight
And these two, Bob,
were throwing at each other.
I hate you.
They seem to be
in conflict.
I'm sure we can, uh,
work through it.
I'd like you to take
a look at my ABS.
Um, no, thank you.
Show him your ABS,
Mr. Frond.
We'd all like
to see your ABS.
Okay.
- I really don't.
- And your ding-dong.
Gene.
Gene,
why don't you Access...
how it makes you feel
that Louise is angry with you?
Fine.
♪ [ Chord ]
That's all I'm gonna say.
Well, this is all
I'm gonna say.
Hi-yah!
[ Grunts ]
- Let go of my--
- H-Hey.
L-Louise? Louise, Louise?
You're not using your ABS.
- Um, this is dumb.
- [ Chuckles ]
- Bob.
- Yes.
When you say
"this is dumb,"
it makes me feel
like pinching you
in the eye.
[ Laughs ]
Why did you do that?
So we can resolve this
and set a good example
for your children!
Okay. I will now
kick you in the shin.
[ Chuckles ]
Okay. Okay.
All right.
♪ [ Chord ]
- Hey! Don't throw
Repressed Memory Emily!
- She won't remember this.
Well, this is really
working out, Mr. Frond.
Your system is amazing.
Oh! No, no. No, no, no.
We're gonna go.
You know what
I forgot to say?
Detention! Detention!
And you--
I am gonna cut you!
I'm gonna cut you out
of the Conflict Resolution
Spaghetti Dinner!
- Wha-- Oh, come on.
You can't--
- Too late!
The Conflict Resolution
Spaghetti Dinner will now be
a Conflict Resolution Fast.
Well, that didn't
go so well.
Mm-mmm.
Yeah, he seemed angry.
Frothy.
And kind of bloated,
right?
Mmm.
Maybe he's
dehydrated.
[ Groans ]
Your mom is gonna
kill me.
[ Frond ]
So glad we had a chance
to talk this out!
[ Shouts ]
[ Thuds ]
Emily, I'm sorry!
Detention?
And we're banned from catering
the Peace Club dinner!
- Bobby!
- I'm sorry, Lin. I--
I can't even tell you
how many favors I had to call in
to cater that thing!
How many?
Two!
Tina, you're supposed to
be watching the restaurant!
I'm too upset
to serve food.
- Wh-- What'd you do?
Did you lock up?
- Yes.
- Were there customers inside?
- I don't know.
No one's gonna come
to the fund-raiser now.
Good job, Bobby!
It's not my fault, Lin.
- It was Mr. Frond's fault.
- And Louise's.
And Gene's!
And most of all,
that stupid movie!
Hey!
Hey, don't blame
the movie.
Leave Bingo
out of this!
Shut up!
All of you!
[ Bob ]
Banjo.
I'm locking these movies
in my jewelry drawer.
[ Bob ]
Aw, come on.
'Bout time.
- You're overreacting, Lin.
- The hell I am!
I'm in charge of
a spaghetti dinner that's not
gonna have any spaghetti!
- If we all just
worked on our ABS--
- Not now with that crap, Tina!
♪ [ Headphones: Dance Pop ]
I can't believe
I got detention.
If I were you,
I would teach Gene a lesson
he'll never forget.
I had a perfect record,
and then you tainted it.
- Taint.
- Looks like you got Choo-Choo
right where you want him.
Just give him that icy stare
with some Little Princess
and finish him.
You want a little of this?
[ Shaky Breathing ]
Oh. Oh, yeah.
He wants it.
Now give him the icy stare.
[ Growling ]
- Put him in his place.
- You're dead!
Quiet!
[ Man, Falsetto ]
♪ Do-do-do, sexual
Sexual, do-do-do ♪
Okay, well, I'm gonna
go get Gene and Louise
from Detention.
Great!
Bring some meatballs!
Got plenty of meatballs--
all dressed up
and nowhere to go.
Mmm.
Ah, meatball.
All right.
I'm gonna leave.
Mmm, mmm, mmm.
Gene, this happens now!
Uh, how are we doing this?
- Staring contest?
- [ Roaring ]
Joke-off?
Kick his ass,
Choo-Choo!
Why are their shirts off?
Oh, boy.
I didn't want to do this.
I haven't even pressed
the blue button yet.
- I don't even know
what sound it--
- [ Ferocious Shouting ]
[ Screaming ]
- Stop. There's not
gonna be a fight.
- Oh, thank God.
Let me go! This train
is off the tracks!
Choo-Choo!
Oh, I get
the name now.
I always thought it was
'cause of how he chewed.
'Cause he chews like a train.
- Hey, calm down.
- [ Tires Screech ]
Let's go home, Gene.
You touching my kid?
Sorry. What?
I said, you touchin' my kid?
Oh, he was
attacking my kid.
Oh, yeah? Good.
What is going on
with the shirts?
I'm gonna
beat your ass so bad,
I can skip the gym tonight.
Dad, this is bad.
[ Boys ]
Fight! Fight!
Thank you, Louise.
I have it under control.
- This happens now!
- [ Choo-Choo ]
Kill him!
[ Ferocious Scream ]
[ Bob ]
Run!
I can't.
I've got this friggin' guitar
around my neck!
[ Choo-Choo ]
Ha!
[ Chains Squeaking ]
- [ Running Footsteps ]
- [ Whimpering ]
[ Bob ]
Oh, Gene, push down.
I'm trying.
[ Sighs ] All right.
[ Louise ]
Ow.
All right.
Just so we're clear, we're
not hiding from those guys.
We're respectfully
declining their invitation
for a fight, okay?
Right.
No, thank you.
I would absolutely
get into a fight under
the right circumstances if--
[ Sniffs ]
What's that smell?
Oh, Gene!
Gene!
- I'm sorry!
- Hey! Shh, shh.
I hear them.
[ Gasps ]
They're coming.
Real-- You-You hear them?
- Gotcha. [ Laughs ]
- Louise, enough!
You've been stirring
the pot for three days
and acting like a baby.
Now, you owe your brother
an apology for getting him
in trouble.
Me? Both of you
owe me an apology.
Both of us? Why?
Because we wanted
to watch Banjo?
Because you stopped
hanging out with me.
What?
Shh.
Use your slide voices.
First, the Burn Unit
stopped hanging out.
Then the Lunch Bunch
- God, we have lame names.
- Who the hell am I gonna hang
around if not you two?
Mom and Tina,
the Menstruation Nation?
Ugh!
That's a really bad name.
You're all I've got.
Louise, I'm sorry.
Me too. Don't cry.
Ha! Got you. You thought
I was really crying.
[ Sniffles ]
Gross.
[ Farts ]
Gene, stop!
Oh, my God!
I can't help it.
It's anxiety.
And turkey jerky.
It's so incredible.
Your farts
smell like mine.
Really?
Oh, great.
Are you guys
bonding again?
[ Chuckles ]
I'm sorry, but that's
a huge discovery.
A fart is like a fingerprint,
and we have the same
fingerprints.
- High five.
Put your hand up.
- Ugh!
All right.
I swear my farts smell
like your farts, Dad.
I don't think so, Louise.
Oh, wait. Wait,
wait, wait, wait.
[ Small Fart ]
Huh?
No. That smells
like your mom's.
No!
Oh, your mom.
What are we gonna do
about Mom and Tina?
They could live
in here with us!
I think I know a better way.
[ Chattering ]
I'm starving.
How embarrassing.
Guess people will be
talking about my baked ziti
for another year.
[ Mimicking ] Guess people
will be talking about my
baked ziti for another year.
Oh, Linda,
I didn't see you.
Hi, Coll.
How are you?
Uh--
Thank you.
Tonight, with your help,
we raised over $100.
[ Inaudible ]
It was 110.
I warned you, skank!
[ Growls, Grunting ]
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa,
whoa, whoa, whoa!
Girls, please.
- It's not time for the skit.
- This isn't a skit.
This is real life.
Last year,
the only fighting was to
get seconds on my ziti.
Okay, that's it, Colleen!
Let me tell you
about that ziti.
That sauce
was store-bought,
and you know it!
- [ Crowd Gasping ]
- Ladies, please!
I thought
I told you, Bob--
You and your spaghetti
aren't welcome here.
- But I want to say something.
- No, thank you.
I've had enough
of your... hurt speech.
Would it make
a difference if I...
worked on my ABS?
- Oh.
- I want to...
"A"--
What was "A" again?
Anus.
Amyl nitrate.
Access-- I wanna
access my feelings.
Okay, okay, okay, okay.
Enough, enough, enough.
Everyone's about
to kill each other here.
Let's-- Let's eat!
[ Linda ]
All right!
Meatballs! Meatballs!
Get your meatballs here!
And spaghetti.
Hmm?
Here, Colleen.
Why don't you put these
balls in your face?
[ Louise ] Food fight!
[ Frond ]
No, no, no, no, no! No!
[ Man ]
♪ Banjo, Banjo
♪ Doesn't play it for fun
♪ He's just hiding his gun
♪ Banjo, Banjo
♪ His chaps made of leather
even in hot weather ♪
♪ Banjo
[ Whispering ]
He's comin', gunnin' for ya.
♪ Banjo
He's comin', strummin' for ya.
♪ You can try to talk
♪ But he don't
give a
pluck ♪
♪ Banjo
He's comin',
gunnin' for ya.
♪ Banjo
He's comin',
strummin'
for ya.
♪ He's strumming for you--