本视频仅供英语学习交流，严禁用于商业途径
更多资源敬请关注公众号：晨雨资料库
[ Ukulele Strumming ]
[ Bell Rings ]
I'm back!
-What's all this?
-We're renting out rooms in our
apartment for the long weekend.
We're gonna be
a bed-and-breakfast!
It's so exciting!
I love bed-and-breakfasts.
They're so quaint.
Aren't they?
Random strangers shedding
skin cells all over the house.
Yech. Well, I'm against this
bed-and-breakfast as much as you
can be against something...
and still let it happen.
Like when my ex-wife
wanted to have a three-way
with our neighbor Ray.
Teddy, Teddy, I don't think you
should be talking about--
Wait, you had a three-way
with Ray, the guy who wears
the seal suit down on the pier?
Yeah. I mean, I wasn't involved,
I just watched, but... yeah.
I had a three-way
in science class yesterday.
Tammy's lab partner was absent,
so she joined in with me
and Joey.
It was fun.
Okay, enough.
Doilies, soapies,
extra-expensive
toilet paper.
I love that soft stuff.
I thought we were doing this
to make extra money.
Isn't all this eating
into our profits?
Don't worry, Bob.
It's gonna be money
and online reviews.
And when I die and I get
to heaven, God's gonna say,
"Hey, aren't you the lady
that ran that B and B
I heard about?"
And I'm gonna say,
"Yes, God.
What can I get you?"
Here, hold this.
[ Sniffs ]
Mmm! Smell!
Mmm, smell it!
Lin, you're shoving
things in my nose.
Smell this one, though.
You always do this, Lin.
Whenever you entertain, you
put way too much effort into it
and drive yourself crazy.
What are you talking about?
I'm a wonderful hostess.
No, Linda, you go overboard.
And then if people aren't
appreciative enough, you snap.
That's not true!
I'm a gifted hostess,
and I'm ready to go pro.
It is really soft.
Put it back on the roll,
please.
Or, Mom, what if we just
put Tina by the toilet?
Yeah!
I don't mind.
Almost check-in time!
Tina, Gene,
are your rooms guest-ready?
Yes.
Subjective.
Ha-ha!
Remember when you made fun of me
for moving into a closet?
Well, now you suckers have to
give up your room and I don't.
[ Doorbell Rings ]
Wooh-ooh, a guest!
Javee is a entomologist.
- Javed.
- What?
- My name is Javed.
- All right.
What kind of doctor
is an entomologist again?
Glands? Butt?
[ Chuckles ]
I'm not a butt doctor.
I study insects.
Specifically, the mating habits
of myfungal beetles.
Oh. So what
brings you here?
Myfungal beetles
feed on fungus,
and this town has a very,
very high potency of fungus.
Uh, that's actually
our town motto.
Fungus town!
Tina, why don't you show
Javeed--
Javed.
his room...
Jav-ed?
Javed.
You'll be in
the Equestrian Suite.
Huh?
Okay.
That's great.
He brought a bug
in a jar into our house.
Don't be racist.
I decorated it myself.
You...
like horses a lot.
You like jars.
These are specimen jars.
I intend to mate the queen with
a male and preserve her eggs.
You mean
you're gonna watch beetles
have sex with each other?
Mm-hmm.
Cool.
What's that for?
Ooh, this is
a synthetic pheromone.
It's similar to
what the queen emits when
she wants to attract males.
Does it work
on human boys?
Oh, no.
Well, maybe.
Ahh.
[ Coughs ]
May I store these
in the bathroom?
Sure.
Everyone would love that.
- [ Rings ]
- More guests!
Welcome!
You must be Ed
and Nora Samuels.
Yes. Hello.
Hi.
Come on.
I'll give you the tour.
Okay, this is the salon.
This is where we're gonna
have the meet-and-greet,
and you're just in time.
Uh--
Actually, we'd just like to go
to our room, if that's okay?
Right. We'd just
like to get settled.
What? Why?
Stay here
for the meet-and-greet.
Maybe we'll come
back out in a bit.
No, stay.
It's gonna be fun.
Tina, get Javeed!
- I think he's napping.
- Wake him up!
So, let's go around
and we'll, um--
we'll play a little game.
Let's say what our most
embarrassing moment was.
Who wants to go?
I'll go.
One time,
I coughed at Communion...
and the wafer flew
right out of my mouth
and it landed on my boob!
Who wants to go next?
Javed?
I'll take a pass.
Get me on the next one.
What about when Dad
got a perm?
It wasn't a perm.
It was a body wave.
You looked like
Barbra Streisand
in The Main Event.
You looked like
Barbra Streisand's pubes.
I did.
How about how Dad says "gracias"
in Mexican restaurants?
That's embarrassing.
Remember the time you asked me
to check your prostate
and you made a poopie?
- Linda!
- Oh, remember when Dad
tried to go jogging?
[ All Laughing ]
Oh, come on!
What about when Dad cried
at the end of About Schmidt?
- Gene, why are you
in your underwear?
- I was eating.
What? You want me to get butter
all over my clothes?
Yeah.
Now we just take him
out back and hose him off.
You're a doctor.
Is this a mole?
I'm not a doctor.
And that's a raisin.
Oh. Edible mole.
All right, let's
let someone else go.
Samuels, how about you?
What's your most
embarrassing moment?
I don't know. This?
Yeah, definitely this.
Hmm.
[ Clears Throat ]
Are we done?
Yes, I guess
we are done, Nora.
Are you sure
there aren't any rooms
available anywhere else?
No, everything's booked.
I checked.
Ooh, hello.
Hmm.
I'm cold.
My nipples are so pointy!
Ding-dong!
It's for you.
Mm-mmm. Mm-mmm.
Mm-hmm.
Mm-mmm.
It might be a package.
You should answer it.
♪ [ Scatting ]
Ecch!
Lin, stop stewing
and go to sleep.
I can't help it, Bob!
Our guests are
such party poopers.
All of 'em!
No one has any B and B
spirit at all!
[ Sighs ]
Okay, just go to sleep,
all right?
You'll feel better
in the morning.
Fine!
Gene.
Gene, your foot is down
the back of my underwear.
It's warm down there.
My feet are cold.
Yes, but it's my ass.
Mmm.
Dad, are you still awake?
Yes, Tina.
I was just talking to Gene,
right? A second ago?
Do you think horses get
songs stuck in their heads?
Oh, my God.
I don't know.
Tina, go to sleep.
Dad, do you want any chicken?
Don't tell anyone. There's just
enough for the two of us.
Just go to sleep,
all of you.
I'm glad our guests
are comfortable, Linda,
'cause this is great!
Oh! Our guests!
They'll appreciate me.
I'll just have to
try harder next time.
Hey!
[ Whispering ]
I've got a backup.
I've never been
so happy to be at work.
Yeah, you opened
early today, huh, Bob?
Well, there was a line
to get into the bathroom
up in the apartment,
so I came down here
to do my morning routine
in the slop sink.
♪ [ Humming ]
Whoo!
[ Chuckles ]
Bob, do we have
any toothpicks down here?
Yeah, over there.
Pretty ones?
What do you mean,
pretty ones, Lin?
The nice ones.
How's the B and B going, Linda?
Oh, it's great!
Why? What'd you hear?
What? Nothing.
I bet it's magical up there.
I picture it like England.
It is, Teddy. It is.
But do they appreciate it?
Holed up in their rooms
like dirty little gophers?
Why come to a B and B if you're
not gonna participate, you know?
Oh, they're so ungrateful!
I wish I was staying
at your B and B.
I'd sit in the parlor. And
maybe I'd have a little wine,
play some board games.
Yes! Wine! Games!
- Teddy, you should stay here.
- What?
You should.
You're the dream guest.
Really?
You're the one I'm looking for.
Do you have
any vacancies?
Yes! Louise's room!
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
Linda, Louise's room?
She'd murder us.
She's a big girl.
She'll get over it.
Linda, she won't get over it.
When you vacuumed in there, she
wouldn't talk to you for a week.
Plus, it's not even a room.
It's, like, a closet.
That sounds perfect for me.
I don't need a lot of room.
I'll just bring,
like, one outfit.
Oh, I love it!
I'll get my stuff.
This is gonna be great.
Well, have fun telling Louise
you're kicking her out of her
room, Lin. Wear a helmet.
♪ [ Humming ]
What are you doing?
Oh, hi, Louise.
Oh, hi, Mom.
Hello.
You're holding my stuff.
Hello, my little lady.
Hello, Mom. What are you
doing with my stuff?
I was just welcoming our newest
bed-and-breakfast guest
into your room.
Into my room?
Say hello to Teddy!
[ Gasps ]
Hi, Louise.
You got wonderful stuff in here.
I love, love, love it.
What?
Except for this little guy.
He's kind of giving me
the creeps.
This isn't happening.
Mother, this isn't
happening, right?
Has the world gone crazy?
Okay, come on, Louise.
Let's leave our guest alone.
You mean your guest.
'Cause I did not invite Teddy
to come into my room...
and move my stuff around!
That's right. Come on.
See you in a little bit
at the wine-and-cheese
mixer, Teddy.
Sounds good, Linda.
And I'll see you
in hell, Teddy.
- I'm sorry, Teddy.
- I will see you in hell!
Where are the Samuels?
The cheese is getting sweaty.
They're in their room.
I think they're jumping
on the bed.
I heard the box spring
going crazy.
Sounds like they're "busy."
They should be busy eating
cheese and sipping wine.
What do you mean,
they're busy?
Like, they got homework?
No. They're-- It's--
Busy jumping? They can't
take a jumping break?
Ah, Javay!
You came back
for the wine and cheese!
You got to catch up.
Chug! Chug! Chug!
Whoa, look at
all those males.
Yes, Tina!
One of these lucky bugs
will mate with the queen,
and then she will
bite off his head.
So romantic.
Cheese?
No, thank you.
Eat it.
Mm-mmm.
Ah, have some.
Mm-mmm. Mm-mmm.
Open your mouth.
Open the mouth.
Mmm, mmm.
Just try it.
You're gonna love it.
- It's really good.
- Gene, you're over your limit!
Well, I hate to miss
wine and cheese,
but it's time for these little
fellas to meet their mate.
[ Chuckles ]
Bye-bye.
Wait. I want to watch.
Well, I'll tell you, Linda,
I'm having the time of my life.
You're not gonna hear me
whining about it.
Hey, "whine."
[ Laughs ]
Everyone should be here
for this! They don't know
what they're missing!
[ All Laughing ]
I heard the...
joke from the... hallway.
Do you like that,
Louise?
Yeah.
Oh, it was really funny!
[ Laughs ]
Get out of my room.
I'm your guest in your room.
Did you talk to your mommy?
It's not my mommy's room.
It's my room.
No, I know, and I paid $75, and
I'm just going to stay in your
room for a couple of nights.
- Louise, put some cheese
in your mouth.
- Mmm.
Mmm, isn't that delicious?
Yeah, it really goes down easy,
doesn't it, Teddy?
Ow.
[ Chuckles ]
Just so you know, Teddy, you
have one hour, then I get real.
If I were a pheromone,
where would I be?
Aha!
[ Evil Laugh ]
[ Coughs ]
Ohh! Ohh!
Good night, Javee!
Oh! Uh, good night.
[ Chuckles ]
Crazy lady. She's a nut.
Am I right?
Oh, you're bad!
- Good night, Teddy.
- Good night, Linda.
Sleep tight.
Sleep tighter, Lin.
Don't let the bed bugs bite.
I won't.
Hey, my pillow
smells funny.
Shh, shh, shh, shh, shh.
Good night, Samuels!
- Oh, woo! Oh, my God!
- [ Linda ] Oh, God!
- Could you please
close the door?
- Yeah. Oh, my God.
- Sorry.
- No. With you on
the other side of it.
- Okay. All right. All right.
- Leave!
Why is Mr. Samuels
wearing handcuffs?
They are--
They are escape artists.
[ Gasps ]
They are?
Yes. Isn't that interesting?
Okay, time for bed. Let's go.
All right, Louise,
since you're new here,
I'll show you the ropes.
That corner of the bed
is for eating.
And this right here
is the exercise area.
This is where I thrash.
[ Groaning ]
Yeah. I'll stand,
thank you very much.
[ Groaning ]
[ Snoring ]
Here we go.
Have you talked to your mommy?
Why don't you talk
to your mommy, Teddy,
about your new roommates?
Where is everybody?
Careful, Bob.
I reused the cheese
from yesterday.
- Some of the omelets
have toothpicks in them.
- Ow. Ow. Ah.
Oh, good morning, Yavee!
I hope you and your bugs
are hungry.
My appetite is gone, along with
several of my specimen jars.
They contained
my most virile males.
Oh, no.
Little insects with wings.
How far could they go?
[ Teddy ]
Hey, guys.
[ All Screaming ]
- What?
Do I have bed head?
- Oh, good God, Teddy.
My beetles!
Ohh!
What?
Teddy, you've got beetles
all over your face.
Is that right?
I haven't looked
in the mirror yet.
These males are in
an extremely amorous state.
You mean, right now
they're trying to mate
with Teddy's face?
- Yes.
- Ahh.
Oh, God, Ted.
Does it hurt?
Nope. Nope.
Don't worry about it.
Teddy, you should probably
get to the hospital.
You okay to drive?
No, I don't need a hospital.
I'll be fine. This is still
a magical weekend.
Ahh.
You know?
He's the perfect guest.
What's for breakfast?
- Eggs!
- Ugh! Nothing gets
to this guy.
You! I don't know how,
but you did this.
[ Sniffs ]
I know how she did it.
She used my pheromones on him.
Okay, well, uh,
Linda, everyone,
have fun in the B and B.
I'll be downstairs
in the restaurant. Bye.
Bye, Dad.
No!
You deal with her!
She's out of control!
Okay. Uh, give her
her room back.
No!
Well, that's all I got. Bye.
Louise!
You're grounded.
Go to your room.
Gladly.
That's all I ever wanted.
No, I mean my room.
Go to my room.
- You can't make me.
- Oh, yes, I can, Miss Missy.
I guess you can.
I've never seen
these beetles so aroused.
I have that affect
on beetles.
[ Chuckles ]
I haven't had this
much action in a while.
Are they gonna call me
tomorrow? Probably not,
right? That's okay.
Teddy, making jokes,
covered with bugs.
You are a man! Damn you!
[ Gene ]
Does anything get to you?
[ Teddy ]
There's really only one thing.
[ Gene, Tina ] Yeah?
[ Teddy ]
Costumed characters.
You know, like the ones
in amusement parks.
Really?
Why?
It's the eyes, Gene.
Their cold, dead eyes...
watching you while they
make love to your wife.
- While they what?
- I mean, when they, uh,
go to birthday parties.
[ Gene ]
All right.
Thank you, Teddy.
Oh, thank you, Mom's purse.
Well, thank you, phone.
Yes, I will make a call.
♪ [ Whistling ]
Oh, I gotcha.
Oh, you're sizzling.
I love your sounds.
Oh, hello.
You have costumed
characters, right?
♪ [ Whistling ]
Oh, that's great.
I'll take the hippo,
the fox.
Here's a cookie.
A baby bear.
And do take a credit card?
[ Knocking ]
Brought you some cookies!
What's going on here?
- Uh, we have to go home.
- What are you talking about?
You can't leave.
You're on vacation.
Sit down, enjoy the cookies,
unpack your pointy bra
and your whip and whip him.
He's a naughty boy.
I'm a naughty boy.
Get to it!
Did you just lock the door?
She just locked the door.
I don't know
what's going on.
[ Linda ]
You can come out when it's
time for the ice cream social!
You too!
- Hey, there's my perfect guest.
- Hey, Linda.
I got good news.
I'm upgrading you
to platinum status!
Oh! Platinum status.
That sounds fancy.
What do I get?
It is! You hungry?
You want some room service?
No.
Uh, I guess I can eat.
What do you want?
Uh, bacon burger?
What?
Bacon burger.
Bacon--
First-First word.
Bacon.
One syllable.
No, two syllables.
Two syllables.
Oink, oink, oink, oink,
oink, oink, oink, oink!
Uh, a pig.
Dinosaur.
Bacon!
Bacon burger.
Kevin Bacon.
Second word.
Burger.
Brake pads?
[ Moos ]
Dinosaur.
Jurassic Park!
[ Moos ]
Charades!
You can't guess charades.
Yes, you can.
Oh. Is it charades?
[ Moos ]
Cow. Burger!
Bacon burger!
All right.
Yes. Bacon burger!
All right. I can do that.
[ Doorbell Rings ]
Uh, doorbell.
I'll get it.
Oh, Footloose.
Can I--
Can I help you?
Is there a Teddy here?
Teddy, you've got visitors.
One second.
We're the Fuzzy Buddies!
Are you Teddy?
[ Gasps ]
What's going on here?
[ Screams ]
- Someone's excited to see
the Fuzzy Buddies.
- [ Screams ]
Don't!
No, no, no!
Whoa.
You're a big boy-- Ohh!
[ Teddy Grunting ]
Oh, my God!
Teddy.
Ohh! Ahh!
[ Teddy Crying ]
It's almost
the ice cream social.
Linda, what is going on up here?
You're losing control
of your B and B.
What are you talking about?
Everything is going perfectly.
Right. Right, Lin.
Everything's fine.
Bob, do you have
my bacon burger?
Oh, yeah,
the bacon burger. Here.
Oh.
Bob, can you help me?
I can't chew.
You need me to feed you?
Yeah.
Chew it up for him,
like a mama bird.
Linda, no!
He's platinum status!
You're crazy, Linda!
It's all right, guys.
I got it.
Perfect guest.
So let me get this straight.
Teddy beat up a bunch
of giant animals.
You locked Louise in our room,
and then you locked the guests
in their rooms?
They were gonna leave before
the big ice cream social
at 3:00.
Lin, just give me
the key, all right?
I'm gonna let them out.
No.
Yes.
Look at yourself. Look at
what you've turned into!
Oh, all right.
All I wanted was a charming
bed and breakfast, that's all.
Now what am I gonna say
to God when I go to heaven?
Ohh! Oh! Uh-oh.
I lost the key!
Oh, my God,
what have I done?
All right, all right,
listen.
You know,
Louise picks locks.
- Louise hates me.
- No, she doesn't
hate you, Lin.
I'm sure she's broken
out of our room already.
Oh.
I'm gonna go
deal with Teddy.
Why don't you try her room?
Okay.
Hi, honey. It's Mommy.
Oh, hello, Mother.
Please do come in.
Louise, I'm sorry
I rented your room to Teddy and
then locked you in our bedroom.
I accept your apology, Mom.
Who among us hasn't
gone a little overboard
from time to time?
Ah, thanks, sweetie.
And you're gonna
apologize to Teddy.
Okay.
And there's something else
I need from you.
[ Sighs ]
I would just
cut it up right now.
Oh. No, not that.
Will you please help me
get Javeed and the Samuels
out of their rooms?
I locked them in and I--
I kind of lost the key.
There might be something
I can do.
Javeed, I'm sorry
I locked you in your room.
You're free to go
if you wish.
- You locked me in my room?
- No.
She's completely bonkers,
isn't she?
Look at me when
I'm talking to you!
They're gone.
How did they get
out of a locked room?
It was their greatest escape.
Look what they left behind.
Look. My tongue is trapped.
Now it's escaped.
Now it's trapped.
Hey, look!
They're still
climbing down.
You two all right?
You need any help
with your bags?
No. Uh, actually we're stuck.
Please help us.
I suppose
we could get a ladder.
How much did you
like my B and B?
A lot.
Are you gonna recommend us
to your friends?
Yes!
Are you gonna leave me
your e-mail address?
[ Both ] Yes!
Get 'em the ladder.
Uh, thanks for coming.
Sorry.
Sorry again.
Uh, here's something
for your trouble.
Two dollars.
Thanks a lot.
I don't know what to tip
in this situation.
Yeah. Not two dollars.
Oh, hey, Teddy.
Uh, you all right?
I think I worked through
my issues, Bob. Me and the owl
are gonna go get a drink.
I'm pretty sure
there's a woman inside.
[ Chuckles ]
That's a guy, Teddy.
Oh, that's a woman.
The owl was a guy.
It's a woman.
The fox was a girl.
Oh. Did the fox
leave already?
Yes.
Oh. Linda, you are
a delightful hostess.
Ah, thanks, Teddy.
See you at lunch, Bob.
Well, that was all right.
It was pretty good.
I give us a B.
Mmm.
B plus.
A B and B plus!
My face is sweaty.
Gene, take that off.
Never! Ohh!
[ Groaning ]
[ Groaning
Continues ]