本视频仅供英语学习交流，严禁用于商业途径
更多资源敬请关注公众号：晨雨资料库
[ Ukulele Strumming ]
Phew. Wow.
I thought last year's
Art Crawl was terrible,
but they really outdid
themselves this year, huh?
[ Louise ]
Yeah.
Ugh, bad.
Very bad.
Mm-hmm.
Oh, look at that.
Really bad.
[ Gags ]
Really, really bad.
I think they're...
good.
Dad, why does Art Crawl
suck so much?
Well, it's just a very loose
definition of art, Louise.
And don't say "suck."
Don't say "suck," please.
You're right though.
It does suck.
I don't want you kids to think
this is what art is.
We should go
to a museum.
Whoa, whoa,
whoa, whoa.
Yeah, maybe not.
We should not
go to a museum.
Let's not overdo it.
Let's just walk around
and make fun of this stuff.
[ Gene ] Yeah.
Why don't we just go back
to the restaurant?
Because your Aunt Gayle is there
hanging up her art,
which we're not allowed
to make fun of at all.
Well, why can't we make fun
of Aunt Gayle's paintings?
She's family.
Yeah.
That means never
holding back anything.
Right, pit stains?
Am I showing?
Let's just say your shirt looks
like my underwear right now.
Yeah. Well, look,
no one tells Gayle
anything she can't handle.
That's your mom's rule.
You treat her like
a mental patient.
Well, I mean, she probably
should be one, right?
Yeah, I heard she ate
her lipstick once...
because she wanted
to feel "red" inside.
And she made a dress
out of "live shrimp"
and wore it to Mass.
- Oh, and she shaved her cat.
- Louise, you know
none of that is true.
Except for the cat shaving.
Maybe the shrimp
and the lipstick.
Are you kidding me?
My kid could paint that.
[ Tina ]
Wow. It costs $200.
Someone bought that mess?
How rude!
Harold!
[ Snoring ]
What?
There are some
poorly supervised
children amongst the art.
Get rid of them!
All right.
Let's go.
Keep moving.
Excuse me. Are you a--
Are you a bouncer?
Are you gonna
bounce my kids?
No, no.
- Just keep it moving, chubs.
- Chubs?
You don't have to go home,
but you can't stay here.
[ Coughs, Wheezes ]
Hey, easy, pal.
All right?
Don't touch.
Come on, Dad.
This guy's not worth it.
- Listen to your kids, fatsy.
- Fatsy?
Come on, Dad.
Dad, look me--
Louise--
Give me your eyes, Dad.
Give me your eyes.
Mm-hmm.
Take a deep breath.
You are lucky, pal!
It's not worth it, Dad.
If you hit him, your hand would
smell like ointment and pee.
You smell
like ointment and pee.
like ointment and pee!
You smell
You--
Well, that was awkward.
What is that place?
You don't know
Reflections?
They sell art, not just during
Art Crawl, but year-round.
Reflections.
Sounds like a strip club
the way you say it.
Reflections.
Mmm!
So, brace yourselves
for Aunt Gayle's art show.
Mom said Aunt Gayle told her
they're just adorable animals.
Oh, yeah? Well, that
doesn't sound so bad.
H-H-Hi, hon!
How was Art Crawl?
Hey.
Huh? Everything's
going great here.
We're having fun.
- Oh, wow.
- Lin--
Gayle's here.
We h-h-hung her paintings.
Look at this one!
Look at that one!
Linda, can you
just let me see--
Oh, my God!
Yeah!
Anuses!
Oh, God.
Oh, my God, Lin.
It's a few days, Bobby.
Linda, there are animal anuses
all over our walls.
Just think of 'em
as cute little rumps.
Lin, they're anuses.
I'm trying to think
of worse paintings
to hang in a restaurant.
Um-- Nope.
I can't think of any.
- Bad monkey!
- Kids, stop that.
No. I'm spanking
the monkey!
No way, Dad.
This is the best thing
that has ever happened to us.
Horse butt.
Oh, hello, sir. Don't look
at the pictures of the anus--
Oh, he already did.
Okay.
You see that, Lin?
No one wants to eat with
one of those staring at them.
Come on, you can't seriously
think that this is a good idea.
Well, they're not for me,
but we promised Gayle
she could display her art
for the Art Crawl.
We can't take it back now.
She's fragile.
- We have to support her.
- She's not that fragile, Lin.
[ Fork Clinks ]
Oh!
[ Hyperventilating ]
What happened?
Gayle, Gayle honey, look.
Look, it's a fork.
[ Whimpering ]
What?
Look, it's a fork.
Oh, it's a fork. Heh.
Oh, you're killing me.
She's killing me.
[ Chuckling ]
Okay, so she's fragile.
And that means we have
to be the anus restaurant?
Yes, it means that.
Oh, we can make T-shirts!
It'll say:
"Milk, milk, lemonade.
Around the corner,
art is made."
Bob! Do you love 'em?
Or do you
just love 'em?
Um, how did you--
Why-- Why would you paint--
this?
The inspiration came to me
on a mountaintop.
What should I paint?
[ Creature Chittering ]
[ Chittering ]
[ Gayle's Voice ]
♪ I look at you
I see in you ♪
♪ I see what's inside you
Huh.
He loves 'em!
All right, listen up.
All the suckers
come out for Art Crawl.
And they all want
to pay money for crap.
So paint some crap,
and we can sell it.
- Wait. You're not painting?
- No. I'm management.
You two paint the stuff.
I'll do the rest.
I'll be wheelin' and dealin'.
I'll be gettin' my percent.
Okay, let's see
what you got so far.
Time's up.
Paint brushes down.
What the hell is this?
I told you to paint
commercial, touristy crap.
I'm sorry.
I'm not a sellout.
I can only paint
what I feel.
And I can only paint
the truth!
The robots are coming!
[ Imitating Laser Blasts ]
Hide!
Ah, this is great.
You guys want to be
real artists, huh?
Okay, that's an angle.
I can sell that.
But if you're going artsy,
then you're going all the way.
Someone's cutting off an ear.
I need both of mine.
I wear glasses.
Whelp, what's your excuse?
Don't got one.
Have at it.
Teddy, what's wrong?
You haven't touched
your food.
I don't know, Bob.
It's just the, uh--
The anuses?
Yeah, you know.
Yeah, they're, uh--
I know.
They're like
Mona Lisa's eyes.
They follow you
wherever you go.
Ooh, you're right.
Well, I like 'em.
You like 'em?
[ Groans ]
Yeah. What's the problem?
[ Bell Rings ]
The anus is
the window of the butt.
It's true.
I guess she's just painting
what we're all thinking.
Well, okay, but, Mort,
would you hang them up
in your funeral home?
Course not. That would
be terrible for business.
I'm not an idiot.
Count to three,
but do it on "two."
I'll keep it on ice
until Art Crawl's over.
Thanks, T.
Here goes.
Now listen, Gene.
I'm gonna have trouble cutting
through the cartilage at first.
Mm-hmm.
Uh! Aaah!
While I'm doing it,
just think about your art.
Okay!
All right.
Ready?
Ninja robot. Ninja robot.
Ninja robot.
One, two--
Hey, kids.
Oh, hey, Dad.
I had to get away from
those anuses for a while.
- You mean Mort and Teddy?
- No. No.
Your-- Gayle's paintings.
What are you kids doing?
What knife?
What do you mean,
"What knife?"
Why are you
holding a knife?
Why am I holding a knife?
She's turning me
into a real artist.
No, she's not.
Put the knife down.
I want to be an artist!
Like Leonardo DiCaprio.
That's right.
That's da Vinci,
Gene.
No!
The only way
I can sell this garbage
is if I make them legit!
Hey, wait a second.
I have an idea.
You know who loves
the stuff you kids draw?
You?
No. Your mother.
This crap is like catnip to her.
She can't resist it.
Bring 'em inside.
All right, we need to get
these up before they get back.
Your mom will be so excited
to see this stuff...
she won't even notice
that I took Gayle's
paintings down.
Pretty manipulative, Dad.
I see where I get it.
Thank you.
You should see my taxes.
What's this supposed to be?
A ninja robot fighting
a vampire tape recorder
at Stonehenge.
- Who's that in the background?
- That's my friend Ken.
Why is he like that?
He's an albino.
Oh.
Yeah.
I've never met Ken.
Is he real or imaginary?
He's real, and he does
improvised hip-hop.
Okay. How old is he?
He's 28.
You can't have
a 28-year-old albino friend.
Yes, I can!
I can't deal with this
right now.
- Tina, what do you got?
- It's our dentist.
Dr. Yap?
Why is he nude?
Wait. Has he been nude
with you, Tina?
I exercised
some artistic license.
[ Murmurs ]
- We're switching dentists.
- No!
I can't deal with that
right now.
- But--
- Let's get 'em up.
[ Bell Rings ]
Linda, Gayle.
How was lunch?
Very interesting.
I think the waiter
might have been
hitting on me.
Yes. He was
very attentive.
And he asked you a lot
of questions about food.
What was that all about?
Uh, Bob?
Where are my paintings?
What? Wha-- Oh.
I had to take a few down
to make room
for the kids' stuff.
Bobby! Aw.
- The kids' stuff!
- Yeah.
It's like our wall
is a giant refrigerator.
I love it.
Oh! Gee, Bob, if I didn't
know any better,
I'd think you didn't
like my paintings.
What? No. I--
Aw.
No, no, no. I know when
I'm being lied to, Bob.
It's like when I look at myself
in the mirror and say,
"It's going to be okay."
Fine, look, Gayle,
I'm gonna level
with you.
No. No, Bob.
No. No leveling.
- No.
- Here we go.
Gayle, the thing about
your paintings--
Bobby!
[ Bell Rings ]
Oh, look.
Senior visitors! Yay!
Oh-ho-ho!
Well, look who it is.
Great.
The art store people.
Oh! Reflections.
I love that store!
I love your yarn.
What can we get for you?
I'm not here as a patron.
I'm here as Edith Cranwinkle,
chairperson of the Art Crawl.
I rushed right over here
because there are murmurs--
whispers and murmurs
around town--
that you're displaying--
[ Whispering ]
certain offensive orifices
during the Art Crawl.
Offices?
- Orifices!
- [ Shrieks ]
Not anymore.
I took them all down.
Oh, what a relief.
I'm glad you agree
with my decision.
Your decision?
What decision?
That you can't display
that type of art here.
Wait. I can't?
Absolutely not!
It's obscene.
Obscene.
- Oh, really?
- Yes. I won't allow it.
[ Scoffs ]
Excuse me?
You won't allow it?
That's right, tubsy.
You heard her.
Who are you two to tell me what
I can or can't hang on my wall?
I am chairperson
of the Art Crawl.
Well, I'm the chairperson
of this restaurant.
And you know what?
They're gonna go
back up.
How dare you!
Aw, Bobby!
Gene, Louise,
go get the paintings.
- Here they are!
- [ Both Gasp ]
- Step into the butt closet!
- I will not!
- You should try it.
What's it gonna take to get you
into this rhino anus today?
You are in direct violation
of my wife, Bob.
Oh, I am, am I?
Well, how about this?
Horse anus.
Oh!
- Look at it.
- Aaah!
Chicken anus.
Agh!
Take a closer look.
Fox anus.
Harold!
Gayle, I'm commissioning
a new series of anus paintings.
Two words-- bigger and more.
- [ Gasps ]
- Out!
I cast you out!
[ Edith, Harold
Gasping, Groaning ]
Keep 'em coming, Gayle!
[ Gayle ]
Almost done!
Oh, my! I feel like I could
fall into this one.
Bob, I thought you didn't want
to become "the anus restaurant."
Well, I've embraced it.
We are the anus restaurant, Lin.
A-nus! A-nus!
Kids!
[ Chanting ]
A-nus! A-nus! A-nus!
[ Bell Rings ]
That's right!
Go tell your friends!
Or don't. Either way.
It's your choice.
Hey, you asked for this, Lin.
I'm just doing what you wanted
me to do-- support your sister.
Oh, what a crock of crap!
This is about you
and your pride
and that Edith.
You just want
to provoke her.
Damn right I do.
[ Rings ]
This one big enough
for you, Edith?
[ Laughing ]
[ Screaming ]
Hah!
Fresh from their triumphant
debut at Bob's Burgers!
That's right, gallery-quality
paintings at sidewalk prices.
Art lover,
check this out!
Hey, that's Dr. Yap.
He's my dentist.
That's a good likeness
in the face, but, uh,
the proportions are off.
No, I--
The proportions are right.
Well, I'm getting
adult braces.
So?
So I should know.
Dr. Yap has short, strong legs,
and his torso is--
Well, I'm off to do
some more roller-skating!
You know what?
I've done all I can
for you hacks.
You refuse to paint
touristy art.
Dad won't let me
cut off Gene's ear.
We're through!
We are through!
I'm dropping you
as my clients,
and I'm dropping you
as my siblings!
Go take some art classes,
you wannabes!
Hey, Andy, Ollie.
Hmm?
Huh?
You too, Red.
Come here.
Huh?
You ever
heard of the game...
"you guys paint
whatever I say
and then I sell it"?
Does the winner
get a hug from Ollie?
Ah, Andy, you can have
one of those any old time.
- Now? Sugar.
- Mmm! Ooh, ooh, ooh.
All right,
stop hugging!
Let's paint!
Let's paint shells
and sunsets and crap!
[ All ]
Yay!
Attention, everyone!
This installation
is not approved
by the Art Crawl Association.
It's obscene and should be
taken down immediately!
Well, I'll tell you this.
It doesn't need to be approved
by the Art Crawl Association...
because this is now
a permanent installation.
- [ Gasps ]
- Permanent?
You'll regret this, Bob!
Oh, is that a threat?
Oh, when I threaten you,
you'll know it!
Yeah, when she threatens you,
Okay, was that
a threat?
You bet it was!
Is that supposed
to scare me?
Defi-- [ Coughing ]
[ Wheezing ]
Yes.
[ Coughing, Wheezing ]
You want some water?
He would never
drink your water!
I really need some--
[ Coughing, Wheezing ]
He's fine!
You're fine.
[ Gasping ]
Could use some water.
You're fine.
Bob, water.
No! He'd rather die
than drink your water!
I wouldn't.
Yes, he would!
- I'll drink it!
- No water, Harold!
Please!
Never!
[ Whimpering ]
[ Rings ]
Edith.
Unbelievable.
This is nuts.
I can't believe
Edith would do this.
[ Gasps ]
My artwork!
It's ruined!
They painted underpants
on my beautiful anuses!
Gayle. Gayle, no need
to go off the deep end, okay?
You should be flattered, right?
All the great artists
get censored.
They do not.
Yes, yes!
All of 'em do.
Every-- All the good ones.
Oh, God, what a whirlwind
we've been on.
I feel, like,
let's just put this
all behind us and move on.
I'm going down there.
What?
Where?
To see Edith.
Bobby, don't do
anything crazy.
[ Bell Rings ]
I'm not crazy.
They're crazy!
And they're not gonna
get away with it!
Glue that shell
in the middle, Andy!
What are you doing?
My hand is cramping up!
I ate too much glue!
Andy, Ollie, come here.
Listen, I'm pushing you because
you've got talent, babies.
And I'm gonna take care of you.
Oh, you better believe it.
But first you gotta make
some money for Mommy.
Okay, babies?
You too, Red.
What's your name,
sweetheart?
Devin McJim--
Shut up!
It doesn't matter!
Stop talking!
Start working!
Work!
Shells go in the middle!
- [ Whimpers ]
- Here you go.
One-of-a-kind
original.
Help support these poor
deformed orphans.
[ Groaning ]
Twenty bucks.
[ Gasps ]
Whoa. Dad's pissed.
That's a take five.
For me!
Not you!
[ Groans ]
Oh, look, everyone.
The town pornographer.
Can it, Edith.
I'm here to get an apology.
For what-- standing up
for artistic integrity
and common decency?
There's nothing decent
about what you did.
First you tried to tell me
what to put on my walls.
Then you vandalized it.
Have you no shame?
I have no idea what
you're talking about.
And neither does he.
What?
Hit her, Dad!
I'm not gonna hit her,
Louise.
Hit her, Dad!
Gene? Tina?
What are you two
doing here?
Learning to paint.
We're honing our craft.
Okay, well, good luck
trying to polish a turd.
Wait, I thought
you hated my kids.
My art workshop
is open to all
who respect art.
So I'll have
to ask you to leave.
Then ask me.
Please leave.
Not before
I get an apology.
Not on your life!
Have it your way,
art lady!
Hey.
Poke her in the eye
with the brush.
Oh, I've got
a better idea, Louise.
[ Laughing ]
Take that!
- [ Gasps ]
- Dad, what is that?
It's an anus.
[ All Gasp ]
What else would it be?
What has this been
all about?
You call that an anus?
It looks just like
a black dot!
What kind of anus
is that?
Oh!
Well, Harold, it looks like I'll
need to practice a little more.
I'll say.
- How about one right here!
- [ Harold, Edith Gasp ]
And what about here!
Ow!
- This one might need an anus!
- [ Edith Groans ]
How about this lighthouse!
It has an anus now!
- [ Harold, Edith Gasp ]
- Looking good, Dad.
- Thanks, Tine.
- Rip that lighthouse
a new one, Dad!
I feel so alive!
This is what
God must feel like.
Kids, tell your mother
not to wait up!
Use the brown!
You should've seen it, Mom.
Dad went nuts!
Aw, Bobby, what'd you do?
I got justice, Lin.
Dad painted an anus
on a lighthouse.
Yeah. And on a mountain and on
a sunset and on a sailboat.
And on Dr. Yap.
And Ken.
Yeah, I'm sorry I painted
on your paintings, kids.
They were
in the line of fire.
You painted anuses
on paintings?
Where's Gayle?
I gotta tell her
how I stood up for her.
She's in the basement
trying to get the underwear
off her paintings.
You shouldn't have
done it, Bob.
Are you kidding, Lin?
It's the best thing
I've ever done in my life.
[ Bob ]
Ow.
See, that's how
you put on handcuffs.
They don't look
tight enough to me.
Why are these on me?
Because you
anally defaced
her property.
But she started it.
Look what she did.
Oh. I like the new direction
and wish I could take credit.
But like I said,
I had nothing to do with it.
We'll see about that.
I'm pressing charges.
We're gonna take this
to court!
Wait. Now you're
charging her?
This is confusin'.
- Is Dad going to jail?
- I'll wait for you.
Word of advice, Dad.
Don't tell your cell mate
what you're in for.
I hope our new dad
is a blond.
I can't take it anymore!
Edith didn't
paint the underwear!
- I did it!
- [ All Gasp ]
What? You painted all those
underpants, Linda?
Oh, I couldn't help it.
Those anuses were
haunting me in my sleep.
♪ [ Macabre ]
[ Male Chorus ]
♪ Butts, butts
butts, butts ♪
Huh? Wha--
[ Shrieking ]
♪ Butts, our butts
Our butts are beautiful ♪
♪ Butts, butts, butts
Whoa! Whoa!
Anu-- Anus! Anus!
No!
You were the one who said
we had to support your sister.
I did support her--
until I figured out
a way to destroy her art...
while preserving
her feelings
and blaming someone else.
I thought
those looked familiar.
Oh, yeah. Mom, you painted
your own underwear.
What? How do you know
what my underwear
looks like?
How don't I know?
She wears it
around the house,
flaunting it
like she's all that.
I do not!
Okay, Bobby,
let's go to jail.
Wait, wait, wait, wait.
Can't I--
Edith, can't I just
pay for the paintings?
Well, the retail value
of what you destroyed
was over a thousand dollars!
We'll give you 200.
We haven't sold a burger
all week, Lin.
We don't have
that kind of money.
I got this one, Dad.
Are we good here?
Fine! We'll take it.
Me and you
can settle up later.
Where the hell'd you get
all that money from?
Shh. Don't ask. Don't ask.
It's Art Crawl.
But--
Shh! Shh, shh,
shh, shh.
Louise. What?
Shut your mouth.
It's Art Crawl.
But I--
But the mon--
Shh!
Shut your mouth.
But where did you--
I said shut your mouth.
It's Art Crawl.
Come on, Harold,
let's get out
of this ass parlor.
It stinks.
Okay.
[ Bell Rings ]
Linda, none of this
would have happened...
if you'd just been honest
with your sister.
It's true, Mom.
I've been honest with these two
since the day Gene got fat.
I remember the ice cream
sandwich that did it.
I regret nothing.
And Tina--
bad breath every day.
Not if you like fish.
See how tough they are?
We've been
desensitized.
I'm so numb.
All right, from now on,
I'm going to be honest
with my sister.
She deserves
to know the truth.
[ Gayle ]
I did it!
I fixed all the paintings!
I added pants and huge,
pendulous breasts.
Oh, I'm so excited!
I think it's
my best work ever.
What do you think?
I'm not hearing anything.
Oh, my God.
Gayle,
it's beautiful.
They're great.
- They look great.
- They're great!
- [ Bob ] I love them.
- Fantastic!
Yes, they are.
Very, very.
Yeah, look at that.
I knew it!
I knew they were great!
Here, you hang these,
and I'm gonna go back down
and finish the rest of 'em.
Oh, I couldn't do it.
I wouldn't have done it.
There's exceptions
to the honesty policy.
Yeah. Yeah, I mean, Lin,
you did the right thing.
Oh, thank you
for supporting me.
I want to hug each
and every one of you!
Come here, all of you!
Come on!
All right.
Oh, I love my family!
I can't breathe.
I love you.
Ow!
[ Squealing ]
[ Wind Blowing ]
[ Seagulls Squawking ]
Do you think
she's coming back?
I don't know.
I'm so cold.
Cut me open
and crawl inside me.
One of us
should live.
Okay.
[ Louise ]
Mama's comin' back, and Mama
better see some paintings!
[ Both Scream ]
♪ [ Macabre ]
[ Male Chorus ]
♪ Butts, butts
butts, butts ♪
♪ Our butts, our butts
Our butts are beautiful ♪
♪ Butts, our butts
♪ Butts, butts, butts
Let's get
out of this
ass parlor.
It stinks.